<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Design on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/web-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web Design on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/web-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Colibri Software</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/colibri-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/colibri-software/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Colibri Software builds awesome software. We work with our clients to understand their needs and then produce a simple and effective solution to their problems. Our focus is on making a product easy to use, from websites to mobile apps, we like it when we hear “this is easy”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a special affinity for mapping projects and have send rugged phone apps as far as Nunavut to help collect data for the hunting community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geoff Crouse</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Geoff has more than 17 years of combined Software Engineering and Information Technology Consulting experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technical Sales Engineer, specializing in medium to large scale Drupal CMS projects including new development, site audits and analysis, and expert support services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Account Management, coordinating customer projects with engineering and support teams from initial conception to final delivery, and continued support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Geoff&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove.  Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove pic care of Wikipedia.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ScotiaCom</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/scotiacom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/scotiacom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ScotiaCom (aka Scotia Computer Resources Inc.) is a small, independent business located in the Annapolis Valley, Nova Scotia. What started as an educational software development company has become a leader in the development and deployment of services that allow organizations, groups, individuals and small businesses to take full advantage of the Internet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>