<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web-Design on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/web-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web-Design on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/web-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UX Fist Fighting - Designing For Usability</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ux-fist-fighting-designing-for-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ux-fist-fighting-designing-for-usability/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;10 years of picking fights and getting kicked out of a meetings - Mike Downs shares his personal quest to define &amp;ldquo;usability.&amp;rdquo; Mike will dive deep in to describing why usability is important for your websites and web applications. He will offer up pointers on how to think about your own projects with a user focused mind.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mike has over eighteen years of Internet marketing strategy and product management experience helping create, shape, and launch technology products on the Web. Mike is very passionate about how human beings use computers. Focusing on usability and user experience for the last 10 years, Mike has helped retail giants like Macy&amp;rsquo;s and The Gap as well as government organizations like Tourism British Columbia and Service Nova Scotia deliver experiences that engage their audience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colibri Software</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/colibri-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/colibri-software/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Colibri Software builds awesome software. We work with our clients to understand their needs and then produce a simple and effective solution to their problems. Our focus is on making a product easy to use, from websites to mobile apps, we like it when we hear “this is easy”.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have a special affinity for mapping projects and have send rugged phone apps as far as Nunavut to help collect data for the hunting community.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geoff Crouse</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Geoff has more than 17 years of combined Software Engineering and Information Technology Consulting experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Technical Sales Engineer, specializing in medium to large scale Drupal CMS projects including new development, site audits and analysis, and expert support services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Account Management, coordinating customer projects with engineering and support teams from initial conception to final delivery, and continued support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Geoff&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove.  Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove pic care of Wikipedia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hope Latta</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/hope-latta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/hope-latta/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hope is in her senior year of Computer Science at Acadia University. She loves teaching and encouraging people to learn computer science. While in her undergrad, she worked two co-op terms in the security industry. This past summer she studied web design and directing at Harvard University. Locally, she won the Best Overall Physical Sciences Project grades 7-12 two years in a row at the Annapolis Valley Regional Science Fair. She also represented Nova Scotia at the Canada Wide National Science Fair. When she isn’t coding, she loves dance and various performing arts activities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Downs</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mike-downs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mike-downs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mike has over eighteen years of Internet marketing strategy and product management experience helping create, shape, and launch technology products on the Web. Mike is very passionate about how human beings use computers. Focusing on usability and user experience for the last 10 years, Mike has helped retail giants like Macy&amp;rsquo;s and The Gap as well as government organizations like Tourism British Columbia and Service Nova Scotia deliver experiences that engage their audience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sandy McFadden</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sandy-mcfadden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sandy-mcfadden/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sandy started playing with and building things for the web in 1999. At some point along the way he started trying out different content management systems to help make things easier. After trying to write his own very basic one he settled on WordPress and has been using it to build web sites for years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now he works for Automattic helping people everyday to use their sites on WordPress.com&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScotiaCom</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/scotiacom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/scotiacom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ScotiaCom (aka Scotia Computer Resources Inc.) is a small, independent business located in the Annapolis Valley, Nova Scotia. What started as an educational software development company has become a leader in the development and deployment of services that allow organizations, groups, individuals and small businesses to take full advantage of the Internet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to WordPress</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/introduction-to-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/introduction-to-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WordPress is a free content management system used by more than 23.3% of the top 10 million websites. In this talk, Sandy McFadden and Raina Noel will show us what is it, what it can do for you, and how you can start using it to get your message online.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to install WordPress and get it setup using Posts, Pages, Widgets, and Menus. Raina and Sandy will also show us how you can extend Wordpress functionality and change the way your site looks with Plugins and Themes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
