<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Labnet Dental Lab Systems on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/labnet-dental-lab-systems/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Labnet Dental Lab Systems on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/labnet-dental-lab-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Innovating on The Internet</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/innovating-on-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/innovating-on-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>Have the next (big or small) idea, no budget, or development skills? No problem &amp;ndash; you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t start with building anyway.
In this hands on workshop we will explore pre-product design tools that anyone can pick up to express their app idea. With these tools you will walk away with a means to engage your user base to test concepts, gather feedback quickly, very inexpensively, and early on in the product cycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digitizing Your Mouth: 2 Decades of Digital Dentistry in Wolfville</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/digitizing-your-mouth-2-decades-of-digital-dentistry-in-wolfville/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/digitizing-your-mouth-2-decades-of-digital-dentistry-in-wolfville/</guid>
      <description>Henry Schein is a distributor and producer of health care products and services with a presence in 33 countries. The company is a Fortune World’s Most Admired Company and is ranked number one in its industry for social responsibility. Its Wolfville operation is at the forefront of digitizing dentistry with its wide range of home grown software solutions.
Come help the Henry Schein Woflville team christen its new office. Product Manager Sandy Macdonald will talk about the state of digital dentistry and how our Wolfville team is working on pushing its edges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Sucks</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/project-management-sucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/project-management-sucks/</guid>
      <description>Project management seems to be one of those areas of necessary evil. Disconnected project managers who don&amp;rsquo;t really understand your work coupled with never ending meetings, charts, spreadsheets, forms, paperwork, complicated management software&amp;hellip; Project management can feel like it is more of a barrier than a help to team productivity.
 In this talk, Mike Caplan, a reluctant Software Development Manager, will explore a lightweight tool for overseeing the project processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Jordan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/chris-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/chris-jordan/</guid>
      <description>Chris is a software developer with 16+ years experience with Henry Schein. Not to be pigeonholed, he&amp;rsquo;s got his hand in all sorts of things: Top tier support for an installation base spanning 2000+ customers, Brand development, Application planning and development, Database design, Documentation, Testing, Training, Training material development: web, print and video, Customer support, Installer creation, Phone system programming.
Chris&#39; profile pic is a mashup of a picture of his swiped from Facebook and R2D2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justin Bezanson</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/justin-bezanson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/justin-bezanson/</guid>
      <description>Since 2000 I have continued to expand my knowledge and skills and worked hard to be the best developer I can be.
I enjoy meeting challenges and working hard to find creative and user friendly solutions.
My goal is to continually improve my development process, delivering higher quality and efficiency.
Specialties: PHP, ASP.NET MVC, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, CodeIgniter, Zend Framework, AJAX, Windows, Linux, MySQL, SQL Server, WordPress, ASP.NET
Justin, pictured here, is The Thing from the Fantastic Four.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Caplan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-caplan/</guid>
      <description>Mike has been active as a web application developer and designer since the late 90s, working in the non-profit, university, retail, agricultural, and health care industries. He was a founding partner of HarvestHand  , a platform that services Community Shared Agriculture farms. Mike founded Refresh Annapolis Valley  , a new media professional association.
Mike is the Software Development Manager for the Labnet Dental Lab Systems  division of Henry Schein - a solutions company for health care professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cooper</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tim-cooper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tim-cooper/</guid>
      <description>Tim Cooper is part of Henry Schein&amp;rsquo;s Global Innovation Center as a Software Developer. He is a member of the small team located in Nova Scotia, Canada, that develops primarily web-based software. The team&amp;rsquo;s mandate is to explore and prototype innovative ways that technology can be applied to the world of dental and health care. As a hobby, Tim enjoys contributing to Free Software projects and answering Stack Overflow questions. He graduated from Acadia University with a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML5 and Semantic Markup</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/html5-and-semantic-markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/html5-and-semantic-markup/</guid>
      <description>Come join us for &amp;ldquo;HTML5 and Semantic Markup,&amp;rdquo; a discussion about HTML5, markup, and HTML5 websites that rock.
Open Web Platform: HTML5 and Semantic Markup Mike Caplan will give a talk about HTML5&amp;rsquo;s new elements and attributes that allow us to define semantically meaningful HTML. Semantics you say? What is the meaning of this? Come find out.
HTML5 Websites Show and Tell Dust off your favorite website that uses anything under the HTML5 sun – offline storage, connectivity, file access, semantics, audio/video, 3D/graphics, presentation, performance, big features, or small.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Projects Roundup: Round One</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 19:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-one/</guid>
      <description>Come join us for Local Projects Roundup - Round One, a discussion about interesting local web projects, and initiatives supporting startups.
  HUB Kentville with Frances Schagen  Calling all forward-thinking entrepreneurs, start ups, creatives, artists, freelancers, coders and non-profits. HUB Kentville  is a membership-based coworking spaces where people share an address, resources, equipment and community.     HarvestHand with Michael Caplan  Community Supported Agriculture (CSA) is a member based model for food production and distribution that unites local communities with local farms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
