<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dr Randy Newman on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/people/dr-randy-newman/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dr Randy Newman on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/people/dr-randy-newman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Where Did All The Women Go?  Retaining Women in Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/where-did-all-the-women-go-retaining-women-in-computer-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/where-did-all-the-women-go-retaining-women-in-computer-science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the last 30 years, the number of women entering Computer Science university programs has dropped from 50% to around 10%. Once in the program, women have a higher drop out rate than men.  And women graduating with Computer Science degrees often leave the field and pursue alternate careers. &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-randy-newman&#34;&gt;Dr Randy Newman&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel&#34;&gt;Cindy Trudel&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; have been actively researching this phenomenon over the last few years. In this Refresh Annapolis Valley talk, Randy and Cindy will discuss the problem, the programs that Acadia has in place, and the needs for the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of Computer Science Education</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-computer-science-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-computer-science-education/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With an estimated 218,000 new skilled ICT workers needed in Canada by 2020 to meet the short term demands of our digital economy, focus on our educational system to address this challenge is paramount. The profound lack of diversity within the digital tech economy further complicates the response required. With changes in our provincial educational pipeline well under way, we are still early on in deploying a comprehensive response.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Join our panel discussion focused on defining challenges and solutions for Computer Science education today.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>f5://imagination</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;f5://imagination is a pop up exhibit focused on digital creativity.  This one day temporary exhibit features work from digital artists, makers, scratchers, computer scientists, engineers and pretendgineer, hardware hackers, lego robotics warriors, indy game developers, new media innovators, VR and AR pioneers&amp;hellip;  digital builders of all shapes, sizes, and credentials.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Schedule&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;    &lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10 AM to 12:30 PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;    &lt;dl&gt;Screening &amp; discussion of &lt;em&gt;Hidden Figures&lt;/em&gt;:  The story of a team of female African-American mathematicians who served a vital role in NASA during the early years of the U.S. space program.  Hosted by Dr. Randy Newman (Professor of Psychology, Acadia University.  &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Women in Science and Engineering at Acadia University&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;).  An area of Dr. Newman&#39;s work is in understanding factors responsible for the gender gap that persists in some areas of science, notably computer science and engineering.  &lt;strong&gt;Limited Space: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.eventbrite.ca/e/f5imagination-hidden-figures-screening-discussion-tickets-40998671129&#34;&gt;get your free ticket to secure your spot&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&#xA;    &lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1 PM to 4:00 PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;    &lt;dl&gt;f5://imagination reception. Artists will be in attendance, light refreshments served.&lt;/dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Submissions are being accepted until midnight December 13.  To submit, fill out the below form (bottom of the page).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women in Science and Engineering at Acadia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WISE (Women in Science and Engineering) at Acadia is a group of female faculty members from the &lt;a href=&#34;http://science.acadiau.ca/&#34;&gt;Faculty of Pure and Applied Science&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://kinesiology.acadiau.ca/&#34;&gt;Kinesiology&lt;/a&gt; who gather together to address the unique issues that women in academia face. The group has supported learning opportunities and award applications for Acadia women faculty members. After a &lt;a href=&#34;http://bit.ly/WISEacadia&#34;&gt;gathering held in October 2014&lt;/a&gt; additional WISE priorities have been identified related to mentoring, science camps for young women, and a course offering for undergraduates in Women and Science.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
