<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshav.github.io/topics/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshav.github.io/topics/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia (BA, MA) is the President &amp;amp; CEO of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/digital-nova-scotia&#34;&gt;
    
        Digital Nova Scotia
    
&lt;/a&gt;
. She’s a multilingual senior level executive with over 20 years of combined experience in the private, public &amp;amp; academic sectors. Her career spans five geographic regions: America (North), Africa (South), Middle East, Asia &amp;amp; Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ulrike thrives on challenges! With a proven track record in International Marketing, Business &amp;amp; Economic Development, Channel Management, Government/Stakeholder Relations, Board Governance, Fundraising, Organizational Growth &amp;amp; Public Speaking, she&amp;rsquo;s a true game-changer. Having lived, worked &amp;amp; studied in the USA, the UK, the Netherlands, Germany, Israel &amp;amp; now Canada, Ulrike has combined her passion for inclusive diversity, entrepreneurship, innovation, new technologies &amp;amp; STEAM-education with her keen ambition to help individuals &amp;amp; businesses succeed in local &amp;amp; global markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ulrike has worked in executive leadership roles at the headquarters of prominent technology multinationals, SMEs &amp;amp; Startups, including Intel, Compaq/HP, RAD Data Communications, Commtouch Software, McAfee &amp;amp; Seaside Wireless. Her diverse sector expertise in software, hardware &amp;amp; networking products in ICT companies &amp;amp; software development in med-tech, aerospace &amp;amp; defense industries, provides her with first-hand experience &amp;amp; insight into the multi-sectoral facets of the ICT sector &amp;amp; its magnitude of opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2015: Ulrike was honoured with the WXN Canada’s Most Powerful Women: Top 100 Award, the RBC Top 25 Canadian Immigrant Award, the national WCT Top 15 Leadership Excellence Award: Innovator &amp;amp; the Atlantic Business Magazine Top 50 CEO Award. 2014: Ulrike was a recipient of the Progress Women of Excellence Award: Innovator/Entrepreneur, named 1 of Canada’s top 40 Change-Makers by Canadian Living, and received the Mannesmann Teaching Award (USA) &amp;amp; Fulbright Scholarship (USA) while pursuing her M.A.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ulrike is an elected member of the International Women’s Forum &amp;amp; sits on Industry Advisory Boards with Dalhousie University &amp;amp; the Saint Mary&amp;rsquo;s University Sobey School of Business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ulrike is married and has two children. She moved with her family from Israel to Nova Scotia in 2002.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>