<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teric Greenan on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/people/teric-greenan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teric Greenan on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/people/teric-greenan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Meet R2-Weed2</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-r2-weed2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-r2-weed2/</guid>
      <description>Technology-driven agricultural experimentation. Iterative product testing. Validated machine learning. Pivot. Pivot. Pivot. Welcome to the ag-tech startup world of Teric Greenan and Nexus Robotics .&#xA;With Nexus Robotics , Teric is applying Artificial Intelligence to building a reliable and cost-effective way to produce crops. Their autonomous robot R2-Weed2 is capable of cutting and spraying weeds, fertilizing crops, and collect data about growing conditions. Teric will talk about his team&amp;rsquo;s start up journey, and the amazing technological innovations they are applying to revolutionize agriculture as we know it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nexus Robotics</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nexus-robotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nexus-robotics/</guid>
      <description>Nexus Robotics is a Nova Scotian technology startup, developing autonomous robotic solutions for Agriculture using machine learning. Nexus provides farmers with a reliable and cost-effective way to produce crops. The Nexus Robotics team created an autonomous machine called R2-Weed2, which uses a camera system to differentiate between weeds and crops. The machine will be capable of cutting and spraying weeds, as well as able to fertilize crops and collect data about the crop and growing conditions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
