<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Copyright on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/copyright/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Copyright on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/copyright/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Intellectual Property Office </title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office/</guid>
      <description>The Canadian Intellectual Property Office (CIPO), a Special Operating Agency (SOA) associated with Innovation, Science and Economic Development Canada, is responsible for the administration and processing of the greater part of intellectual property in Canada. CIPO&amp;rsquo;s areas of activity include:
 Patents cover new inventions (process, machine, manufacture, composition of matter), or any new and useful improvement of an existing invention;
 A trademark is a word (or words), a design, or a combination of these, used to identify the goods or services of one person or organization and to distinguish these goods or services from those of others in the marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catherine Vardy</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/catherine-vardy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/catherine-vardy/</guid>
      <description>Catherine Vardy joined the Canadian Intellectual Property Office  (CIPO) in 2015. As a Business Development Officer for the Atlantic Region, Catherine enjoys working with people to identify and highlight the value of IP.
As the Network Liaison and Program Manager at Springboard Atlantic, Catherine worked closely with innovative SMEs, universities and colleges. Catherine also worked in Atlantic Canada as a Research and Innovation Development Officer with the Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council (NSERC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kerr &amp; Nadeau</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/kerr-nadeau/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/kerr-nadeau/</guid>
      <description>At Kerr &amp;amp; Nadeau our job is to de-mystify and to simplify the rules for you, to offer you sound professional advice and superior legal services that will enable you, whether you are an inventor, an entrepreneur or a corporate executive, to execute your business plan, to protect your legal rights and to realize your strategic objectives while mitigating risk and ensuring compliance. Risk is the bane and Achilles heel of most business enterprises, and the single greatest obstacle to achieving your mission critical goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philip Kerr</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/philip-kerr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/philip-kerr/</guid>
      <description>Philip is a Canadian lawyer, and Canadian patent and trademark agent with 29 years of experience. He is a partner in the Canadian patent firm of Kerr &amp;amp; Nadeau  (offices in Halifax and Ottawa).
Philip is also the president of PCTxs Inc., a firm that provides an online marketplace for selling/licensing patent application rights, particularly unexpired PCT national phase rights and unexpired Paris Convention patent application rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IP Matters</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ip-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ip-matters/</guid>
      <description>Take an engaging journey into the world of intellectual property (IP) and software. What IP do you have and how can you protect it? Is it better to use a trademark, copyright or a patent? How long does it take and what does it cost? This presentation will introduce you to the types of IP and why they matter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>