<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Refresh Annapolis Valley on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshav.github.io/organizations/refresh-annapolis-valley/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Refresh Annapolis Valley on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:30:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshav.github.io/organizations/refresh-annapolis-valley/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>CODE: Debugging the Gender Gap</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE: Debugging The Gender Gap&lt;/em&gt; exposes the dearth of American female and minority
software engineers and explores the reasons for this gender gap and digital divide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tech jobs are growing three times faster than our colleges are producing computer science
graduates. By 2020, there will be one million unfilled software engineering jobs in the USA.
Through compelling interviews, artistic animation and clever flashpoints in popular culture,
&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; examines the reasons why more girls and people of color are not seeking out
opportunities in computer science and explores how cultural mindsets, stereotypes,
educational hurdles, and sexism all play roles in this national crisis. Expert voices from the
worlds of tech, psychology, science, and education are intercut with personal stories of women
who are engaged in the fight to challenge complacency in the tech industry and have their
voices heard. &lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; aims to inspire change in mindsets, in the educational system, in startup
culture and in the way women see themselves in the field of coding.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/123004482&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Computer code forms the foundation of modern society. Cell phones, apps, navigation systems,
medical equipment, banking, movie animation… are all driven by code. The more diverse a
team of coders is, the broader their perspective of society’s needs, which can ultimately result
in products that serve a greater breadth of humanity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; takes a hard look at the pipeline question in technology: why aren’t there more women
and minority graduates in computer science? What is stopping them from getting to the
threshold? &lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; follows the various challenges faced by a new generation of women
programmers and the ingenious ways they are using their skills, drive, intellect and vision to
disrupt the traditional, male-dominated tech world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; looks to the past, delving into the history of computing to highlight women like Ada
Lovelace and Grace Hopper who set the stage for today’s technology. &lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; acknowledges that
women have been an important part of computing since the genesis of computers, but have
since been written out of this history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; is not afraid to ask the hard questions and does so with intelligence and a sense of
humor, examining our culture from high (the views of former Harvard President Larry Summers
on innate ability) to low (an app called &amp;ldquo;Titstare&amp;rdquo; presented to a room of tech heavyweights).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A blend of personal stories, expert voices, innovative animation, historic discoveries, and
moments from popular culture are complemented with a cutting edge musical score and
bolstered by a strong sense of purpose. &lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; reflects, at its heart, the interconnectedness of
the stories, the web, and by proxy, the shared vision of a new, more democratic community
made possible by the inclusion of more women in code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Caplan</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/person/michael-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/person/michael-caplan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mike has been active as a web application developer and web designer for 16 years, working in the non-profit, university, retail, agricultural, and dental industries. He is a founding partner of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/harvesthand&#34;&gt;
    
        HarvestHand
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, a platform that services Community Shared Agriculture farms. More recently, Mike founded &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley&#34;&gt;
    
        Refresh Annapolis Valley
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, a new media professional association to help grow the Valley&amp;rsquo;s technology industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike is the Software Development Manager for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems&#34;&gt;
    
        Labnet Dental Lab Systems
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 division of Henry Schein - a Fortune 300 company with a small footprint here in Wolfville.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Caplan</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/person/michael-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/person/michael-caplan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mike has been active as a web application developer and web designer for 16 years, working in the non-profit, university, retail, agricultural, and dental industries. He is a founding partner of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/harvesthand&#34;&gt;
    
        HarvestHand
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, a platform that services Community Shared Agriculture farms. More recently, Mike founded &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley&#34;&gt;
    
        Refresh Annapolis Valley
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, a new media professional association to help grow the Valley&amp;rsquo;s technology industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike is the Software Development Manager for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems&#34;&gt;
    
        Labnet Dental Lab Systems
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 division of Henry Schein - a Fortune 300 company with a small footprint here in Wolfville.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>