<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/refresh-annapolis-valley/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/refresh-annapolis-valley/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>State of Our Digital Nation: Digital Nova Scotia 2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-our-digital-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-our-digital-nation/</guid>
      <description>Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s digital economy is currently valued at $2.5 billion. Tyler Farmer, Project Manager at Digital Nova Scotia, will present a state of our digital nation, reflecting on trends and opportunities, both urban and rural. Join us for our last Refresh meetup for the 2018-2019 year for discussion and drinks care of our host, Annapolis Cider Company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovating on The Internet</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/innovating-on-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/innovating-on-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>Have the next (big or small) idea, no budget, or development skills? No problem &amp;ndash; you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t start with building anyway.
In this hands on workshop we will explore pre-product design tools that anyone can pick up to express their app idea. With these tools you will walk away with a means to engage your user base to test concepts, gather feedback quickly, very inexpensively, and early on in the product cycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Developer Bootcamp: Part 3 of 3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-3-of-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-3-of-3/</guid>
      <description>In this teen Hoist mini series, you will learn about how to build your own web application. Web applications are unlike traditional websites. Traditional websites are largely informational (like the Refresh Annapolis Valley website) where web applications solve particular problems (think Gmail for email).
 In part 1, you will learn the ins-and-outs of building app interfaces In part 2, you will learn how to add interactivity to your web app In part 3, you will learn how to manage app data  If you haven&amp;rsquo;t attended part 1 or 2, you can jump right into part 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Developer Bootcamp: Part 2 of 3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-2-of-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-2-of-3/</guid>
      <description>In this teen Hoist mini series, you will learn about how to build your own web application. Web applications are unlike traditional websites. Traditional websites are largely informational (like the Refresh Annapolis Valley website) where web applications solve particular problems (think Gmail for email).
 In part 1, you will learn the ins-and-outs of building app interfaces In part 2, you will learn how to add interactivity to your web app In part 3, you will learn how to manage app data  If you haven&amp;rsquo;t attended part 1, you can jump right into part 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Developer Bootcamp: Part 1 of 3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-1-of-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-1-of-3/</guid>
      <description>In this teen Hoist mini series, you will learn about how to build your own web application. Web applications are unlike traditional websites. Traditional websites are largely informational (like the Refresh Annapolis Valley website) where web applications solve particular problems (think Gmail for email).
 In part 1, you will learn the ins-and-outs of building app interfaces In part 2, you will learn how to add interactivity to your web app In part 3, you will learn how to manage app data  Pizza + workshop + building</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Succeeding at Failing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/succeeding-at-failing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/succeeding-at-failing/</guid>
      <description>Behind every entrepreneurial success lie the stories of numerous failures. As a mindset, entrepreneurship is characterized by risk-taking, experimentation, and continually challenging oneself to produce meaningful results. It is also about learning from failure, and, where possible, finding new ways to tackle problems that eventually lead to success.
Join Katelyn Bourgoin , a 3X founder/business owner turned growth strategist, for a discussion about how to think about entrepreneurship. Come mingle with a wide cross section of Annapolis Valley entrepreneurs for drinks, networking, and old fashioned discussion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap 2018-2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/bootstrap-2018-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/bootstrap-2018-2019/</guid>
      <description>Refresh Annapolis Valley has been rocking the world of Computer Science and New Media circa 2012. We&amp;rsquo;ve built friendships, business relationships, helped form new statups, educated each other, helped rear the next generation&amp;hellip;. We&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished tons.
The 2018 - 2019 season is upon us! Organizers, visionaries, and supporters of all descriptions, come join us for an action oriented discussion on what our new season should look like. What sort of monthly meetup topics would you like to see?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of Computer Science Education</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-computer-science-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-computer-science-education/</guid>
      <description>With an estimated 218,000 new skilled ICT workers needed in Canada by 2020 to meet the short term demands of our digital economy, focus on our educational system to address this challenge is paramount. The profound lack of diversity within the digital tech economy further complicates the response required. With changes in our provincial educational pipeline well under way, we are still early on in deploying a comprehensive response.
Join our panel discussion focused on defining challenges and solutions for Computer Science education today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>f5://imagination</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 10:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</guid>
      <description>f5://imagination is a pop up exhibit focused on digital creativity. This one day temporary exhibit features work from digital artists, makers, scratchers, computer scientists, engineers and pretendgineer, hardware hackers, lego robotics warriors, indy game developers, new media innovators, VR and AR pioneers&amp;hellip; digital builders of all shapes, sizes, and credentials.
Schedule  10 AM to 12:30 PM Screening &amp; discussion of Hidden Figures: The story of a team of female African-American mathematicians who served a vital role in NASA during the early years of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seed: Hacking Entrepreneurship in the Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/seed-hacking-entrepreneurship-in-the-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 18:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/seed-hacking-entrepreneurship-in-the-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>Seed is a documentary that follows an international group of programmer entrepreneurs at AngelHack: one of the most competitive global hackathons and digital business ideation competitions. Three minutes to pitch. One shot to fund their proposals.
Seed is also a gathering of our Annapolis Valley startup community. The event will feature the diversity of associations, businesses, and individuals who comprise our digital tech startup community. An assembly of our entrepreneurial family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Realtime Web: Intro To Node.js</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-realtime-web-intro-to-node-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-realtime-web-intro-to-node-js/</guid>
      <description>Node.js is a rapidly growing technology that has been making big waves in the world of web development. Node lets you easily build fast and scalable network applications perfect for the realtime web. In this workshop you’ll learn how to get started using Node, its background and history, and the problems it seeks to address. We’ll get our hands dirty building a realtime chat server to get a feel for the amazing power of Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Fist Fighting - Designing For Usability</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ux-fist-fighting-designing-for-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ux-fist-fighting-designing-for-usability/</guid>
      <description>10 years of picking fights and getting kicked out of a meetings - Mike Downs shares his personal quest to define &amp;ldquo;usability.&amp;rdquo; Mike will dive deep in to describing why usability is important for your websites and web applications. He will offer up pointers on how to think about your own projects with a user focused mind.
Mike has over eighteen years of Internet marketing strategy and product management experience helping create, shape, and launch technology products on the Web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Caplan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-caplan/</guid>
      <description>Mike has been active as a web application developer and web designer for 16 years, working in the non-profit, university, retail, agricultural, and dental industries. He is a founding partner of HarvestHand  , a platform that services Community Shared Agriculture farms. Mike founded Refresh Annapolis Valley  , a new media professional association to help grow the Valley&amp;rsquo;s technology industry.
Mike is the Software Development Manager for the Labnet Dental Lab Systems  division of Henry Schein - a Fortune 300 company with a small footprint here in Wolfville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to WordPress</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/introduction-to-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/introduction-to-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is a free content management system used by more than 23.3% of the top 10 million websites. In this talk, Sandy McFadden and Raina Noel will show us what is it, what it can do for you, and how you can start using it to get your message online.
You&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to install WordPress and get it setup using Posts, Pages, Widgets, and Menus. Raina and Sandy will also show us how you can extend Wordpress functionality and change the way your site looks with Plugins and Themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STEAM Powered! Maker Space / FabLab @AcadiaU</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/steam-powered-maker-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/steam-powered-maker-space/</guid>
      <description>The recent and explosive growth in maker-culture combined with the emergence of 3D Printing in Fabrication Laboratories (or “FabLabs”) presents an opportunity for the province to prepare for the future by investing in economic and cultural change in rural Nova Scotia. Acting in concert with the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre and the Centre for Rural Innovation, Acadia’s new STEAM Space is working toward the creation of a Maker Space/FabLab on the Acadia University campus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>