<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Comp Sci Education Week - Build a micro:bit Mini Crane</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creating-mini-crane-with-the-microbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creating-mini-crane-with-the-microbit/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in robotics or do you enjoy messing around with electronics? In this workshop, you&amp;rsquo;ll assemble both the hardware and software needed to create a miniature crane controlled by the micro:bit microcontroller.
Join us as we kick off Computer Science Education Week with this hands on workshop. We are limited to 10 spots, so act fast!
What is a micro:bit? The micro:bit is a small, compact computer based on a 43 mm × 52 mm circuit board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Enter the Side Door</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-enter-the-side-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 18:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-enter-the-side-door/</guid>
      <description>Side Door is a digital platform that matches performing artists with venues to create shows anytime, anywhere, on their own terms. Come meet CEO &amp;amp; Co-Founder Laura Simpson for a fireside chat and live performance with Cassie Josephine (Indie Folk Country princess). Laura and Cassie will talk about the challenges artists in the music business face and how Side Door  &amp;rsquo;s unique digital platform is defining a new business model capitalizing on the power of a networked community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Entrepreneur Chat over Beers</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-influencing-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 16:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-influencing-markets/</guid>
      <description>For this popup Startup Life entrepreneur chat over beers, we will be hosting Avery Schrader, a Nova Scotian living abroad in Tallinn, Estonia. Estonia, for those not in the know, is a tiny Baltic state, but in tech terms it&amp;rsquo;s a giant. It has a population of just 1.3 million, yet produces more start-ups per head than any other country in Europe.
Avery is the founder of Modash, a tool that enables marketing teams to find and verify the audiences of over 50,000,000 influencers globally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Meet R2-Weed2</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-r2-weed2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-r2-weed2/</guid>
      <description>Technology-driven agricultural experimentation. Iterative product testing. Validated machine learning. Pivot. Pivot. Pivot. Welcome to the ag-tech startup world of Teric Greenan and Nexus Robotics  .
With Nexus Robotics  , Teric is applying Artificial Intelligence to building a reliable and cost-effective way to produce crops. Their autonomous robot R2-Weed2 is capable of cutting and spraying weeds, fertilizing crops, and collect data about growing conditions. Teric will talk about his team&amp;rsquo;s start up journey, and the amazing technological innovations they are applying to revolutionize agriculture as we know it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Ladies Learning Code Day: Intro to UX Design</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-user-experience-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 10:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-user-experience-design/</guid>
      <description>Join thousands of Canadians coast to coast to coast taking their first steps learning about application development.
With great design comes great responsibility. User experience (UX) design isn’t just about creating pretty or functioning websites - it’s about creative solutioning and trying to make people&amp;rsquo;s lives and experiences better.
As application designers, we need to remember that we aren&amp;rsquo;t designing products for ourselves, but for other people. Being a UX designer allows you to work with and problem solve for a variety of different people, and empathy plays a huge part in this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUILD: Computer Science Camp for Girls</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/camp-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 08:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/camp-2019/</guid>
      <description>BUILD is a week long dive into the world of Computer Science for girls 11 to 14. We will explore the basics of software development while building interactive artwork and literature, video games, and software that interacts with the physical world. Through our exploration we will also journey through use of hardware, refine our ideation skills and turn our ideas into software. Campers will also connect with Computer Scientists in our community who are changing the world one algorithm at a time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avery Schrader</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/avery-schrader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/avery-schrader/</guid>
      <description>Whoop Whoop! You found me.
I have been starting businesses since I was 12, When I hijacked my moms old laptop to entertain myself while we lived in a barn. A few months later I accidentally started a business connecting people online playing a game that I loved. As a kid I sold Christmas trees, made maple syrup, started volunteer groups, and played in the woods.
Now I have an amazing team and a real vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richelle Brown Redden</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/richelle-brown-redden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/richelle-brown-redden/</guid>
      <description>The Valley Regional Enterprise Network is the only publicly funded organization dedicated to supporting the local economic development of five municipalities and one First Nation in the Annapolis Valley region. Through the Valley Regional Enterprise Network’s BusinessNOW program Richelle helps businesses assess their needs, plan for success and fight the right resources. As a publicly funded resource, the BusinessNOW services are offered at not cost to local businesses. A combination of experience and passion to see the region grow, bring insight and dedication to her work with the BusinessNOW program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teric Greenan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/teric-greenan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/teric-greenan/</guid>
      <description>Teric grew up in Halifax, Nova Scotia. He ran a small vegetable farm in Lunenburg County, Nova Scotia for three years. He observed there were a lot of repetitive tasks on farms that were consuming farmers’ resources. These repetitive tasks seemed like good candidates to be automated. After talking with other vegetable farmers, it became clear that weeding was a massive problem that could be solved by a robot. In May of 2017, Teric founded Nexus Robotics with his close friend who is a computer engineer, Jad Tawil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Camp 2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/camp-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 08:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/camp-2019/</guid>
      <description>Creative Computing Camp is a week long adventure into the world of Computer Science. Using the popular Scratch programming environment as a starting point, we will build interactive artwork and stories, video games, and software that interacts with the physical world. Through our exploration of the creativity of software development, we will learn about where ideas come from, and how to turn ideas into action. We will explore the world beyond Scratch, including 3D design, printing, and virtual reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of Our Digital Nation: Digital Nova Scotia 2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-our-digital-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-our-digital-nation/</guid>
      <description>Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s digital economy is currently valued at $2.5 billion. Tyler Farmer, Project Manager at Digital Nova Scotia, will present a state of our digital nation, reflecting on trends and opportunities, both urban and rural. Join us for our last Refresh meetup for the 2018-2019 year for discussion and drinks care of our host, Annapolis Cider Company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovating on The Internet</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/innovating-on-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/innovating-on-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>Have the next (big or small) idea, no budget, or development skills? No problem &amp;ndash; you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t start with building anyway.
In this hands on workshop we will explore pre-product design tools that anyone can pick up to express their app idea. With these tools you will walk away with a means to engage your user base to test concepts, gather feedback quickly, very inexpensively, and early on in the product cycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming Hardware with Python</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/programming-hardware-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 12:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/programming-hardware-with-python/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to know how to make code interact with the real world? In this introductory workshop to Python programming, you’ll learn the vital stepping stones to controlling hardware using the Circuit Playground microcontroller (microcomputer) with one of the most robust, versatile, and popular programming languages.
What is a Circuit Playground? The Circuit Playground is a microcontroller, or a tiny computer. This computer can easily be programmed to interact with hardware that you connect to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alexander Petkov</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/alexander-petkov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/alexander-petkov/</guid>
      <description>Alexander Petkov is a high school student who attends Horton High School and is one of the co-founders of Spark West Network, a non-profit organization that aims to pull together the diverse organizations, events, and opportunities present in the Annapolis Valley. He is also the Chief Marketing Officer for Refresh Annapolis Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#ScratchFest</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2019/</guid>
      <description>Calling all Digital Builders #ScratchFest is a weekend (April 6th and April 7th) Build-a-thon for kids and teens interested in creating amazing original work with digital technologies, such as the Scratch programming environment, Processing, Virtual Reality, and more.
During #ScartchFest, participants will brainstorm an idea, develop their project, and showcase a final prototype. This weekend warrior event provides an excellent opportunity for coders to invent their own projects and demonstrate their knowledge within a collaborative, creative, and playful environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retro Game Carnival</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/retro-game-fest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 17:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/retro-game-fest/</guid>
      <description>Calling All Classic Gamers! The Retro Game Carnival is a celebration of the video games of yesteryear. From the 1970s to early 2000s, we will explore the arcade, console, and PC games that defined eras gone by. Our game fest will include a pop-up museum, fan-made DIY retro arcade, game tournaments, and workshops.
Young and inspired? Be sure to join us for #ScratchFest 2019 the following day and put your creativity towards building your own retro influenced games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency and Blockchain: The Crash Course</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/blockchain-the-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 17:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/blockchain-the-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>This 4 hour crash course will get attendees up-to-speed on the world of cryptocurrency and the technology that powers much of it: Blockchain.
This unique opportunity runs from 5PM to 9PM, and is limited to 20 attendees. Dinner and snacks provided.
Part 1: Intro to Blockchain Fintech The Bitcoin Blockchain just had its 10 year anniversary on January 3rd, 2019. With several monumental crashes and rushes in its market, no one could say with certainty whether or not the network would be a success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women in Technology: Uncensored</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/women-in-technology-uncensored/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/women-in-technology-uncensored/</guid>
      <description>Join Acadia Women in Technology Society  and Refresh Annapolis Valley for an evening of networking, refreshments, and discussion. Guest speakers Lori Shepherd , Chief Creative Officer Cold Furnace Studios, and Cindy Trudel , Instructor in Acadia University’s Jodrey School of Computer Science, will lead a discussion about hacking the male dominated computer science academy and industry to work for women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging to Be Found</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/blogging-to-be-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/blogging-to-be-found/</guid>
      <description>How to use a business blog to improve search engine ranking Upon learning simple strategies for business blogging, Anita Kirkbride &amp;rsquo;s WordPress business blog (https://twirp.ca/) went from ZERO to HERO in a matter of weeks and she&amp;rsquo;s coming to share with you her best tips for using a business blog to be found. Anita will share her best strategies, and walk you through how to use WordPress to get your search engine placement scores up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ag &#43; Tech = Innovation</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ag-tech-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ag-tech-innovation/</guid>
      <description>Agriculture globally is a 12 trillion dollar annual industry ripe for technology startups looking to bring new hi-tech innovations to market. Where does digital technology and agriculture meet, and what are the opportunities?
Gary Morton (Morton Horticultural Associates, Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce Agriculture Committee) will discuss this exciting technology space, and the over $160,000 (cash and in-kind services) that the AVCC has awarded locally to spark agriculture innovation. Dr. Danny Silver (Acadia Institute for Data Analytics) will look at the opportunities around ag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winning at Search Engines</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/winning-at-search-engines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/winning-at-search-engines/</guid>
      <description>What’s the point of having a website if you’re not getting any traffic?
With over half of the average website’s traffic coming from search engines, it’s important to rank in search results for keywords that are not only searched frequently but also have high intent.
You’ve taken the first step, you’ve built a website you’re happy with – now, it’s time to take out the guesswork and help your target market find what they are looking for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Course 2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 23:59:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2019/</guid>
      <description>We are thrilled to be opening up our 2019 Creative Computing Course for registration. This is our 3rd year offering this popular course. Unlike other years, we will be running 2 cohorts of learners for free. One cohort will be a mixed class of girls and boys. The second will be for girls. Registration is open until Jan. 2.
 Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to the computer sciences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Computer Science Course For Girls Announced</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/post/free-computer-science-course-for-girls-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/post/free-computer-science-course-for-girls-announced/</guid>
      <description>Wolfville, NS, (Dec. 19, 2018) — Coming into its third year running, Refresh Annapolis Valley has opened registration for its popular Creative Computing course for kids. Unlike previous years, the program is now free for participants. Beginning in January of 2019, Refresh’s Creative Computing course will be ready to teach kids the basics of software development using Scratch programming.
 “Computer Scientists are everywhere solving problems in very diverse corners of society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Digital to Physical: 3D Design and Printing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/from-digital-to-physical-3d-printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/from-digital-to-physical-3d-printing/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new world of of 3D printing, where you can produce 3D objects almost as easily as you can dream of them. In this hands on workshop we will:
 Learn about how 3D printing is shaking up different industries Types of 3D printing technologies How to design for printing How to print your designs  Bring a laptop and be prepared to roll up your sleeves. Space is limited to 20 people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Developer Bootcamp: Part 3 of 3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-3-of-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-3-of-3/</guid>
      <description>In this teen Hoist mini series, you will learn about how to build your own web application. Web applications are unlike traditional websites. Traditional websites are largely informational (like the Refresh Annapolis Valley website) where web applications solve particular problems (think Gmail for email).
 In part 1, you will learn the ins-and-outs of building app interfaces In part 2, you will learn how to add interactivity to your web app In part 3, you will learn how to manage app data  If you haven&amp;rsquo;t attended part 1 or 2, you can jump right into part 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Developer Bootcamp: Part 2 of 3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-2-of-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-2-of-3/</guid>
      <description>In this teen Hoist mini series, you will learn about how to build your own web application. Web applications are unlike traditional websites. Traditional websites are largely informational (like the Refresh Annapolis Valley website) where web applications solve particular problems (think Gmail for email).
 In part 1, you will learn the ins-and-outs of building app interfaces In part 2, you will learn how to add interactivity to your web app In part 3, you will learn how to manage app data  If you haven&amp;rsquo;t attended part 1, you can jump right into part 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refreshing Valley Youth Recognized For Their Entrepreneurship</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/post/refreshing-youth-recognized/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/post/refreshing-youth-recognized/</guid>
      <description>Wolfville, NS, (Nov. 29, 2018) — At a recognition event for outstanding community contributors to the Kings South riding, MLA Keith Irving presented a group of Refresh Annapolis Valley youth an award for their efforts and contributions. Recipients Emma He, Gerald Kaulback, Max Caplan, and Alexander Petkov were recognized for placing first place at Start It Up, a rigorous business ideation competition hosted by the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre.
“Entrepreneurship is crucial to the future economic success of our province and with amazing young entrepreneurs like these in our communities, I think our future is bright,” said Keith Irving MLA in a statement read in the Nova Scotia House of Assembly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The School in the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-school-in-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 18:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-school-in-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>What is the future of education in a networked world?
In this documentary screening and discussion, we will discuss Indian professor Sugata Mitra&amp;rsquo;s calls for a revolution in how and what we learn. With a global network of information a few clicks away, Mitra argues that the Victorian model on which our school systems are based is obsolete.
School In The Cloud follows a three-year experiment as Mitra installs unmanned internet kiosks in locations ranging from remote villages in West Bengal to a school in northeast England, to enable children to self-organize their learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Developer Bootcamp: Part 1 of 3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-1-of-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-1-of-3/</guid>
      <description>In this teen Hoist mini series, you will learn about how to build your own web application. Web applications are unlike traditional websites. Traditional websites are largely informational (like the Refresh Annapolis Valley website) where web applications solve particular problems (think Gmail for email).
 In part 1, you will learn the ins-and-outs of building app interfaces In part 2, you will learn how to add interactivity to your web app In part 3, you will learn how to manage app data  Pizza + workshop + building</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Succeeding at Failing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/succeeding-at-failing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/succeeding-at-failing/</guid>
      <description>Behind every entrepreneurial success lie the stories of numerous failures. As a mindset, entrepreneurship is characterized by risk-taking, experimentation, and continually challenging oneself to produce meaningful results. It is also about learning from failure, and, where possible, finding new ways to tackle problems that eventually lead to success.
Join Katelyn Bourgoin , a 3X founder/business owner turned growth strategist, for a discussion about how to think about entrepreneurship. Come mingle with a wide cross section of Annapolis Valley entrepreneurs for drinks, networking, and old fashioned discussion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Learn to Code Day: Build a Browser Extension!</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-browser-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 12:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-browser-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Join thousands of Canadians coast to coast to coast taking their first steps learning about Computer Science.
At this &amp;ldquo;Women Learning Code&amp;rdquo; event, we will learn how to build web browser extensions with JavaScript. Browser extensions extend your web browser with additional features, modify web pages, and integrate your browser with the other services you use. Extensions can help customize our browsing experience or increase productivity by reducing repetitive tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap 2018-2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/bootstrap-2018-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/bootstrap-2018-2019/</guid>
      <description>Refresh Annapolis Valley has been rocking the world of Computer Science and New Media circa 2012. We&amp;rsquo;ve built friendships, business relationships, helped form new statups, educated each other, helped rear the next generation&amp;hellip;. We&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished tons.
The 2018 - 2019 season is upon us! Organizers, visionaries, and supporters of all descriptions, come join us for an action oriented discussion on what our new season should look like. What sort of monthly meetup topics would you like to see?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support Our Digital Technology Community</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/support/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUILD: Computer Science Camp for Girls</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/camp-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 08:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/camp-2018/</guid>
      <description>BUILD is a week long dive into the world of Computer Science for girls 11 to 13. We will explore the basics of software development while building interactive artwork and stories, video games, and software that interacts with the physical world. Through our exploration we will also journey through use of hardware, refine our ideation skills and turn our ideas into software. Campers will also connect with Computer Scientists in our community who are changing the world one algorithm at a time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Camp 2018</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/camp-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 08:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/camp-2018/</guid>
      <description>Creative Computing Camp is a week long adventure into the world of Computer Science. Using the popular Scratch programming environment to master the basics of software development, we will build interactive artwork and stories, video games, and software that interacts with the physical world. Through our exploration of the creativity of software development, we will learn about where ideas come from, and how to turn ideas into action. Campers will also connect with Computer Scientists in our community who are changing the world one algorithm at a time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#ScratchFest</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2018/</guid>
      <description>Calling all Digital Builders #ScratchFest is a weekend (June 23th and June 24th) Build-a-thon for kids and teens interested in creating amazing original work with digital technologies, such as the Scratch programming environment, Processing, Virtual Reality, and more.
During #ScartchFest, participants will brainstorm an idea, develop their project, and showcase a final prototype. This weekend warrior event provides an excellent opportunity for coders to invent their own projects and demonstrate their knowledge within a collaborative, creative, and playful environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scratch For Educators</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/scratch-for-educators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 12:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/scratch-for-educators/</guid>
      <description>Scratch is being used in thousands of schools around the world to teach kids about the Computer Sciences. Since its launch over 10 years ago, kids from Elementary to High School have created over 6 million projects. In this crash course, adults (parents and educators) will learn about the Scratch programming environment and how it might be used to introduce learners to the Computer Sciences. No coding experience required.
Please register in advance so we know how much pizza to order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching a Computer To See</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/teaching-a-computer-to-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/teaching-a-computer-to-see/</guid>
      <description>Machine&amp;rsquo;s can learning amazing things when we train them. In this Hoist workshop, teens will will explore Artificial Intelligence by learning how to build a program that can guess what it sees in a picture. No coding experience? No worries. This fun introductory workshop is meant for the beginner. Using cutting edge machine learning tools, participants will learn how software is being used to create amazing programs that learn along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using DNA to Reverse-Engineer Your Family Tree</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/using-dna-to-reverse-enginee-your-family-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/using-dna-to-reverse-enginee-your-family-tree/</guid>
      <description>Recent advances in consumer genetics have enabled genealogists to solve mysteries in their family tree. Adoptees are finding their biological families by sharing the results of DNA tests with Websites that match millions of individuals.
Progeny Genealogy&amp;rsquo;s Charting Companion software displays the relationship distance of family members, as a number in an easy to understand chart. CC can also empirically find an adoptee&amp;rsquo;s family with an algorithm that simulates placement and compares theoretical to laboratory DNA results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Hardware - Programming The Physical World </title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hacking-hardware-programming-the-physical-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hacking-hardware-programming-the-physical-world/</guid>
      <description>Interactive jewelry, DIY laser tag, robots you design and build. In this Hoist workshop, teens will explore electronics by learning how to build and program robots . No coding or electronics experience? No worries. This fun introductory workshop is meant for the beginner. Using the Circuit Playground, participants will learn how coding and circuits are being used to create amazing creations. This workshop is for teens with no prior experience with programming required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Game Making and Circuitry</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/video-game-making-and-circuitry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 16:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/video-game-making-and-circuitry/</guid>
      <description>Building games is a great way to experience game play from the perspective of the creator. In this creative computing workshop, kids will learn how to program a computer to build their own games and build their own game controllers. Kids will learn basic coding and circuitry concepts in a fun beginner friendly environment. Using Scratch, a visual programming environment, kids will be exposed to an international community of coders making a wide range of games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking About Design - Creative Strategies</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/thinking-about-design-creative-strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/thinking-about-design-creative-strategies/</guid>
      <description>Design Thinking is being used by large innovative companies to create exceptional products and experiences (think Google Glass, AirBnB, your arrival experience with major airlines, and, of course, toilet paper). It can also be applied at much smaller scales - in education, to find solutions for sustainability challenges, and of course in tech companies of any size. Join Anne Stieger for an introduction to this powerful toolbox, process and mindset for user-centered design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animating Stories - Interactive Stories with Scratch</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/animating-stories-interactive-stories-with-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 16:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/animating-stories-interactive-stories-with-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Animating is a great way to bring a story to life. In this Creative Computing workshop, kids will learn how to program a computer to create animations for their own stories. Kids will learn basic coding concepts in a fun beginner friendly environment. Using Scratch, a visual programming environment, kids will be exposed to an international community of coders making a wide range of animation based projects. This intro workshop is for kids as young as 8 with no prior experience with Scratch required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Making with Your Computer!</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/art-making-with-your-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 16:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/art-making-with-your-computer/</guid>
      <description>Art is made with a variety of media - even computers! In this Creative Computing workshop, kids will learn how to program a computer to make interactive artwork. Kids will learn basic coding concepts in a fun beginner friendly environment. Using Scratch, a visual programming environment, kids will be exposed to an international community of coders making a wide range of interactive art projects. This intro workshop is for kids as young as 8 with no prior experience with Scratch required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring your Visual Art Alive with Computers - Intro to Processing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/intro-to-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/intro-to-processing/</guid>
      <description>Do you enjoy painting or drawing? In this Hoist workshop, teens will learn how to program a computer to build generative art. We will learn how how simple math equations can be used to create beautiful and engaging outcomes. No coding experience? No worries. This fun introductory workshop is meant for the beginner coder with a visual arts interest. Using OpenProcessing, participants will be exposed to an international community of coder-artists making a wide range of digital creations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Did All The Women Go?  Retaining Women in Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/where-did-all-the-women-go-retaining-women-in-computer-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/where-did-all-the-women-go-retaining-women-in-computer-science/</guid>
      <description>Over the last 30 years, the number of women entering Computer Science university programs has dropped from 50% to around 10%. Once in the program, women have a higher drop out rate than men. And women graduating with Computer Science degrees often leave the field and pursue alternate careers. Dr Randy Newman and Cindy Trudel have been actively researching this phenomenon over the last few years. In this Refresh Annapolis Valley talk, Randy and Cindy will discuss the problem, the programs that Acadia has in place, and the needs for the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Course 2018</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 18:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2018/</guid>
      <description>Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to the computer sciences. Broken up into 7 units, this course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid young people (aged 8 to 13) in learning the basics of software development. Scratch is used over the world by students to easily create interactive artwork, interactive stories, and video games while acting as a stepping stone to the more advanced world of computer science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refreshing Marketing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/refreshing-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/refreshing-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Marketing is forever changing. What works one week does not necessarily work the next. Join Duncan Ebata , Evan Hill , and Ashley Greene for a marketing insiders discussion on how to stay on the curve. They will explore why and how empathizing and understanding customers can be game changing; how to &amp;ldquo;growth hack&amp;rdquo; your marketing to double your results at half the cost; and time saving and low cost tools for marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revved Up!</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/revved-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 14:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/revved-up/</guid>
      <description>March 23 to 24th is launchbox&amp;rsquo;s Start It Up! - a weekend business ideation competition with 10K in prizes to be won. If you are interested in playing with new business ideas, this event is for you. While an University event, we have had youth teams (and winning youth teams!) at several Start It Up! competitions. This year is no different. If you are interested in learning more about this business ideation event, come to this information session and beef up on your skills to help you compete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anne Stieger</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anne-stieger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anne-stieger/</guid>
      <description>Anne is a process geek, facilitator and trainer with a knack for creative, collaborative processes and deep play. She is trained and experienced in a diverse range of facilitation practices including the Art of Hosting, Design Thinking, Dynamic Governance and Appreciative Inquiry. Anne was first introduced to Design Thinking when she was a teacher at Duisburg-Essen University in Germany through a project that connects High School &amp;amp; University students to solve local sustainability challenges through Design Thinking, and she has been hooked ever since by the power of the approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashley Greene</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ashley-greene/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ashley-greene/</guid>
      <description>Ashley Greene, J.D., is the Founder &amp;amp; CEO of Instratify, a growth-focused customer research firm for software and e-commerce businesses. Ashley is known for using her legal training to help companies get inside their customers’ heads, so they can achieve and maintain sustainable hypergrowth.
Ashley’s advised dozens of tech companies and has worked on projects with businesses from Fortune 500 companies to tech startups. Ashley writes and speaks on growth / customer insight, and has served as an advisor/trainer for leading startup organizations including Ryerson, Volta, and Communitech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duncan Ebata</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/duncan-ebata/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/duncan-ebata/</guid>
      <description>I’ve worked primarily with food social enterprises and tech startups, so adaption and collaboration are in my bag. Whether it be branding for food social enterprises, promoting local investment funds, implementing community economic development strategies, hosting food community events, building entrepreneurial culture: building food communities and promoting social enterprises is what I do.
I’ve been on the ground growing food and beverage start-ups reach their first $100k in sales, promoting local investment funds to reach their first $1 million, and growing multi-million dollar retail food businesses with 30%+ yearly growth rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evan Hill</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/evan-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/evan-hill/</guid>
      <description>Evan works with small to medium businesses in solving marketing hurdles, content creation, product launches, and digital growth. After working as an analyst in the hedge fund industry, he co-found an apparel design &amp;amp; distribution company that focused on student travel. Then spent 3 years in Toronto and the US with a content marketing company that generated digital athletic training content for young athletes. He’s worked with clients &amp;amp; brands such as Recode, Cut, @Dunk, Hyperice, APL Athletics, Sports1Marketing, Susar Lee Restaurants, and Nova Scotia Fisherman Bodycare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katelyn Bourgoin</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/katelyn-bourgoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/katelyn-bourgoin/</guid>
      <description>Katelyn Bourgoin is a 3X founder/business owner turned growth strategist. She helps frustrated marketers and business owners to figure out why customers aren’t buying and how they can fix it.
When companies know who their best customers are and what they really want, it becomes much easier to create awesome products and sell more of them. The result? Happier customers and more money in the bank.
Katelyn’s past clients include startups, small businesses, and Fortune 500s like Target and Holiday Inn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of Computer Science Education</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-computer-science-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-computer-science-education/</guid>
      <description>With an estimated 218,000 new skilled ICT workers needed in Canada by 2020 to meet the short term demands of our digital economy, focus on our educational system to address this challenge is paramount. The profound lack of diversity within the digital tech economy further complicates the response required. With changes in our provincial educational pipeline well under way, we are still early on in deploying a comprehensive response.
Join our panel discussion focused on defining challenges and solutions for Computer Science education today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Go</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/getting-started-with-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 18:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/getting-started-with-go/</guid>
      <description>Computer programming is the art, craft and science of writing programs which define how computers operate. This workshop, lead by Jodrey School of Computer Science alumn Tim Cooper , will teach you how to write computer programs using a programming language designed by Google named Go. Learn the basics as we design an AI to interact in a multiplayer game with the other participants in the workshop.
Go is a general purpose programming language with advanced features and a clean syntax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>f5://imagination</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 10:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</guid>
      <description>f5://imagination is a pop up exhibit focused on digital creativity. This one day temporary exhibit features work from digital artists, makers, scratchers, computer scientists, engineers and pretendgineer, hardware hackers, lego robotics warriors, indy game developers, new media innovators, VR and AR pioneers&amp;hellip; digital builders of all shapes, sizes, and credentials.
Schedule  10 AM to 12:30 PM Screening &amp; discussion of Hidden Figures: The story of a team of female African-American mathematicians who served a vital role in NASA during the early years of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digitized Reality</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/digitized-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/digitized-reality/</guid>
      <description>Come slap on a headset and enter the world of virtual reality. In this workshop, we will explore virtual reality by both examining the capabilities of commercial headsets, as well as learn how to build our own VR environments. If you can, bring a smart phone to test your uniquely constructed VR world. We can only accommodate a limited number of people for this event, so get your free ticket fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seed: Hacking Entrepreneurship in the Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/seed-hacking-entrepreneurship-in-the-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 18:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/seed-hacking-entrepreneurship-in-the-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>Seed is a documentary that follows an international group of programmer entrepreneurs at AngelHack: one of the most competitive global hackathons and digital business ideation competitions. Three minutes to pitch. One shot to fund their proposals.
Seed is also a gathering of our Annapolis Valley startup community. The event will feature the diversity of associations, businesses, and individuals who comprise our digital tech startup community. An assembly of our entrepreneurial family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Entrepreneurship: Turning Ideas into Action</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creative-entrepreneurship-turning-ideas-into-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creative-entrepreneurship-turning-ideas-into-action/</guid>
      <description>Problems and solutions. In between are the numerous ideas that eventually lead to innovative solutions and new business opportunities. Join the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre  for a talk all about ideas. Where do they come from? How do we nurture them? How can we turn them into problem solving new business?
Build your mad ideation skills at this workshop, then take them to Start It Up: our business ideation competition with $10K in prizes on the line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Founders Meetup: Lets Start a Business</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/founders-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 13:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/founders-meetup/</guid>
      <description>For this Hoist meetup, we will be doing something a little different. We are looking for a few budding teen entrepreneurs to start a business. This is the pitch:
Services supporting the business startup space in Rural Nova Scotia are diverse and not well represented as a whole. Our business aims to unify the Western Nova business startup ecosystem by building a coherent communication platform. By doing so, we will encourage entrepreneurship within our community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Smart Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/smart-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/smart-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>The Smart Communities movement involves villages, towns and cities getting ubiquitously connected to the Internet, and using the connection to involve citizens in networked activities. This movement argues that all the economic wealth created since WW2 has come from innovation - a networking activity that Smart Communities excel at. Smart Communities have better economic growth, more sustainable life-styles, and better health care.
i-Valley, a non-for-profit group working to put fast broadband networks into our communities, is bringing the Smart Community movement to our rural and remote regions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Learn to Code Day: Intro to AI and Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-ai-and-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-ai-and-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Join hundreds of Canadians coast to coast to coast taking their first steps learning about Computer Science. National Learn to Code Day was launched by Ladies Learning Code 5 years ago!
At this &amp;ldquo;Women Learning Code&amp;rdquo; event, we will learn about Artificial intelligence and machine learning. From Siri on your iPhone to Google Map suggestions, to recommendations for purchases during your Amazon check-out, AI is all around us.
AI and machine learning at its core is about data - and ways to make meaning of data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Printing: From Concept to the Palm of Your Hand</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/3d-printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/3d-printing/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new world of of 3D printing, where you can produce 3D objects almost as easily as you can dream of them. Emoji figurines, jewellery, nick nacks, to the more practical, in this hands on workshop you will learn how to design a 3D project. We will cap off the event by printing your original work.
Pizza + workshop + building
Bring your own laptop. A small number of laptops will be available to borrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Usability Lab: Testing With Little Or No Budget</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/diy-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/diy-usability/</guid>
      <description>Usability testing uncovers problem areas with your website. But not many do it, or do too little because of perceived complexity and cost. When you have limited time and budget, build your own usability lab and get results. A low-cost usability lab will be demonstrated using readily available hardware and software and results from testing our Acadia University library website will be shared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#ScratchFest</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2017/</guid>
      <description>Calling all Scratchers #ScratchFest is a weekend (June 24th and June 25th) Scratch-a-thon for kids interested in creating amazing original work with the Scratch programming environment.
During #ScartchFest, kids will brainstorm an idea, develop their project, and showcase a final prototype. This weekend warrior event provides an excellent opportunity for Scratch coders to invent their own projects and demonstrate their knowledge in Scratch within a collaborative, creative, and playful environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Against Flat Screens: Learn 3D Design</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/against-flat-screens-learn-3d-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/against-flat-screens-learn-3d-design/</guid>
      <description>In this Hoist teen design talk, Max Caplan will introduce us to 3D design using Blender. Blender is a professional 3D computer graphics software used for creating animated films, visual effects, art, 3D printed models, interactive 3D applications and video games. Max will walk us through installing, using, and designing your first Blender project: an awesome robot.
Pizza + workshop + building
Bring your own laptop. A small number of laptops will be available to borrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digitizing Your Mouth: 2 Decades of Digital Dentistry in Wolfville</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/digitizing-your-mouth-2-decades-of-digital-dentistry-in-wolfville/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/digitizing-your-mouth-2-decades-of-digital-dentistry-in-wolfville/</guid>
      <description>Henry Schein is a distributor and producer of health care products and services with a presence in 33 countries. The company is a Fortune World’s Most Admired Company and is ranked number one in its industry for social responsibility. Its Wolfville operation is at the forefront of digitizing dentistry with its wide range of home grown software solutions.
Come help the Henry Schein Woflville team christen its new office. Product Manager Sandy Macdonald will talk about the state of digital dentistry and how our Wolfville team is working on pushing its edges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrapping The Web</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/bootstrapping-the-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/bootstrapping-the-web/</guid>
      <description>For our first Hoist meetup, we&amp;rsquo;ll be learning how to use the Twitter Bootstrap code library to create beautiful front-end websites. Bootstrap is a combination of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript that allow you to write very little but get a whole lot. We&amp;rsquo;ll start with the basics of HTML and CSS and then dive into using Bootstrap to jump-start your web project.
Pizza + workshop + building
Bring your own laptop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life:  Youth Gone Wild</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-youth-gone-wild/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-youth-gone-wild/</guid>
      <description>Aristides Milios is possessed. In 2014 he co-founded Microcent Technologies. As CTO he focused on incubating hyper-local location technology for use in small-to-mid sized businesses. In 2015, he co-founded Hoist Halifax: a monthly series of workshops for teens interested in design, entrepreneurship and tech. That same year, he graduated from Propel ICT Accelerator Program. In 2016 he graduated from High School.
In this fireside chat, come learn what drives Aristides towards the tech startup trenches, and how he is building a youth entrepreneurship culture in Nova Scotia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Sucks</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/project-management-sucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/project-management-sucks/</guid>
      <description>Project management seems to be one of those areas of necessary evil. Disconnected project managers who don&amp;rsquo;t really understand your work coupled with never ending meetings, charts, spreadsheets, forms, paperwork, complicated management software&amp;hellip; Project management can feel like it is more of a barrier than a help to team productivity.
 In this talk, Mike Caplan, a reluctant Software Development Manager, will explore a lightweight tool for overseeing the project processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maker Meetup</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/maker-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/maker-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Calling all makers, inventors, artists, entrepreneurs, tinkerers, and the like. Join Refresh Annapolis Valley and Annapolis Valley STEAMspace for what we hope will be a regular meetup for the Valley maker community to gather, share ideas, and build community.
Projects galore to explore!
 Ian McKay will be demoing a magic cauldron, CNC stuff and a possible new product. Max Caplan will show off a homebrew handheld gaming console.  And you&amp;hellip;?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting: Using Machine Learning Techniques in Energy, Environment and Agriculture</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/forecasting-using-machine-learning-techniques-in-energy-environment-and-agriculture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/forecasting-using-machine-learning-techniques-in-energy-environment-and-agriculture/</guid>
      <description>Dr Daniel Silver will review a series of projects undertaken by the Acadia Institute for Data Analytics  . These amazing projects can estimate crop yield from smart phone images, do solar energy forecasting, manage building energy, determine stream flow rate and aquifer recharge prediction, sales forecasting, and classifying objects in UAV agriculture field images.
Many of these problems utilize high resolution observed and forecasted weather, high definition and multi-spectral digital images, and 5 minute through 60 minute data flow rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Course 2017</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 18:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2017/</guid>
      <description>Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to the computer sciences. Broken up into 7 units, this course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid young people (aged 8 to 13) in learning the basics of software development. Scratch is used over the world by students to easily create animations and games while acting as a stepping stone to the more advanced world of computer science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Feel The Frost Byte</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-feel-the-frost-byte/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-feel-the-frost-byte/</guid>
      <description>Business-hypothesis-driven experimentation. Iterative product releases. Validated learning. Pivot. Pivot. Pivot. Welcome to the tech startup world of John Frost .
From the early days of Frostbyte Interactive, Aerhyve Aerial Technologies, and now PrecisionHawk, John&amp;rsquo;s pursuit of innovative products and services in the digital tech space runs years long. Join us for a fireside chat with John where we will explore the inner working of a person committed to the startup life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding The World Through R</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/understanding-the-world-through-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/understanding-the-world-through-r/</guid>
      <description>The world is bubbling over with data. When analyzed, data can provide the inquiring mind with useful information that can suggest outcomes and support decision-making. Be it the data generated about business practices, human behaviours, the biological world; being able to understand what your data is telling you is incredibly empowering. &amp;ldquo;R&amp;rdquo; is a free, accessible, and powerful programming language that offers a suite of tools for data analysis.
Our tour guide, Trevor Avery — biostatistician, faculty member at Acadia University, and coordinator of R-bar  — will provide us a primer on R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Ideas for Your Next Social Media Campaign</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/10-ideas-for-your-next-social-media-campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/10-ideas-for-your-next-social-media-campaign/</guid>
      <description>Wes Booth will break down and share 10 tips he&amp;rsquo;s learned over his 10 year experience in the world of social media. Everything from emerging platforms and tools you can use to promote your business, to specific tips for boosting your marketing campaign success, and how to go above and beyond for your audience and customers. Wes won&amp;rsquo;t promise you life changing results because that&amp;rsquo;s not possible, but what he can do is prepare you to be in a position to have success and offer you practical things to take away and test out on your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Realtime Web: Intro To Node.js</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-realtime-web-intro-to-node-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-realtime-web-intro-to-node-js/</guid>
      <description>Node.js is a rapidly growing technology that has been making big waves in the world of web development. Node lets you easily build fast and scalable network applications perfect for the realtime web. In this workshop you’ll learn how to get started using Node, its background and history, and the problems it seeks to address. We’ll get our hands dirty building a realtime chat server to get a feel for the amazing power of Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Fist Fighting - Designing For Usability</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ux-fist-fighting-designing-for-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ux-fist-fighting-designing-for-usability/</guid>
      <description>10 years of picking fights and getting kicked out of a meetings - Mike Downs shares his personal quest to define &amp;ldquo;usability.&amp;rdquo; Mike will dive deep in to describing why usability is important for your websites and web applications. He will offer up pointers on how to think about your own projects with a user focused mind.
Mike has over eighteen years of Internet marketing strategy and product management experience helping create, shape, and launch technology products on the Web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CODE: Debugging the Gender Gap</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</guid>
      <description>CODE: Debugging The Gender Gap exposes the dearth of female and minority software engineers and explores the reasons for this gender gap and digital divide.
Tech jobs are growing three times faster than our colleges are producing computer science graduates. By 2019 there will be 182,000 jobs in information and communications technology that will go unfilled by homegrown Canadian talent because not enough people will have the right skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/creative-computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/creative-computing/</guid>
      <description>Creative Computing is a series of programs (courses, workshops, and events) geared towards kids 8 to 13 focused on exposing them to the amazing world of computer science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hoist Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/hoist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/hoist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hoist Annapolis Valley is a tech club for teens interested in coding, design and entrepreneurship. If you’re age 12 to 19 and have an interest in startups or coding, then come check it out! Everyone is welcome, and it’s free!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet up with Hoist members once per month at Acadia University&amp;rsquo;s Rural Innovation Centre &amp;ndash; like attending an tech + entrepreneurship class at university.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Labs</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/labs/</guid>
      <description>The Refresh Annapolis Valley Labs is a playground where adventurous builders come to create. Labs initiatives are community driven digital technology projects that tend to be entrepreneurial in nature. In the lab, Refreshers work on building and applying their skills all while pursuing the objectives of their projects.
Refresh Annapolis Valley Labs is hosted at the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre Rural Innovation Centre. We meet on Saturdays from 12:30 to 3:30 starting January 26.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Meetups</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/meetups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/meetups/</guid>
      <description>Our monthly Refresh meetup is where the Annapolis Valley community of designers, developers and innovators come hang out. Those interested in the creative, technical, and professional culture of digital technology endeavours in the Annapolis Valley meet and talk about all things design, technology, and entrepreneurship.
Refresh meets the second Tuesday evening of each month in the Wolfville area. These are casual affairs with short, member-interest talks followed by an opportunity to mingle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Computer Science Society</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-computer-science-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-computer-science-society/</guid>
      <description>The Acadia Computer Science Society welcomes not only Computer Science students but all students enrolled at Acadia University. We endeavour to be an advocate for students with interests in computer science and technology. We plan events like banquets, CaCHe, LAN parties, and seminars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</guid>
      <description>AEC has been developing and delivering workshops for business professionals, entrepreneurs, and not-for-profits for over 25 years. AEC continues to innovate and develop new and relevant programs for today’s business professional.
Rural Innovation Centre The Rural Innovation Centre (RIC) supports entrepreneurs and businesses in the Annapolis Valley and on the South Shore by providing training, advisory and consulting services to small businesses, government and not-for-profit organizations. The Rural Innovation Centre is an incubator for start up companies to access working space and support, networking events, mentors and connect to Acadia faculty and facilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Institute for Data Analytics</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-institute-for-data-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-institute-for-data-analytics/</guid>
      <description>Rural Canada feeds our nation literally, economically, and environmentally. It provides the food, fiber, minerals, water and other bio-resources and natural resources on which our country depends and the arteries of transportation by which they are delivered. Digital technologies and data analytics can help us shape how we work with these resources and their impact on our local communities and our planet.
Mission To advance knowledge in data analytics through collaborative and interdisciplinary research, education and outreach and to foster the ethical application and commercialization of data analytic solutions to challenges facing industry, government and society in rural Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Robotics Program</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</guid>
      <description>The Robot Programming Competition mission is to increase interest in building digital technology and computer science by engaging Nova Scotia students in annual robotics programming competitions and related activities that feature problem solving and teamwork.
The Acadia Robotics Program, through the Jodrey School of Computer Science, depends heavily on financial support from external organizations and the committed volunteers who annually contribute to the season from late August through to mid-June. We have a junior program, FIRST® LEGO® League, and a senior program, Robofest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia School of Business</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-school-of-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-school-of-business/</guid>
      <description>Acadia BBA students majoring in Entrepreneurship and Innovation are given the tools needed to succeed as entrepreneurs as well as to manage entrepreneurship for continuous innovation, sustainable competitive advantage and growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia University</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>Far above the dykes of Fundy
And its basin blue
Stands our noble alma mater
Glorious to view
Lift the chorus
Speed it onward
Sing it loud and free
Hail to thee our alma mater
Acadia, hail to thee
Far above the busy highway
And the sleepy town
Raised against the arch of heaven
Looks she proudly down</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Women in Technology Society</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-women-in-technology-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-women-in-technology-society/</guid>
      <description>We are a group of driven people dedicated toward the goal of supporting women in achieving success and promoting an inclusive feeling in STEM at Acadia.
Pictured above are 2 of the 6 women who where the first and primary programmers of the ENIAC, the world&amp;rsquo;s first digital computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACENET</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acenet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acenet/</guid>
      <description>Advanced computing - computing beyond the capabilities of a traditional laptop - can remove years from innovation timelines. Use it to create complex models, develop and test algorithms, run large-scale simulations, and test scalability. ACENET provides access to advanced computing infrastructure through your desktop, along with ongoing support, expertise and training. If your computing needs are outgrowing your laptop, you&amp;rsquo;re having difficulty using a commercial cloud platform, or you&amp;rsquo;re just not ready to purchase expensive hardware and software, call us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adam Conner</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/adam-conner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/adam-conner/</guid>
      <description>Adam is a teacher at Northeast Kings Education Centre in Canning, NS. He teaches math, technology, and computer programming. Adam been experimenting with the world of Making and 3D Printing for the past 18 months. Working with students at NKEC, he has been helping them create, print, and selling products designed and 3D printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex Sanford</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/alex-sanford/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/alex-sanford/</guid>
      <description>Alex is a software developer, musician, coffee enthusiast, and space geek. He was born and raised here in the Valley, and has a long time passion for science, technology, and lifelong learning.
Currently, Alex is a Code Wrangler for Automattic, the creators of WordPress.com. Automattic has close ties with the WordPress open source project, which powers 33% of the websites on the internet. Automattic’s mission is to make the web a better place by advocating openness, freedom, diversity, and inclusivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Button</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</guid>
      <description>After a 15 year career with various businesses and economic development organizations, Andrew felt it was about time to move from being a ‘cheerleader’ and ‘curator’ of entrepreneurship to doing something that actually produced more entrepreneurs in rural communities.
​In 2014 he founded Mashup Lab; a for-more-than-profit company that activates rural ideas. That same year he launched a chapter of the Awesome Foundation in his community. Andrew has since gone on to launch another social enterprise - CO3  , a fresh new coworking space for Freelancers, Entrepreneurs, and Independents located in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anita Kirkbride</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anita-kirkbride/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anita-kirkbride/</guid>
      <description>She&amp;rsquo;s on a mission to help small businesses understand how to use social media to serve their clients and grow sales.
Trying to keep up with ever-changing social media trends is exhausting, even for the most caffeinated among us. But Twirp Communications founder Anita Kirkbride is here to help you save all that coffee money.
Anita’s social media experience extends all the way back to the 90s, when she joined the first generation of bloggers, launching a crafting blog in a flurry of cardstock, buttons, and fabric swatches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annapolis Cider Company</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-cider-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-cider-company/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re all about local. Our apples are grown in nearby orchards, pressed into juice just down the road, and fermented into cider at our cidery in downtown Wolfville. Come for a tour, enjoy a tasting and tap into the valley.
The Annapolis Valley is who we are, it’s where we live and we couldn’t be more proud to call it home.
Annapolis Cider Company is a supporter of Refresh Annapolis Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-valley-chamber-of-commerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-valley-chamber-of-commerce/</guid>
      <description>Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce is a strong united voice for business and works to ensure that business thrives in the Annapolis Valley.
AVCC is a not-for-profit organization that provides member businesses with access to a variety of services such as group insurance, professional development and networking opportunities. AVCC celebrates and promotes the accomplishments of business people and their contribution to the valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annapolis Valley STEAMspace</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-valley-steamspace/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-valley-steamspace/</guid>
      <description>A place for Annapolis Valley Makers, inventors, artists, entrepreneurs, tinkerers and the like to meet, share ideas and work towards establishing the proposed Acadia University STEAMspace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aristides Milios</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/aristides-milios/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/aristides-milios/</guid>
      <description>Aristides is a highly motivated university student passionate about entrepreneurship, innovation, and web development.
CTO MicroCent Technologies and Co-Founder of Hoist Halifax, Aristides is full stack web developer who loves public speaking and is a natural leader. Smokin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Blockchain Company</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/atlantic-blockchain-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/atlantic-blockchain-company/</guid>
      <description>We are the Atlantic Blockchain Company Atlantic Blockchain Company Inc. is an education based company operating out of Halifax, Nova Scotia, in Atlantic Canada.
Who do we help? We consult with businesses of all sizes to determine the possible adoption of blockchain technology into their existing business infrastructure.
We deliver educational seminars to universities and private venues to give the common individual the tools and definitions they need to make sense of the “crypto phenomenon” that is sweeping the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AVCC Young Business Leaders</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/young-business-leaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/young-business-leaders/</guid>
      <description>Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce Young Business Leaders is a new committee that is exploring ways to connect to established business leaders for advice and mentorship. The AVCC Young Business Leaders Committee will recognize, encourage and engage future business leaders. The Young Business Leaders meet the last Tuesday of each month at noon at Gates Insurance, New Minas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barry Gander</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/barry-gander/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/barry-gander/</guid>
      <description>For 25 years Barry Gander has helped jump-start the development of advanced technology organizations in Canada and abroad. Working with companies, associations, the public sector and academia, Barry has established a network of leaders who thrive on leading-edge initiatives. As EVP of Canada’s largest high-tech association, the Canadian Advanced Technology Alliance (CATA) Barry has helped showcase the best of Canadian innovation to global markets. The i-CANADA program, which he co-founded, aims to create an “Intelligent Nation” by establishing a grass-roots movement of communities that network at ultra-fast speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Intellectual Property Office </title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office/</guid>
      <description>The Canadian Intellectual Property Office (CIPO), a Special Operating Agency (SOA) associated with Innovation, Science and Economic Development Canada, is responsible for the administration and processing of the greater part of intellectual property in Canada. CIPO&amp;rsquo;s areas of activity include:
  Patents cover new inventions (process, machine, manufacture, composition of matter), or any new and useful improvement of an existing invention;
  A trademark is a word (or words), a design, or a combination of these, used to identify the goods or services of one person or organization and to distinguish these goods or services from those of others in the marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canopy Creative</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canopy-creative/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canopy-creative/</guid>
      <description>We are a team of marketing consultants that work with small businesses to plan and strategize for marketing growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cassie Josephine</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cassie-josephine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cassie-josephine/</guid>
      <description>With “a voice that sits between Roy Orbison and Dolly Parton,” Cassie Josephine provides a vintage sound to her deeply personal narratives (Jeff Liberty - CBC). Her latest collection of songs, Only Half Blue, is one she thinks of fondly as a fairytale of middle-aged proportions. With her backing band, The Cry If I Want To’s, Cassie’s dreamy anthems are brought to life with soaring harmonies, violin, piano, and electric guitar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catherine Vardy</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/catherine-vardy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/catherine-vardy/</guid>
      <description>Catherine Vardy joined the Canadian Intellectual Property Office  (CIPO) in 2015. As a Business Development Officer for the Atlantic Region, Catherine enjoys working with people to identify and highlight the value of IP.
As the Network Liaison and Program Manager at Springboard Atlantic, Catherine worked closely with innovative SMEs, universities and colleges. Catherine also worked in Atlantic Canada as a Research and Innovation Development Officer with the Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council (NSERC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Greene</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/charlie-greene/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/charlie-greene/</guid>
      <description>Charlie is a senior software developer at The REDspace. He is alumni from Colibri Software  where he worked for two years, ever since graduating from Acadia University with a Honors degree in Computer Science with Co-Op option.
Charlie&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by the work of Ruby the painting elephant. True story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Jordan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/chris-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/chris-jordan/</guid>
      <description>Chris is a software developer with 16+ years experience with Henry Schein. Not to be pigeonholed, he&amp;rsquo;s got his hand in all sorts of things: Top tier support for an installation base spanning 2000+ customers, Brand development, Application planning and development, Database design, Documentation, Testing, Training, Training material development: web, print and video, Customer support, Installer creation, Phone system programming.
Chris&#39; profile pic is a mashup of a picture of his swiped from Facebook and R2D2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cindy Trudel</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel/</guid>
      <description>Cindy Trudel is an Instructor in Acadia University&amp;rsquo;s Departments of Computer Science, Business and Mathematics. Her primary research interest is in developing retention programs for students who have self-selected Computer Science as an area of study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CO3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3/</guid>
      <description>CO3 is a fresh bew co-working space for freelancers, entrepreneurs and independents.
CO3 Is a concept created by ​Andrew Button , a social entrepreneur based in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.
&amp;ldquo;The mission is to create a space that further cultivates rural Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s freelance economy.&amp;rdquo;
Through the success of his own company Mashup Lab and other social ventures ​he&amp;rsquo;s discovered a lot of hidden talent in the Maritimes which he feels needs more room to grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colibri Software</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/colibri-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/colibri-software/</guid>
      <description>Colibri Software builds awesome software. We work with our clients to understand their needs and then produce a simple and effective solution to their problems. Our focus is on making a product easy to use, from websites to mobile apps, we like it when we hear “this is easy”.
We have a special affinity for mapping projects and have send rugged phone apps as far as Nunavut to help collect data for the hunting community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Common Good Solutions</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/common-good-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/common-good-solutions/</guid>
      <description>Common Good Solutions (CGS) is a company focused on growing the social enterprise movement in Nova Scotia, Canada, and beyond. CGS operates a social enterprise incubator aimed at launching and supporting over 100 social businesses by 2019, and offers a full range of social enterprise consulting, mentoring and training services. Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s first Community Interest Company, CGS devotes 60% of all profits toward its social mission of growing the social enterprise sector in Nova Scotia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Duke</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/david-duke/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/david-duke/</guid>
      <description>David Duke is an Associate Professor in the Department of History and Classics and as Coordinator of the university&amp;rsquo;s recently-established Environmental and Sustainability Studies program. His academic areas of expertise are the history of Russia and the USSR, the history of science, and environmental history, and he teaches in all these areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nova Scotia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/digital-nova-scotia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/digital-nova-scotia/</guid>
      <description>Engaging both members and stakeholders in the region, Digital Nova Scotia provides advocacy, multi-sectoral industry intelligence, facilitates connections between industry and talent, and delivers high-level programming to ensure Nova Scotia’s $1.5 billion digital industry (which boasts an additional $1 billion in spin-offs) continues to flourish.
IT starts here. IT stays here. IT grows here. As the industry association for the fastest growing sector in the province with the highest number of ICT graduates per capita in Canada, Digital Nova Scotia encourages our tech talent and growing ecosystem of digital businesses to start here, stay here, and grow here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Daniel Silver</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-daniel-silver/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-daniel-silver/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Daniel L. Silver is the Director of the Acadia Institute for Data Analytics  . He is also a Professor in and currently the Acting-Director of the Jodrey School of Computer Science  at Acadia University. His areas of research and application are machine learning, data mining, and data analytics. His expertise is in Lifelong Machine Learning and Transfer Learning. He has published over 65 scientific papers and has co-chaired or been part of program committees for a number of national and international conferences, seminars and workshops on data mining and machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Darcy Benoit</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-darcy-benoit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-darcy-benoit/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Darcy Benoit is a Professor in and the Director of the Jodrey School of Computer Science at Acadia University. His areas of research include mobile application development, database management systems, and computer science education. An avid supporter educational outreach, Darcy oversees the Acadia Robotics program, a province-wide outreach program that sees approximately 400 students from grades 9-18 compete in two international robot programming competitions. His outreach work resulted in him collaborating with the Nova Scotia Department of Education and Early Childhood Development on the implementation of computer programming in the public school system from grades 7-12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Randy Newman</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-randy-newman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-randy-newman/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Newman is a Cognitive Neuroscientist whose primary research interest is in understanding the brain mechanisms responsible for reading and speech processes using event-related potentials and eye tracking techniques. Current research is examining the impact of a word&amp;rsquo;s spelling on how quickly we recognize spoken words.
A secondary area of interest is in understanding factors responsible for the gender gap that persists in some areas of science, notably computer science and engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Garrett</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/elizabeth-garrett/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/elizabeth-garrett/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Just like becoming an expert in wine - you learn by drinking it, the best you can afford - you learn great food by finding the best there is, whether simply or luxurious. Then you savor it, analyze it, discuss it with your companions, and you compare it with other experiences&amp;rdquo; - Julia Child, Mastering the Art of French Cooking</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emily Konrath</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/emily-konrath/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/emily-konrath/</guid>
      <description>Emily is a small business enthusiast with a passion for homegrown talent. Emily was born and raised in Wolfville, studied her Bachelor of Commerce degree at Saint Mary’s University and obtained her Masters in International Business from Jönköping, Sweden. Emily has lived and studied in cities across Canada and abroad in Germany and Sweden.
Emily is an Economic Development Officer with the Valley Regional Enterprise Network, a municipal corporation that works as a catalyst for regional economic development in the Annapolis Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enactus Acadia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/enactus-acadia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/enactus-acadia/</guid>
      <description>Enactus Acadia is a small chapter of a global organization that unites students with academic and business leaders. We implement various projects in the community that help improve the quality of life and standard of living for those in need. Enactus Acadia currently has multiple projects underway, which fit into categories such as eco-living, youth empowerment, financial literacy, and entrepreneurship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frances Schagen</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/frances-schagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/frances-schagen/</guid>
      <description>Frances is a small business innovator. She geeks out over business strategy, business models and building entrepreneurial ecosystems. She believe that&amp;rsquo;s the kind of thinking we need to save the world. Frances helps create places where entrepreneurship can thrive within our business and within our community.
Business innovation is essential for us to solve our biggest issues and to succeed in the world today. Business theory was developed for large business and small business is not a little big business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fusion Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/fusion-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/fusion-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>Fusion AV is a non-profit, community engagement organization that’s mission to engage with young professionals in the Annapolis Valley. We aim to give them opportunities to connect and build their personal and professional network to ensure the long term success of this great place we all call home. Thus ENGAGE CONNECT SUCCEED</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gary Morton</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/gary-morton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/gary-morton/</guid>
      <description>Gary is a business development consultant/coach that for over 30 years has worked with farms, business and organization clients to find and develop new value added ideas, profit and success from what they do. This includes product development, commercialization, business planning, market development (domestic and export), product launch, training programs and managing business growth around new products and services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genevieve Allen Hearn</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/genevieve-allen-hearn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/genevieve-allen-hearn/</guid>
      <description>Genevieve is an arts administrator, specializing in organizing cultural events and festivals. Currently, Genevieve is working for the Atlantic Public Arts Funders, organizing an Indigenous Arts Symposium for Atlantic Canada. She is part-owner and Operations Manager of The Grapevine, the Annapolis Valley’s bi-weekly arts and culture publication. Her volunteer work includes serving on the board of Uncommon Common Art, the Kentville Art Gallery Society, and the Youth Engagement Working Group for the Municipality of the County of Kings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geoff Crouse</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</guid>
      <description>Geoff has more than 17 years of combined Software Engineering and Information Technology Consulting experience.
  Technical Sales Engineer, specializing in medium to large scale Drupal CMS projects including new development, site audits and analysis, and expert support services.
  Account Management, coordinating customer projects with engineering and support teams from initial conception to final delivery, and continued support.
  Geoff&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HarvestHand</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/harvesthand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/harvesthand/</guid>
      <description>HarvestHand is a community platform dedicated to strengthening regional food systems. We&amp;rsquo;re passionate about supporting farms with CSA&amp;rsquo;s to become more profitable using HarvestHand CSA Software, helping communities eat better through the HarvestHand Community, creating good jobs in rural communities, and building new media solutions that make sharing the harvest easier.
Our vision is to create new media solutions that strengthen regional food systems&#39; ability to succeed in value oriented approaches to production, distribution, consumption and community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hope Latta</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/hope-latta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/hope-latta/</guid>
      <description>Hope is in her senior year of Computer Science at Acadia University. She loves teaching and encouraging people to learn computer science. While in her undergrad, she worked two co-op terms in the security industry. This past summer she studied web design and directing at Harvard University. Locally, she won the Best Overall Physical Sciences Project grades 7-12 two years in a row at the Annapolis Valley Regional Science Fair. She also represented Nova Scotia at the Canada Wide National Science Fair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HUB Kentville</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville/</guid>
      <description>Get Inspired, Get Connected, Get involved. HUB spaces provide an inspirational home to members and are a focal point for change within the local communities.
What is the Hub? The HUB is about the power of innovation through collaboration.
We believe there is no shortage of good ideas to solve the issues of our time. But there is an acute lack of collaboration and support structures to help make them happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i-Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/i-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/i-valley/</guid>
      <description>i-Valley is a not-for-profit collaboration of Mayors, Wardens, business leaders, civic planners and academia, dedicated to facilitating the transformation of the Annapolis Valley to a Smart Region. The goal of “Smart Annapolis Valley” is to drive efficiencies is such vital areas as energy, healthcare, business, and social engagement. Smart Communities are those which use digital tools and services to achieve the higher employment, better income, more sustainable environment and better education that are universal traits of such communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian McKay</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ian-mckay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ian-mckay/</guid>
      <description>“Creative Technician”&amp;hellip;what the heck is that?
I see my role, primarily, as that of a possibilitist. I listen closely to your ideas, what you hope to create, the problem you are working and then share with you the possibilities technology may offer. My years of immersion in Maker culture, joyfully exploring new and unusual uses for the wonders of emerging and age-old tech, provide me with a deep pool of possible solutions to your creative problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>innovacorp</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/innovacorp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/innovacorp/</guid>
      <description>Innovacorp is Nova Scotia’s early stage venture capital organization. We work to find, fund and foster innovative Nova Scotia start-ups that strive to change the world. Early stage investment is at the core of our business model. We also give entrepreneurs access to world-class incubation facilities, expert advice and other support to help them accelerate their companies.
Target industries include clean technology, information technology, life sciences and ocean technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy Lutes</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/jeremy-lutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/jeremy-lutes/</guid>
      <description>Jeremy Lutes is a Partner at Equilibrium Engineering. Jeremy has been successfully managing and operating businesses since 1998. Previous to Equilibrium, Jeremy was the Business Analyst for Internetworking Atlantic (IAI), a private Halifax based telecommunications company.
From a volunteer perspective, Jeremy was previously on the Board of Directors of the Halifax Pop Explosion for twelve years, and the Music Nova Scotia Board of Directors for three years. These positions illustrate a long-standing passion for the arts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jodrey School of Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>The Jodrey School of Computer Science prepares students for today&amp;rsquo;s ever changing world of technology in a unique, fully mobile computing environment. Students develop a thorough understanding of computer systems software, modern software design methods and computer systems software.
Students in all degree programs complete a self-directed project during the course of their studies. This provides students with the opportunity to work closely with professors and to apply knowledge acquired through experiment and real-life application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Frost</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/john-frost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/john-frost/</guid>
      <description>John Frost is a Senior Manager, Satellite Products, at PrecisionHawk. John worked extensively in geophysical research and exploration before returning to university to complete studies in International Relations/Intercultural Studies. With broad national and international project exposure, he is a cross-cultural specialist in technology adaptation. Through the Aerhyve brand, the company focused on the analysis of UAV data with Machine Learning, providing actionable intelligence for agricultural and industrial applications. An entrepreneur and technophile, John is always pursuing opportunities which make a local-global impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Josh Smith</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/josh-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/josh-smith/</guid>
      <description>Front End Engineer at Chalk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justin Bezanson</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/justin-bezanson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/justin-bezanson/</guid>
      <description>Since 2000 I have continued to expand my knowledge and skills and worked hard to be the best developer I can be.
I enjoy meeting challenges and working hard to find creative and user friendly solutions.
My goal is to continually improve my development process, delivering higher quality and efficiency.
Specialties: PHP, ASP.NET MVC, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, CodeIgniter, Zend Framework, AJAX, Windows, Linux, MySQL, SQL Server, WordPress, ASP.NET
Justin, pictured here, is The Thing from the Fantastic Four.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keegan Francis</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/keegan-francis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/keegan-francis/</guid>
      <description>My name is Keegan Francis, i have been working with, interested in, and invested in cryptocurrencies and blockchain since 2014.
 Invested in bitcoin and dogecoin in 2014 Graduated with a degree in computer science in 2015 Built my first mining rig in 2017 Have given several lectures and presentations to Nova Scotia universities in 2017 and 2018 Attended an international blockchain conference in Shanghai, China, 2018 Co-founded Atlantic Blockchain Company Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keith Diehl</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/keith-diehl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/keith-diehl/</guid>
      <description>Keith got his first glimpse of HTML with NCSA&amp;rsquo;s Mosaic browser in 1994. A few “View Sources” later and he was hooked.
Soon after, he got his first web job as Webmaster for the Arizona Daily Wildcat. Over the years, Keith has worked for several newspapers and Fortune 500 companies including Coca Cola and Aflac insurance. He has been the Webmaster for North America&amp;rsquo;s premiere training provider CED Solutions for over 15 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kerr &amp; Nadeau</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/kerr-nadeau/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/kerr-nadeau/</guid>
      <description>At Kerr &amp;amp; Nadeau our job is to de-mystify and to simplify the rules for you, to offer you sound professional advice and superior legal services that will enable you, whether you are an inventor, an entrepreneur or a corporate executive, to execute your business plan, to protect your legal rights and to realize your strategic objectives while mitigating risk and ensuring compliance. Risk is the bane and Achilles heel of most business enterprises, and the single greatest obstacle to achieving your mission critical goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Labnet Dental Lab Systems</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems/</guid>
      <description>Labnet Dental Lab Systems offers the Dental Lab industry&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive and powerful management systems with solutions suited for labs of all sizes and budgets. Whether your lab is a thriving multi-site corporation or a one-technician miracle lab, we have a perfect fit for you.
As a Henry Schein company, you can depend on Labnet Dental Lab Systems for stability and providing your dentists with the latest technological advancements. When you are operating within tight deadlines, the last thing you should worry about is your software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launchbox</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/launchbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/launchbox/</guid>
      <description>Launchbox is the centre for student entrepreneurs, located on the 4th floor of Patterson Hall at Acadia University. We support students in their entrepreneurial pursuits by providing free programming, networking, access to mentors, and other entrepreneurs, working space and competitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laura Simpson</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson/</guid>
      <description>Lover of music and truth. Listen to the poets. Founder of The Syrup Factory, Make.Do.Camp. and Side Door.
Laura Simpson is a music industry professional, living with her family in Halifax, Nova Scotia. She founded The Syrup Factory, which began hosting house concerts 2011 and offering strategy and services to artists in 2015.
She has been an organizer in the arts scene since she was 14, going to all-ages shows and then eventually taking live music photography and freelance writing about shows and artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leanne Strathdee</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/leanne-strathdee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/leanne-strathdee/</guid>
      <description>Leanne Strathdee is the Manager of Innovation and Incubation for Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre  . In this role, she manages the Rural Innovation Centre – an incubator for start-up companies at Acadia University  , that are connected to the services and amenities that Acadia offers in research, data analytics, tidal energy or business - skills development. Additionally, she manages all the student entrepreneurship programming through the provincial sandbox, launchbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lori Shepherd</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/lori-shepherd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/lori-shepherd/</guid>
      <description>Lori builds games. Lori also builds teams from the ground up, ensuring the effectiveness of the team through collaboration.
Lori creates military based games, combining her security training, and creativity into realistic and engrossing experiences. Encompassing criminal elements, espionage, law enforcement, cyberwarfare, intelligence, and tactics.
Lori’s audience, in the security forum, have included police agencies, government, military and defense, legal professionals, technology sectors, consultants, and private investigators.
International law enforcement and security organizations have worked with her in understanding and preparing for virtual world culture and threats to games associated with crime in online gaming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maggie Neilson</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/maggie-neilson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/maggie-neilson/</guid>
      <description>Maggie Neilson is an Academic Librarian at Acadia University’s Vaughan Memorial Library. Her role primarily revolves around liaison responsibilities with the Jodrey School of Computer Science, the Ivan Curry School of Engineering, the Earth and Environmental Science Department, the Environmental and Sustainability Studies Programme, and the School of Kinesiology. In addition to the collection development services, instructional sessions and research assistance she provides to these disciplines, Maggie also has coordinating responsibilities in government documents, the library’s discovery layer, and geospatial and numeric data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Margaret Hopkins</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/margaret-hopkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/margaret-hopkins/</guid>
      <description>Margaret Hopkins is a third year math and music major at Acadia University with an interest in promoting mathematics and technology education for youth in the Annapolis Valley. She is a founding member and now coach of the Horton High Robats, an all-girls&#39; robotics team; coaches Wolfville School&amp;rsquo;s First Lego League team, Robo Lobo Wired; and volunteers with WISE Acadia and other organizations in the region to promote STEM education for all students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Davis</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-davis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-davis/</guid>
      <description>Founder / CEO at colovo and co-founder of The HUB Yarmouth  .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Richards</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-richards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-richards/</guid>
      <description>Mark has been working in the field of education for over 20 years. For the past four years Mark has been the AVRSB Consultant of Technology integration and Student Data. Prior to that, Mark spent 10 years teaching high school science/technology, was a high school vice principal and was project manager for the provincial PowerSchool implementation. Mark wrote the original Computer Programming 12 curriculum document for the province of Nova Scotia in the early 2000’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mashup Lab</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/mashup-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/mashup-lab/</guid>
      <description>Mashup Lab is a for-more-than-profit company that works with people to figure out if there is a great business to be built around their great ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Hall</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matt-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matt-hall/</guid>
      <description>I make stuff happen at Agile*, an independent geoscience idea factory in Canada.
We build awesome knowledge engines for organizations (mostly wikis), and we hone our skills in subsurface science&amp;hellip; We have most recently been working on geothermal reservoir description. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked the Montney tight gas of Alberta and BC, frontier exploration in the Canadian Beaufort Sea, the Athabasca oil sands, the Norwegian North Sea. I also worked in software for several years, as an advocate of integrated volume visualization and interpretation and viz room pilot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Doucette</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matthew-doucette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matthew-doucette/</guid>
      <description>I am a video game developer (Xbox 360 &amp;amp; PC). Check out my video game company, Xona Games, and my first professional video game, Duality ZF, for more information. My only parter is my twin brother, Jason Doucette.
Here is the Duality ZF April 2009 trailer:
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max Caplan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/max-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/max-caplan/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, he was born. What happened after this is the interesting part. Relatively speaking. After his long and tedious early childhood, Max found himself being introduced to the fascinating world of technology. One of his earliest experiences was with the beginner programming environment known as Scratch. After a couple of years of making awesome scratch projects, Max moved on to explore more that tech had to offer. Through his School he found himself on a Lego Robotics team for a couple years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Caplan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-caplan/</guid>
      <description>Mike has been active as a web application developer and web designer for 16 years, working in the non-profit, university, retail, agricultural, and dental industries. He is a founding partner of HarvestHand  , a platform that services Community Shared Agriculture farms. Mike founded Refresh Annapolis Valley  , a new media professional association to help grow the Valley&amp;rsquo;s technology industry.
Mike is the Software Development Manager for the Labnet Dental Lab Systems  division of Henry Schein - a Fortune 300 company with a small footprint here in Wolfville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Macmillan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-macmillan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-macmillan/</guid>
      <description>Michael is an SEO and marketing specialist, focusing on consultancy for software &amp;amp; service companies and specializing in troubleshooting. He built his first website in 1996 and was a working professional in the digital world by 1999. Having held various roles in the digital world, he transitioned to an SEO role in 2009. Since then he has held SEO roles in-house, as leadership for an agencies SEO team, and as an independent consultant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Downs</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mike-downs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mike-downs/</guid>
      <description>Mike has over eighteen years of Internet marketing strategy and product management experience helping create, shape, and launch technology products on the Web. Mike is very passionate about how human beings use computers. Focusing on usability and user experience for the last 10 years, Mike has helped retail giants like Macy&amp;rsquo;s and The Gap as well as government organizations like Tourism British Columbia and Service Nova Scotia deliver experiences that engage their audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morton Horticultural Associates</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/morton-horticultural-associates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/morton-horticultural-associates/</guid>
      <description>Morton Horticultural Associates was established in 1982 to provide specialized consulting, advisory and coaching services to clients in the horticulture, agriculture and the agri-food industry. The company focus is on helping agriculture businesses and organizations chart a clear path to the future and to develop the business management skills that will get them there. The areas of expertise include industry analysis, new value-added product development and commercialization, direct marketing, agritourism, business development, strategic and business planning and market innovation strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mrugakshee Palwe</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mrugakshee-palwe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mrugakshee-palwe/</guid>
      <description>My name is Mrugakshee Palwe. I started investing my time in understanding the blockchain technology in mid-2018.
 Graduated with a degree in computer science in spring 2018 Received a scholarship for Consensys academy’s 2018 Developer Bootcamp in October 2018. Certificate of Proficiency from Ethereum Blockchain Developer Bootcamp - Feb 2019 Forked and customized the Bitshares, Graphene, and Peerplays blockchains Co-founded Atlantic Blockchain Company Inc. in November 2018  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nexus Robotics</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nexus-robotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nexus-robotics/</guid>
      <description>Nexus Robotics is a Nova Scotian technology startup, developing autonomous robotic solutions for Agriculture using machine learning. Nexus provides farmers with a reliable and cost-effective way to produce crops. The Nexus Robotics team created an autonomous machine called R2-Weed2, which uses a camera system to differentiate between weeds and crops. The machine will be capable of cutting and spraying weeds, as well as able to fertilize crops and collect data about the crop and growing conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nick Baskwill</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/nick-baskwill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/nick-baskwill/</guid>
      <description>Nick is a grade 5 teacher at Kingston Elementary school in Kingston, NS. He has been teaching for 10 years. Nick completed his B. Sc from Lyndon State College, his B. Ed from Acadia University, and his M. Ed from Mount Saint Vincent University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noah Tomkins</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/noah-tomkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/noah-tomkins/</guid>
      <description>Originally from Dartmouth, Nova Scotia, Noah Tompkins is a fourth-year Entrepreneurship &amp;amp; Innovation major at Acadia University. His passion for sustainability and social enterprise has lead Noah to working as the Marketing Coordinator for Just Us! Coffee Roasters, becoming a project manager and presenter for Enacts Acadia, and the President of Fair Trade Acadia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nova Scotia Community College</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nscc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nscc/</guid>
      <description>The School of IT &amp;amp; Creative Industries offers many dynamic programs that prepare you for a range of IT and creative careers.
Our instructors are professionals who remain current in their fields of expertise. They’re ready to teach you the latest industry techniques so you’ll graduate with the creativity and know-how to excel in the workforce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nova Scotia Works</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nova-scotia-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nova-scotia-works/</guid>
      <description>Nova Scotia Works employment services centres help Nova Scotians understand, prepare for, and fill the needs of the province’s job market. Nova Scotia Works also helps businesses recruit, manage and develop the talent they need to be more productive here at home and around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office of Industry &amp; Community Engagement - Acadia University</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/office-of-industry-community-engagement-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/office-of-industry-community-engagement-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>Acadia’s Office of Industry &amp;amp; Community Engagement (ICE), identifies and connects Acadia’s researchers with industry, government and community groups interested in research, commercialization, outreach and entrepreneurship activities. As a member of Springboard Atlantic, ICE works with other universities in Atlantic Canada, as well as incubators and accelerators to ensure Acadia is making a strong contribution to the development and prosperity of our local and regional communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Richards</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/paul-richards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/paul-richards/</guid>
      <description>Paul Richards is innovacorp&amp;#39;s  regional manager for Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s Annapolis Valley and South Shore. In this role, Paul focuses on enabling knowledge-based companies to accelerate their growth and helping foster a dynamic high-growth entrepreneurial culture in the region.
Paul spent over 10 years working with the Acadia Centre for Social and Business Entrepreneurship (ACSBE) assisting businesses in rural Nova Scotia. In this role, Paul also worked to build the entrepreneurial capacity and infrastructure of several developing economies in Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philip Kerr</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/philip-kerr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/philip-kerr/</guid>
      <description>Philip is a Canadian lawyer, and Canadian patent and trademark agent with 29 years of experience. He is a partner in the Canadian patent firm of Kerr &amp;amp; Nadeau  (offices in Halifax and Ottawa).
Philip is also the president of PCTxs Inc., a firm that provides an online marketplace for selling/licensing patent application rights, particularly unexpired PCT national phase rights and unexpired Paris Convention patent application rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pierre Clouthier</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/pierre-clouthier/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/pierre-clouthier/</guid>
      <description>Co-founder, President, Progeny Genealogy Inc., specialising in computer graphics software for genealogy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PrecisionHawk</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/precisionhawk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/precisionhawk/</guid>
      <description>PrecisionHawk is the leading provider of aerial data and safety platforms for drones. The Lancaster is PrecisionHawk’s fixed-wing, autonomous drone built to collect the highest quality terrestrial data using a host of integrated sensors including visual, thermal, LiDAR, multispectral and hyperspectral. PrecisionHawk houses three divisions that support its mission: DataMapper aerial mapping and analysis software, TerraServer satellite imagery and LATAS (Low Altitude Traffic and Airspace Safety).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progeny Genealogy</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/progeny-genealogy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/progeny-genealogy/</guid>
      <description>Progeny Genealogy is the leading developer of family tree software and other useful, easy-to-use genealogy research resources, including Charting Companion™, Genelines™ and Map My Family Tree™. More than pretty charts, our genealogy software programs are also powerful research tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R-bar</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/r-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/r-bar/</guid>
      <description>R-bar is Acadia University&amp;rsquo;s scientific programming study group. They cover everything R: a programming language and software environment for statistical computing and graphics.
WHAT WE DO   Skill Sharing: Share your favorite coding skills and tools with your friends and colleagues in friendly, no-pressure work-alongs.
  Co-Working: Get together to work on your coding projects, help each other out and share your work.
  Community Building: Meet new people in your field, organization or community - and find out what we can do when we work together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raina Noel</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/raina-noel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/raina-noel/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>Refresh is a community of designers, developers and innovators working to refresh the creative, technical, and professional culture of digital technology endeavours in the Annapolis Valley while promoting design, technology, and entrepreneurship.
Refresh Annapolis Valley was founded to create a cultural and educational space for our regional digital technology professionals, both current and future, to grow their skills and build regional synergies.
We believe deeply in the digital economy as a component of a strong diversified Nova Scotian economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sandy McFadden</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sandy-mcfadden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sandy-mcfadden/</guid>
      <description>Sandy started playing with and building things for the web in 1999. At some point along the way he started trying out different content management systems to help make things easier. After trying to write his own very basic one he settled on WordPress and has been using it to build web sites for years.
Now he works for Automattic helping people everyday to use their sites on WordPress.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sara Baxter</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sara-baxter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sara-baxter/</guid>
      <description>A fourth year Accounting major, Sara Baxter from Moncton, New Brunswick, exercises her entrepreneurial skillset through Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre as the Community Entrepreneurship Developer. Her desire to create change and have a positive impact on society has led her to become a Project Co-Manager for Enacts Acadia&amp;rsquo;s Project Regenerate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Ryan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sarah-ryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sarah-ryan/</guid>
      <description>A graduate of Mount Saint Vincent University, Sarah has worked in the science enrichment and education fields for over nine years. For the past three years, Sarah has been Program Director at Brilliant Labs Nova Scotia, a not-for-profit organization that supports students and educators with innovative ways to make learning fun and relevant by using tools, materials and technologies to solve everyday challenges. In this role, she is responsible for delivering programming to enhance digital literacy skills and support project-based learning initiatives for teachers, students, and community groups across Nova Scotia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ScotiaCom</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/scotiacom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/scotiacom/</guid>
      <description>ScotiaCom (aka Scotia Computer Resources Inc.) is a small, independent business located in the Annapolis Valley, Nova Scotia. What started as an educational software development company has become a leader in the development and deployment of services that allow organizations, groups, individuals and small businesses to take full advantage of the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott Olszowiec</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/scott-olszowiec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/scott-olszowiec/</guid>
      <description>Scott Olszowiec is creative partner that has been building solutions to communicate ideas and inspiration for over 17 years.
From digital content creation to educational technology, he is somewhere between what you might call &amp;ldquo;artsy&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;techie.&amp;rdquo;
He has worked in a variety of ways with expedition travellers, universities, NSCC and private career colleges, global finance, non-profits, indigenous economic development and education organizations in Canada.
Most recently, Scott has partnered with Ulnooweg to assist in the implementation of a bold new project that aims to transform science and digital education for Mi’kmaw children and youth living on reserves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shift! Mobile Interactive</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/shift-mobile-interactive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/shift-mobile-interactive/</guid>
      <description>Digital media technology changes weekly. We help you understand digital marketing and how to use it to grow your business.
Organizations typically approach us because they are:
 Feeling overwhelmed by all the digital marketing options Sick of getting “marketing tactics,” without effective and efficient methods to implement them On the “marketing hamster wheel” spending too much time and or ad money on digital media channels and they want better results Looking to rebrand or launch a brand Looking to launch a website Getting people to their website, but people aren’t converting or purchasing Needing a marketing planning template plan, implement, measure, and adjust as things change  Any of these sound familiar?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side Door</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/side-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/side-door/</guid>
      <description>Platform matching artists with spaces to create shows anytime, anywhere.
Side Door is a curated digital booking and ticketing platform used to facilitate booking and ticketing micro-performances in homes and other alternative venues in Canada and around the world. As a website and future mobile app, this technology-based company is innovating the traditional touring model for performers, live performances, and fan experiences.
Artists and Hosts sign up for free online through the Side Door website by creating profiles and answering questions about their preferences for performing or presenting a show in a house or alternative space (think bookstores, warehouses, parks, libraries, community centres, etc).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spark West Network</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/spark-west-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/spark-west-network/</guid>
      <description>We believe that rural Nova Scotia is a great place to be an entrepreneur. However, there is much need for improvement. There are gaps in our Western Nova rural ecosystem that we wish to tackle:
Unified Voice There is no unifying voice that pulls together the diverse organizations, events, and opportunities present in the Annapolis Valley, and sister municipalities. As individuals interested in what this community offers to entrepreneurs and creative professionals, it can be challenging to keep on top of what is going on of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terry Weatherbee</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/terry-wetherbee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/terry-wetherbee/</guid>
      <description>Terry Weatherbee is a Professor in the Manning School of Business at Acadia University, and has a number of different research areas of interest including the negative impacts of technology use in organizations and the historiography of management thought. His most current research focuses on the disruptive impact of Maker Technology and its opportunities for economic development and academic/economic partnership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The HUB South Shore</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-south-shore/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-south-shore/</guid>
      <description>The HUB South Shore is a coworking space that connects progressive businesses and people together so innovation and enterprise can thrive. We enjoy the freedom to run our own lives and depend on the motivation, productivity, and creativity that comes from working with others.
Our vision is for a self-reliant rural economy rooted in the collaboration of local entrepreneurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The HUB Yarmouth</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-yarmouth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-yarmouth/</guid>
      <description>Creative shared space The Hub is a co-working space for creative and social entrepreneurs in Yarmouth, Nova Scotia, Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Valley Regional Enterprise Network</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/valley-regional-enterprise-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/valley-regional-enterprise-network/</guid>
      <description>The Valley Regional Enterprise Network (Valley REN) was incorporated in March 2014 under the Municipal Government Act. The partnership comprises the Glooscap First Nation; Municipality of the County of Kings; Municipality of the District of West Hants; and the Towns of Berwick, Kentville, Middleton, Windsor and Wolfville. It is led by a volunteer Board of Directors, drawn mostly from the private sector and bringing to the table a wealth of experience in business and economic leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cooper</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tim-cooper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tim-cooper/</guid>
      <description>Tim Cooper is part of Henry Schein&amp;rsquo;s Global Innovation Center as a Software Developer. He is a member of the small team located in Nova Scotia, Canada, that develops primarily web-based software. The team&amp;rsquo;s mandate is to explore and prototype innovative ways that technology can be applied to the world of dental and health care. As a hobby, Tim enjoys contributing to Free Software projects and answering Stack Overflow questions. He graduated from Acadia University with a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Avery</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/trevor-avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/trevor-avery/</guid>
      <description>Trevor Avery is a marine biologist (Ph.D.) and biostatistician (P.Stat.) with a variety of research interests. U. of Guelph was home for his undergraduate Honours, Acadia U. for an M.Sc. (under Mike Dadswell) and Memorial U. for his Ph.D. (with Joe Brown, r.i.p.); Currently he is back with Acadia as an Associate Professor cross appointed within the faculties of Biology and Mathematics &amp;amp; Statistics.
Technology and analysis techniques (statistics) play a significant role in most of his research projects, but not all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Farmer</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tyler-farmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tyler-farmer/</guid>
      <description>For the last year and a half, Tyler has lead Digital Nova Scotia’s projects and skill development programs across Nova Scotia. Through this role, Tyler has had the opportunity to connect with a wide variety of ICT &amp;amp; digital tech companies, professional service providers, community leaders, and government agencies which has enabled him to build an effective grassroots network with a birds-eye perspective of the economic challenges facing the province. Prior to diving into the rewarding work of economic development through Nova Scotia’s IT association, Tyler coordinated inspection, expediting, and project management services for many of Canada’s leading oil and gas companies in Alberta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia/</guid>
      <description>Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia (BA, MA) is the President &amp;amp; CEO of Digital Nova Scotia  . She’s a multilingual senior level executive with over 20 years of combined experience in the private, public &amp;amp; academic sectors. Her career spans five geographic regions: America (North), Africa (South), Middle East, Asia &amp;amp; Europe.
Ulrike thrives on challenges! With a proven track record in International Marketing, Business &amp;amp; Economic Development, Channel Management, Government/Stakeholder Relations, Board Governance, Fundraising, Organizational Growth &amp;amp; Public Speaking, she&amp;rsquo;s a true game-changer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valley Family Fun</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/valley-family-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/valley-family-fun/</guid>
      <description>People who are new to the area (and some who are not) often ask Laura Churchill Duke what they can do with their families in the Valley.
This made her realize that there isn’t one central place to look for information. Valley Family Fun is a compilation of what she&amp;rsquo;s discovered! Follow VFF on their Facebook group too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are NS</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/we-are-ns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/we-are-ns/</guid>
      <description>Nova Scotia’s portfolio of the very best people, products, and places. We Are NS&#39; mission is to celebrate the very best brands and creative talent Nova Scotia has to offer one story at a time. Our vision is to create a vibrant community of people who build confidence among Nova Scotians by challenging themselves and supporting others to be better every day.
Join us and use the hashtag #WeAreNS to help us share our story to the world!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wes Booth</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/wes-booth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/wes-booth/</guid>
      <description>Wes Booth literally grew up during the birth of social media. In 2006, he signed on Facebook for the first time and in 2013 he sent his first Snap. Wes started his first business when he was 14 and is now working on a project to better connect and support brands and creative talent in Nova Scotia through his social media community called We Are NS. Wes believes in Atlantic Canada 100% and is determined social media is a good place to start telling our stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women in Science and Engineering at Acadia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>WISE (Women in Science and Engineering) at Acadia is a group of female faculty members from the Faculty of Pure and Applied Science and Kinesiology who gather together to address the unique issues that women in academia face. The group has supported learning opportunities and award applications for Acadia women faculty members. After a gathering held in October 2014 additional WISE priorities have been identified related to mentoring, science camps for young women, and a course offering for undergraduates in Women and Science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women&#39;s and Gender Studies</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-and-gender-studies-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-and-gender-studies-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>In 1973, Acadia University became one of the first universities in Canada to offer a course in Women&amp;rsquo;s Studies. The course, entitled Women in the Modern World, was the cornerstone of a program which in three decades has developed a multi-disciplinary approach to teaching and research in gender-related issues. Faculty members from the Arts, Pure and Applied Sciences, Education, Kinesiology, and Theatre contribute to the program on a rotational basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ballmer Peak</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ballmer-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ballmer-peak/</guid>
      <description>When surveying a bunch of #Refreshers what we should do for July:
A) Take off and enjoy the sun (47.1%)
B) Keep on trucking - regular Refresh meetup for July (35.3%)
C) Other - drink beer (17.6%)
&amp;hellip; so we drink beer!
Join us for a crazy selection of craft beer, pizza and banter. Bring your laptop and we can put the Ballmer Peak to the test**. Come chat about the BIG plans for Refresh in September and beyond&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiration. Imitation. Innovation: Transforming The Physical World With Open Source Hardware</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/inspiration-imitation-innovation-transforming-the-physical-world-with-open-source-hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/inspiration-imitation-innovation-transforming-the-physical-world-with-open-source-hardware/</guid>
      <description>Powered by open source hardware and software, students, engineers, and garage tinkerers alike are hacking the physical world. Using inexpensive “mini computers” like the Arduino, these makers are building interactive devices that can sense and control other physical objects. In this presentation, we will look at opportunity the Open Source Hardware Movement has created for everyday people to hack our technological world. Ian McKay will introduce us to hacking the Arduino with a newbie how-to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IP Matters</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ip-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ip-matters/</guid>
      <description>Take an engaging journey into the world of intellectual property (IP) and software. What IP do you have and how can you protect it? Is it better to use a trademark, copyright or a patent? How long does it take and what does it cost? This presentation will introduce you to the types of IP and why they matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Work: Coworking</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</guid>
      <description>There is lots of buzz around coworking spaces as a new way for independent and SME creative professionals to engage work. Coworking is about shared office space for professionals, but it is also about a style of work that suggests there are greater opportunities working in a diverse community setting. Coworking spaces themself are diverse in structure, ranging from the community powered, real-estate centric, to highbred business incubators.
In rural Nova Scotia, numerous coworking spaces are springing up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to WordPress</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/introduction-to-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/introduction-to-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is a free content management system used by more than 23.3% of the top 10 million websites. In this talk, Sandy McFadden and Raina Noel will show us what is it, what it can do for you, and how you can start using it to get your message online.
You&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to install WordPress and get it setup using Posts, Pages, Widgets, and Menus. Raina and Sandy will also show us how you can extend Wordpress functionality and change the way your site looks with Plugins and Themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STEAM Powered! Maker Space / FabLab @AcadiaU</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/steam-powered-maker-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/steam-powered-maker-space/</guid>
      <description>The recent and explosive growth in maker-culture combined with the emergence of 3D Printing in Fabrication Laboratories (or “FabLabs”) presents an opportunity for the province to prepare for the future by investing in economic and cultural change in rural Nova Scotia. Acting in concert with the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre and the Centre for Rural Innovation, Acadia’s new STEAM Space is working toward the creation of a Maker Space/FabLab on the Acadia University campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F5://Food</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/f5-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/f5-food/</guid>
      <description>Measure and mix together:
1 cup of farmers
½ pound regional food distributors
  2 tbsp chefs
  1 cup food policy experts
  1 dash of deep concern about making our regional bounty more accessible
  Stir in:
  2 tbsp software developers
  ½ cup interactive designers
  4 tbsp marketers
  1 pound new media entrepreneurs
  Stir new media ingredients into agricultural mixture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML5 and Semantic Markup</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/html5-and-semantic-markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/html5-and-semantic-markup/</guid>
      <description>Come join us for &amp;ldquo;HTML5 and Semantic Markup,&amp;rdquo; a discussion about HTML5, markup, and HTML5 websites that rock.
Open Web Platform: HTML5 and Semantic Markup Mike Caplan will give a talk about HTML5&amp;rsquo;s new elements and attributes that allow us to define semantically meaningful HTML. Semantics you say? What is the meaning of this? Come find out.
HTML5 Websites Show and Tell Dust off your favorite website that uses anything under the HTML5 sun – offline storage, connectivity, file access, semantics, audio/video, 3D/graphics, presentation, performance, big features, or small.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Projects Roundup: Round Two</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 19:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-two/</guid>
      <description>Come join us for &amp;ldquo;Local Projects Roundup - Round Two,&amp;rdquo; a discussion about interesting local web projects, platforms, business, and techies.
  Online Community Engagement with Laura Churchill Duke  Laura is the owner and operator of Valley Family Fun  which is a website for families living in the Annapolis Valley. It includes resources, ideas, information and a calendar of family-friendly events. Started in January 2012, it has grown to include a Facebook and Twitter site to form a web-based network of over 6000 followers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Projects Roundup: Round One</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 19:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-one/</guid>
      <description>Come join us for Local Projects Roundup - Round One, a discussion about interesting local web projects, and initiatives supporting startups.
  HUB Kentville with Frances Schagen  Calling all forward-thinking entrepreneurs, start ups, creatives, artists, freelancers, coders and non-profits. HUB Kentville  is a membership-based coworking spaces where people share an address, resources, equipment and community.     HarvestHand with Michael Caplan  Community Supported Agriculture (CSA) is a member based model for food production and distribution that unites local communities with local farms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
