<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:30:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>CODE: Debugging the Gender Gap</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;figure class=&#34;float-right&#34;&gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/images/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/poster.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;CODE: Debugging the Gender Gap&#34; /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE: Debugging The Gender Gap&lt;/em&gt; exposes the dearth of female and minority
software engineers and explores the reasons for this gender gap and digital divide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tech jobs are growing three times faster than our colleges are producing computer science
graduates. By 2019 there will be 182,000 jobs in information and communications technology
that will go unfilled by homegrown Canadian talent because not enough people will have the right skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through compelling interviews, artistic animation and clever flashpoints in popular culture,
&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; examines the reasons why more girls and people of color are not seeking out
opportunities in computer science and explores how cultural mindsets, stereotypes,
educational hurdles, and sexism all play roles in this national crisis. Expert voices from the
worlds of tech, psychology, science, and education are intercut with personal stories of women
who are engaged in the fight to challenge complacency in the tech industry and have their
voices heard. &lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; aims to inspire change in mindsets, in the educational system, in startup
culture and in the way women see themselves in the field of coding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This screening will feature an introductory keynote address by &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia&#34;&gt;Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia&lt;/a&gt;
,
President and CEO of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/digital-nova-scotia&#34;&gt;
    
        Digital Nova Scotia
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, to provide Canadian context to the film.
&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; will also be followed by an interactive panel discussion.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/123004482&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Computer code forms the foundation of modern society. Cell phones, apps, navigation systems,
medical equipment, banking, movie animation… are all driven by code. The more diverse a
team of coders is, the broader their perspective of society’s needs, which can ultimately result
in products that serve a greater breadth of humanity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; takes a hard look at the pipeline question in technology: why aren’t there more women
and minority graduates in computer science? What is stopping them from getting to the
threshold? &lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; follows the various challenges faced by a new generation of women
programmers and the ingenious ways they are using their skills, drive, intellect and vision to
disrupt the traditional, male-dominated tech world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; looks to the past, delving into the history of computing to highlight women like Ada
Lovelace and Grace Hopper who set the stage for today’s technology. &lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; acknowledges that
women have been an important part of computing since the genesis of computers, but have
since been written out of this history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; is not afraid to ask the hard questions and does so with intelligence and a sense of
humor, examining our culture from high (the views of former Harvard President Larry Summers
on innate ability) to low (an app called &amp;ldquo;Titstare&amp;rdquo; presented to a room of tech heavyweights).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A blend of personal stories, expert voices, innovative animation, historic discoveries, and
moments from popular culture are complemented with a cutting edge musical score and
bolstered by a strong sense of purpose. &lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; reflects, at its heart, the interconnectedness of
the stories, the web, and by proxy, the shared vision of a new, more democratic community
made possible by the inclusion of more women in code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Computer Science Society</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/acadia-computer-science-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/acadia-computer-science-society/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Need some info&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;AEC has been developing and delivering workshops for business professionals, entrepreneurs, and not-for-profits for over 25 years. AEC continues to innovate and develop new and relevant programs for today’s business professional.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;rural-innovation-centre&#34;&gt;Rural Innovation Centre&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Rural Innovation Centre (RIC) supports entrepreneurs and businesses in the Annapolis Valley and on the South Shore by providing training, advisory and consulting services to small businesses, government and not-for-profit organizations. The Rural Innovation Centre is an incubator for start up companies to access working space and support, networking events, mentors and connect to Acadia faculty and facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;launchbox&#34;&gt;Launchbox&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Launchbox is the centre for student entrepreneurs, located on the 4th floor of Patterson Hall at Acadia University. We support students in their entrepreneurial pursuits by providing free programming, networking, access to mentors, and other entrepreneurs, working space and competitions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Robotics Program</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Robot Programming Competition mission is to increase interest in building digital technology and computer science by engaging Nova Scotia students in annual robotics programming competitions and related activities that feature problem solving and teamwork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Acadia Robotics Program, through the Jodrey School of Computer Science, depends heavily on financial support from external organizations and the committed volunteers who annually contribute to the season from late August through to mid-June.  We have a junior program, FIRST® LEGO® League, and a senior program, Robofest. All the outreach throughout the season culminates in a Provincial Robot Programming Championship here at Acadia Unversity each February, involving over 400 participants, 100 volunteers, media and many organizations.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/qA3L8_KJB4c&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Intellectual Property Office </title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Canadian Intellectual Property Office (CIPO), a Special Operating Agency (SOA) associated with Innovation, Science and Economic Development Canada, is responsible for the administration and processing of the greater part of intellectual property in Canada. CIPO&amp;rsquo;s areas of activity include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patents cover new inventions (process, machine, manufacture, composition of matter), or any new and useful improvement of an existing invention;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A trademark is a word (or words), a design, or a combination of these, used to identify the goods or services of one person or organization and to distinguish these goods or services from those of others in the marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Copyright provide protection for artistic, dramatic, musical or literary works (including computer programs), and three other subject-matter known as: performance, sound recording and communication signal;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Industrial designs are the visual features of shape, configuration, pattern or ornament (or any combination of these features), applied to a finished article of manufacture;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Integrated circuit topographies refer to the three-dimensional configurations of electronic circuits embodied in integrated circuit products or layout designs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catherine Vardy</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/catherine-vardy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/catherine-vardy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Catherine Vardy joined the &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office&#34;&gt;
    
        Canadian Intellectual Property Office
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 (CIPO) in 2015. As a Business Development Officer for the Atlantic Region, Catherine enjoys working with people to identify and highlight the value of IP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Network Liaison and Program Manager at Springboard Atlantic, Catherine worked closely with innovative SMEs, universities and colleges. Catherine also worked in Atlantic Canada as a Research and Innovation Development Officer with the Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council (NSERC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When she’s not travelling, Catherine usually hangs out at her office at &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/innovacorp&#34;&gt;
    
        Innovacorp
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, in Halifax, Nova Scotia.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Greene</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/charlie-greene/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/charlie-greene/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Charlie is a software developer and system administrator at The REDspace. He is alumni from &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/colibri-software&#34;&gt;
    
        Colibri Software
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 where he worked for two years, ever since graduating from Acadia University with a Honors degree in Computer Science with Co-Op option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlie&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by the work of Ruby the painting elephant.  True story.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Jordan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/chris-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/chris-jordan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chris is a software developer with 16+ years experience with Henry Schein.  Not to be pigeonholed, he&amp;rsquo;s got his hand in all sorts of things: Top tier support for an installation base spanning 2000+ customers, Brand development, Application planning and development, Database design, Documentation, Testing, Training, Training material development: web, print and video, Customer support, Installer creation, Phone system programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chris&amp;rsquo; profile pic is a mashup of a picture of his swiped from Facebook and R2D2.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colibri Software</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/colibri-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/colibri-software/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Colibri Software builds awesome software. We work with our clients to understand their needs and then produce a simple and effective solution to their problems. Our focus is on making a product easy to use, from websites to mobile apps, we like it when we hear “this is easy”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a special affinity for mapping projects and have send rugged phone apps as far as Nunavut to help collect data for the hunting community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nova Scotia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/digital-nova-scotia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/digital-nova-scotia/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Engaging both members and stakeholders in the region, Digital Nova Scotia provides advocacy, multi-sectoral industry intelligence, facilitates connections between industry and talent, and delivers high-level programming to ensure Nova Scotia’s $1.5 billion digital industry (which boasts an additional $1 billion in spin-offs) continues to flourish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;it-starts-here-it-stays-here-it-grows-here&#34;&gt;IT starts here. IT stays here. IT grows here.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the industry association for the fastest growing sector in the province with the highest number of ICT graduates per capita in Canada, Digital Nova Scotia encourages our tech talent and growing ecosystem of digital businesses to start here, stay here, and grow here! We believe that Nova Scotia’s digital technologies sector has the potential to be what the oil and gas sector is for Alberta. Nova Scotia has the “IT” factor: globally competitive talent, an ecosystem of support, advanced digital infrastructure, and a drive to push our economic boundaries. We are going for growth on a global scale!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frances Schagen</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/frances-schagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/frances-schagen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Frances is a small business innovator. She geeks out over business strategy, business models and building entrepreneurial ecosystems. She believe that&amp;rsquo;s the kind of thinking we need to save the world. Frances helps create places where entrepreneurship can thrive within our business and within our community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business innovation is essential for us to solve our biggest issues and to succeed in the world today. Business theory was developed for large business and small business is not a little big business. Frances has been on this quest for decades, talking to 1000&amp;rsquo;s of business owners and reading 1000&amp;rsquo;s of books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your Effortless Business is her book where she outlines how you can make your business work better and be more entrepreneurial Hint:you don&amp;rsquo;t need an MBA to succeed in small business, in fact it will get in the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frances&amp;rsquo; profile picture was created by software trained in the fine art of pastels.  Header image a pic of Jacob Epstein&amp;rsquo;s sculpture &lt;em&gt;The Rush of Green or The Bowater House Group&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geoff Crouse</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Geoff has more than 17 years of combined Software Engineering and Information Technology Consulting experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technical Sales Engineer, specializing in medium to large scale Drupal CMS projects including new development, site audits and analysis, and expert support services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Account Management, coordinating customer projects with engineering and support teams from initial conception to final delivery, and continued support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Geoff&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove.  Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove pic care of Wikipedia.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HUB Kentville</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Get Inspired, Get Connected, Get involved. HUB spaces provide an inspirational home to members and are a focal point for change within the local communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-the-hub&#34;&gt;What is the Hub?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HUB is about the power of innovation through collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe there is no shortage of good ideas to solve the issues of our time. But there is an acute lack of collaboration and support structures to help make them happen. The HUB was founded to address this need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We set out to create spaces that combine the best of a trusted community, innovation lab, business incubator and the comforts of home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spaces with all the tools and trimmings needed to grow and develop innovative ventures for the world. But above all, spaces for meaningful encounters, exchange and inspiration, full of diverse people doing amazing things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea has been spreading like wildfire and resulted in the emergence of a global movement. To date, there are 25+ open HUBs and many more in the making, from London to San Francisco, Johannesburg, Melbourne and Sao Paulo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;mission&#34;&gt;Mission&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To become a global network of connected communities that enable collaborative ventures for a better world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the HUB, people from every profession, background and culture are being united by one thing: the imagination and drive to pursue enterprising ideas for the world. These are the people who see and do things differently and have entrepreneurial passion to create sustainable impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HUB is becoming the place they call home.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HarvestHand</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/harvesthand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/organization/harvesthand/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HarvestHand is a community platform dedicated to strengthening regional food systems. We&amp;rsquo;re passionate about supporting farms with CSA&amp;rsquo;s to become more profitable using HarvestHand CSA Software, helping communities eat better through the HarvestHand Community, creating good jobs in rural communities, and building new media solutions that make sharing the harvest easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our vision is to create new media solutions that strengthen regional food systems&amp;rsquo; ability to succeed in value oriented approaches to production, distribution, consumption and community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Mandate is to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the profitability of Community Shared Agriculture (CSA) farms through the ease and functionality of HarvestHand CSA Software Platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create localized and fairly paid employment opportunities in rural communities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make it easy for citizens to locate, join and remain a member of a CSA farm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a space for exploration of ideas, identification of problems and creation of solutions related to local food systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build out best of regional food tooling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;flex-video&#34;&gt;
    &lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/qNxWThFGa5M&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian McKay</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/ian-mckay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapilsvalley.org/person/ian-mckay/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“Creative Technician”&amp;hellip;what the heck is that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see my role, primarily, as that of a possibilitist. I listen closely to your ideas, what you hope to create, the problem you are working and then share with you the possibilities technology may offer. My years of immersion in Maker culture, joyfully exploring new and unusual uses for the wonders of emerging and age-old tech, provide me with a deep pool of possible solutions to your creative problems. While I am happy to help suggest solutions and inform you of the possibilities and challenges, I always keep in mind that the piece is YOUR work and will strive to help YOUR vision come to fruition. In those cases where a more collaborative model is what you are seeking, I would love to work with you to make our ideas a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ian&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://deepdreamgenerator.com/ddream/56b79f0b2d&#34;&gt;banner image&lt;/a&gt; is a photo of his home at Scots Bay&amp;hellip; reinterpreted by a machine influenced by the work of &lt;a href=&#34;http://hollycarr.weebly.com/&#34;&gt;Holly Carr&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>