<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Economy on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/economy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Economy on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/economy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>State of Our Digital Nation: Digital Nova Scotia 2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-our-digital-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-our-digital-nation/</guid>
      <description>Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s digital economy is currently valued at $2.5 billion. Tyler Farmer, Project Manager at Digital Nova Scotia, will present a state of our digital nation, reflecting on trends and opportunities, both urban and rural. Join us for our last Refresh meetup for the 2018-2019 year for discussion and drinks care of our host, Annapolis Cider Company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Farmer</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tyler-farmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tyler-farmer/</guid>
      <description>For the last year and a half, Tyler has lead Digital Nova Scotia’s projects and skill development programs across Nova Scotia. Through this role, Tyler has had the opportunity to connect with a wide variety of ICT &amp;amp; digital tech companies, professional service providers, community leaders, and government agencies which has enabled him to build an effective grassroots network with a birds-eye perspective of the economic challenges facing the province. Prior to diving into the rewarding work of economic development through Nova Scotia’s IT association, Tyler coordinated inspection, expediting, and project management services for many of Canada’s leading oil and gas companies in Alberta.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
