<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Startups on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshav.github.io/topics/startups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Startups on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshav.github.io/topics/startups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;AEC has been developing and delivering workshops for business professionals, entrepreneurs, and not-for-profits for over 25 years. AEC continues to innovate and develop new and relevant programs for today’s business professional.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;rural-innovation-centre&#34;&gt;Rural Innovation Centre&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Rural Innovation Centre (RIC) supports entrepreneurs and businesses in the Annapolis Valley and on the South Shore by providing training, advisory and consulting services to small businesses, government and not-for-profit organizations. The Rural Innovation Centre is an incubator for start up companies to access working space and support, networking events, mentors and connect to Acadia faculty and facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;launchbox&#34;&gt;Launchbox&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Launchbox is the centre for student entrepreneurs, located on the 4th floor of Patterson Hall at Acadia University. We support students in their entrepreneurial pursuits by providing free programming, networking, access to mentors, and other entrepreneurs, working space and competitions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frances Schagen</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/person/frances-schagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/person/frances-schagen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Frances is a small business innovator. She geeks out over business strategy, business models and building entrepreneurial ecosystems. She believe that&amp;rsquo;s the kind of thinking we need to save the world. Frances helps create places where entrepreneurship can thrive within our business and within our community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business innovation is essential for us to solve our biggest issues and to succeed in the world today. Business theory was developed for large business and small business is not a little big business. Frances has been on this quest for decades, talking to 1000&amp;rsquo;s of business owners and reading 1000&amp;rsquo;s of books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your Effortless Business is her book where she outlines how you can make your business work better and be more entrepreneurial Hint:you don&amp;rsquo;t need an MBA to succeed in small business, in fact it will get in the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frances&amp;rsquo; profile picture was created by software trained in the fine art of pastels.  Header image a pic of Jacob Epstein&amp;rsquo;s sculpture &lt;em&gt;The Rush of Green or The Bowater House Group&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Richards</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/person/paul-richards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/person/paul-richards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Paul Richards is &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/innovacorp&#34;&gt;
    
        innovacorp&amp;#39;s
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 regional manager for Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s Annapolis Valley and South Shore. In this role, Paul focuses on enabling knowledge-based companies to accelerate their growth and helping foster a dynamic high-growth entrepreneurial culture in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paul spent over 10 years working with the Acadia Centre for Social and Business Entrepreneurship (ACSBE) assisting businesses in rural Nova Scotia. In this role, Paul also worked to build the entrepreneurial capacity and infrastructure of several developing economies in Africa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining Innovacorp, Paul worked with the Atlantic Canadian Opportunities Agency, where he worked with several priority industry sectors, provided commercialization advice to academic researchers, and developed many innovative community projects designed to stimulate economic improvement across Nova Scotia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paul holds an economics degree from Acadia University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unknown to Paul, his profile pic was reinterpreted by a computer who studied the works of the famous Nova Scotia artist Maud Lewis.  Kashi Go Lean waffles inspired by Paul&amp;rsquo;s teachings on Lean business concepts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>innovacorp</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/innovacorp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/innovacorp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Innovacorp is Nova Scotia’s early stage venture capital organization. We work to find, fund and foster innovative Nova Scotia start-ups that strive to change the world. Early stage investment is at the core of our business model. We also give entrepreneurs access to world-class incubation facilities, expert advice and other support to help them accelerate their companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Target industries include clean technology, information technology, life sciences and ocean technology.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Projects Roundup: Round Two</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/event/local-projects-roundup-round-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 19:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/event/local-projects-roundup-round-two/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us for &amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;Local Projects Roundup - Round Two&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;rdquo; a discussion about interesting local web projects, platforms, business, and techies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;media-object&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;thumbnail&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img style=&#34;max-width: 100px&#34; src= &#34;https://refreshav.github.io/images/organization/valley-family-fun/icon.jpg&#34;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Online Community Engagement&lt;/strong&gt; with Laura Churchill Duke&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
    Laura is the owner and operator of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/valley-family-fun&#34;&gt;
    
        Valley Family Fun
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 which is a website for families living in the Annapolis Valley. It includes resources, ideas, information and a calendar of family-friendly events. Started in January 2012, it has grown to include a Facebook and Twitter site to form a web-based network of over 6000 followers.
&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;media-object&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;thumbnail&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img style=&#34;max-width: 100px&#34; src= &#34;https://refreshav.github.io/images/organization/scotiacom/icon.jpg&#34;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s Build a Drupal Site in 8 Minutes, 32 Seconds!&lt;/strong&gt; with Geoff Crouse&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
    Geoff of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/scotiacom&#34;&gt;
    
        ScotiaCom
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 will walk us through the build out of web sites using the popular open source Content Management System Drupal.
&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;media-object&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;thumbnail&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img style=&#34;max-width: 100px&#34; src= &#34;https://refreshav.github.io/images/organization/colibri-software/icon.png&#34;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Locomotive CMS&lt;/strong&gt; with Charlie&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
    Charlie from &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/colibri-software&#34;&gt;
    
        Colibri Software
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 will present a description of the architecture of Locomotive CMS (a data driven system which uses Ruby on Rails, MongoDB and liquid markup) in contrast to a traditional PHP (page driven, PHP, SQL) content management system. We will look at the strengths and weaknesses of Locomotive in this context.
&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;media-object&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;thumbnail&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img style=&#34;max-width: 100px&#34; src= &#34;https://refreshav.github.io/images/event/local-projects-roundup-round-two/coldfusion.png&#34;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coldfusion&lt;/strong&gt; with Keith Diehl&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
    How Coldfusion saved me from a week of grunt work - Using SQL Server and Coldfusion to generate 600 Word Documents.
&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Projects Roundup: Round One</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/event/local-projects-roundup-round-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 19:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/event/local-projects-roundup-round-one/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us for &lt;strong&gt;Local Projects Roundup - Round One&lt;/strong&gt;, a discussion about interesting local web projects, and initiatives supporting startups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;media-object&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;thumbnail&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img style=&#34;max-width: 100px&#34; src= &#34;https://refreshav.github.io/images/organization/hub-kentville/icon.jpg&#34;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HUB Kentville&lt;/strong&gt; with Frances Schagen&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
    Calling all forward-thinking entrepreneurs, start ups, creatives, artists, freelancers, coders and non-profits. &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/hub-kentville&#34;&gt;
    
        HUB Kentville
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 is a membership-based coworking spaces where people share an address, resources, equipment and community.
&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;media-object&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;thumbnail&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img style=&#34;max-width: 100px&#34; src= &#34;https://refreshav.github.io/images/organization/harvesthand/icon.png&#34;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HarvestHand&lt;/strong&gt; with Michael Caplan&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
    Community Supported Agriculture (CSA) is a member based model for food production and distribution that unites local communities with local farms. &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/harvesthand&#34;&gt;
    
        HarvestHand
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 is an Internet platform for CSA farms to communicate with and manage their community of members.
&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;media-object&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;thumbnail&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img style=&#34;max-width: 100px&#34; src= &#34;https://refreshav.github.io/images/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems/icon.png&#34;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digital Dental Exchange&lt;/strong&gt; with Chris Jordan and Justin Bezanson&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
    The &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems&#34;&gt;
    
        Digital Dental Exchange
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 (DDX) is a network connecting dental labs and dental practices, and all sorts of dental technologies in between.  Crowns, dentures, 3D scanners and printers, DDX is the fabric of twenty-first century dentistry.
&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;media-object&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;thumbnail&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img style=&#34;max-width: 100px&#34; src= &#34;https://refreshav.github.io/images/organization/progeny-genealogy/icon.png&#34;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wallcharts.com&lt;/strong&gt; with Pierre Clouthier&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
    Build your family tree or create a family chart, &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/progeny-genealogy&#34;&gt;
    
        wallcharts.com
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 allows you to easily share family genealogy information.
&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;media-object&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;thumbnail&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img style=&#34;max-width: 100px&#34; src= &#34;https://refreshav.github.io/images/organization/innovacorp/icon.jpg&#34;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;innovacorp&lt;/strong&gt; with Paul Richards&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/innovacorp&#34;&gt;
    
        innovacorp
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 is a provincial crown corporation that works to development the knowledge based economy through the development of growth orientated technology businesses.  Paul will discuss innovacorp&#39;s work here in the Valley to strengthen our IT sector.
&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>