<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Startups on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/startups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Startups on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 18:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/startups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Enter the Side Door</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-enter-the-side-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-enter-the-side-door/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Side Door is a digital platform that matches performing artists with venues to create shows anytime, anywhere, on their own terms.  Come meet CEO &amp;amp; Co-Founder &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson&#34;&gt;Laura Simpson&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; for a fireside chat and live performance with &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cassie-josephine&#34;&gt;Cassie Josephine&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; (Indie Folk Country princess).  Laura and Cassie will talk about the challenges artists in the music business face and how &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/side-door&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Side Door&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&amp;rsquo;s unique digital platform is defining a new business model capitalizing on the power of a networked community.  Learn how Side Door is poised to hit $1 million in annual ticket sales by the end of 2020.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Entrepreneur Chat over Beers</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-influencing-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-influencing-markets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this popup Startup Life entrepreneur chat over beers, we will be hosting Avery Schrader, a Nova Scotian living abroad in Tallinn, Estonia.  Estonia, for those not in the know, is a tiny Baltic state,  but in tech terms it&amp;rsquo;s a giant. It has a population of just 1.3 million, yet produces more start-ups per head than any other country in Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Avery is the founder of Modash, a tool that enables marketing teams to find and verify the audiences of over 50,000,000 influencers globally. Modash has raised $300,000 in funding from successful founders who have started companies like Pipedrive, Veriff, Yes.com and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Meet R2-Weed2</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-r2-weed2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-r2-weed2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Technology-driven agricultural experimentation.  Iterative product testing. Validated machine learning.  Pivot. Pivot. Pivot.  Welcome to the ag-tech startup world of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/teric-greenan&#34;&gt;Teric Greenan&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nexus-robotics&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Nexus Robotics&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nexus-robotics&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Nexus Robotics&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;, Teric is applying Artificial Intelligence to building a reliable and cost-effective way to produce crops. Their autonomous robot R2-Weed2 is capable of cutting and spraying weeds, fertilizing crops, and collect data about growing conditions.  Teric will talk about his team&amp;rsquo;s start up journey, and the amazing technological innovations they are applying to revolutionize agriculture as we know it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avery Schrader</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/avery-schrader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/avery-schrader/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Whoop Whoop! You found me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have been starting businesses since I was 12, When I hijacked my moms old laptop to entertain myself while we lived in a barn. A few months later I accidentally started a business connecting people online playing a game that I loved. As a kid I sold Christmas trees, made maple syrup, started volunteer groups, and played in the woods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now I have an amazing team and a real vision.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richelle Brown Redden</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/richelle-brown-redden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/richelle-brown-redden/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Valley Regional Enterprise Network is the only publicly funded organization dedicated to supporting the local economic development of five municipalities and one First Nation in the Annapolis Valley region. Through the Valley Regional Enterprise Network’s BusinessNOW program Richelle helps businesses assess their needs, plan for success and fight the right resources.  As a publicly funded resource, the BusinessNOW services are offered at not cost to local businesses.  A combination of experience and passion to see the region grow, bring insight and dedication to her work with the BusinessNOW program.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revved Up!</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/revved-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/revved-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;March 23 to 24th is launchbox&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://acadiaentrepreneurshipcentre.com/launchbox/start-it-up/&#34;&gt;Start It Up!&lt;/a&gt; - a weekend business ideation competition with 10K in prizes to be won.  If you are interested in playing with new business ideas, this event is for you.  While an University event, we have had youth teams (and winning youth teams!) at several Start It Up! competitions.  This year is no different.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in learning more about this business ideation event, come to this information session and beef up on your skills to help you compete.  We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the event format, review tools, and hear from a profesional public speaker on how to nail a presentation.  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life:  Youth Gone Wild</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-youth-gone-wild/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-youth-gone-wild/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aristides Milios is possessed.  In 2014 he co-founded Microcent Technologies. As CTO he focused on incubating hyper-local location technology for use in small-to-mid sized businesses.  In 2015, he co-founded Hoist Halifax: a monthly series of workshops for teens interested in design, entrepreneurship and tech.  That same year, he graduated from Propel ICT Accelerator Program.  In 2016 he graduated from High School.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this fireside chat, come learn what drives Aristides towards the tech startup trenches, and how he is building a youth entrepreneurship culture in Nova Scotia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Feel The Frost Byte</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-feel-the-frost-byte/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-feel-the-frost-byte/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Business-hypothesis-driven experimentation.  Iterative product releases. Validated learning.  Pivot. Pivot. Pivot.  Welcome to the tech startup world of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/john-frost&#34;&gt;John Frost&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From the early days of Frostbyte Interactive, Aerhyve Aerial Technologies, and now PrecisionHawk, John&amp;rsquo;s pursuit of innovative products and services in the digital tech space runs years long.  Join us for a fireside chat with John where we will explore the inner working of a person committed to the startup life.  We will examine his failures, study lessons learned from the startup trenches, and most importantly celebrate his successes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AEC has been developing and delivering workshops for business professionals, entrepreneurs, and not-for-profits for over 25 years. AEC continues to innovate and develop new and relevant programs for today’s business professional.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;rural-innovation-centre&#34;&gt;Rural Innovation Centre&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Rural Innovation Centre (RIC) supports entrepreneurs and businesses in the Annapolis Valley and on the South Shore by providing training, advisory and consulting services to small businesses, government and not-for-profit organizations. The Rural Innovation Centre is an incubator for start up companies to access working space and support, networking events, mentors and connect to Acadia faculty and facilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Button</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a 15 year career with various businesses and economic development organizations, Andrew felt it was about time to move from being a ‘cheerleader’ and ‘curator’ of entrepreneurship to doing something that actually produced more entrepreneurs in rural communities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;​In 2014 he founded &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mashuplab.ca/&#34;&gt;Mashup Lab&lt;/a&gt;; a for-more-than-profit company that activates rural ideas.  That same year he launched a chapter of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.awesomesouthshore.ca/&#34;&gt;Awesome Foundation&lt;/a&gt; in his community. Andrew has since gone on to launch another social enterprise - &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        CO3&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;, a fresh new coworking space for Freelancers, Entrepreneurs, and Independents located in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aristides Milios</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/aristides-milios/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/aristides-milios/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aristides is a highly motivated university student passionate about entrepreneurship, innovation, and web development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CTO MicroCent Technologies and Co-Founder of Hoist Halifax, Aristides is full stack web developer who loves public speaking and is a natural leader.  Smokin.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Garrett</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/elizabeth-garrett/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/elizabeth-garrett/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Just like becoming an expert in wine - you learn by drinking it, the best you can afford - you learn great food by finding the best there is, whether simply or luxurious. Then you savor it, analyze it, discuss it with your companions, and you compare it with other experiences&amp;rdquo; - Julia Child, &lt;em&gt;Mastering the Art of French Cooking&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emily Konrath</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/emily-konrath/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/emily-konrath/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emily is a small business enthusiast with a passion for homegrown talent. Emily was born and raised in Wolfville, studied her Bachelor of Commerce degree at Saint Mary’s University and obtained her Masters in International Business from Jönköping, Sweden.  Emily has lived and studied in cities across Canada and abroad in Germany and Sweden.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Emily is an Economic Development Officer with the Valley Regional Enterprise Network, a municipal corporation that works as a catalyst for regional economic development in the Annapolis Valley. Emily is tasked with sector development of five core sectors that present key opportunities for growth and investment attraction (Agriculture; Information, Communications and Technologies (ICT); Manufacturing, Sustainable Energy; and Tourism). Previously, Emily worked as an International Trade Consultant working with firms interested in exporting to international markets where she travelled across Europe, South America, and the Caribbean matching businesses to international opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frances Schagen</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/frances-schagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/frances-schagen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Frances is a small business innovator. She geeks out over business strategy, business models and building entrepreneurial ecosystems. She believe that&amp;rsquo;s the kind of thinking we need to save the world. Frances helps create places where entrepreneurship can thrive within our business and within our community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Business innovation is essential for us to solve our biggest issues and to succeed in the world today. Business theory was developed for large business and small business is not a little big business. Frances has been on this quest for decades, talking to 1000&amp;rsquo;s of business owners and reading 1000&amp;rsquo;s of books.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>innovacorp</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/innovacorp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/innovacorp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Innovacorp is Nova Scotia’s early stage venture capital organization. We work to find, fund and foster innovative Nova Scotia start-ups that strive to change the world. Early stage investment is at the core of our business model. We also give entrepreneurs access to world-class incubation facilities, expert advice and other support to help them accelerate their companies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Target industries include clean technology, information technology, life sciences and ocean technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Frost</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/john-frost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/john-frost/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;John Frost is a Senior Manager, Satellite Products, at PrecisionHawk.  John worked extensively in geophysical research and exploration before returning to university to complete studies in International Relations/Intercultural Studies. With broad national and international project exposure, he is a cross-cultural specialist in technology adaptation. Through the Aerhyve brand, the company focused on the analysis of UAV data with Machine Learning, providing actionable intelligence for agricultural and industrial applications. An entrepreneur and technophile, John is always pursuing opportunities which make a local-global impact.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launchbox</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/launchbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/launchbox/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Launchbox is the centre for student entrepreneurs, located on the 4th floor of Patterson Hall at Acadia University. We support students in their entrepreneurial pursuits by providing free programming, networking, access to mentors, and other entrepreneurs, working space and competitions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laura Simpson</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lover of music and truth. Listen to the poets. Founder of The Syrup Factory, Make.Do.Camp. and Side Door.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Laura Simpson is a music industry professional, living with her family in Halifax, Nova Scotia. She founded The Syrup Factory, which began hosting house concerts 2011 and offering strategy and services to artists in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She has been an organizer in the arts scene since she was 14, going to all-ages shows and then eventually taking live music photography and freelance writing about shows and artists. That led her to be a journalist for seven years, working for CBC and Rogers Radio.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul Richards</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/paul-richards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/paul-richards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Paul Richards is &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/innovacorp&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        innovacorp&amp;#39;s&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; regional manager for Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s Annapolis Valley and South Shore. In this role, Paul focuses on enabling knowledge-based companies to accelerate their growth and helping foster a dynamic high-growth entrepreneurial culture in the region.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Paul spent over 10 years working with the Acadia Centre for Social and Business Entrepreneurship (ACSBE) assisting businesses in rural Nova Scotia. In this role, Paul also worked to build the entrepreneurial capacity and infrastructure of several developing economies in Africa.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Side Door</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/side-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/side-door/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Platform matching artists with spaces to create shows anytime, anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Side Door is a curated digital booking and ticketing platform used to facilitate booking and ticketing micro-performances in homes and other alternative venues in Canada and around the world. As a website and future mobile app, this technology-based company is innovating the traditional touring model for performers, live performances, and fan experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Artists and Hosts sign up for free online through the Side Door website by creating profiles and answering questions about their preferences for performing or presenting a show in a house or alternative space (think bookstores, warehouses, parks, libraries, community centres, etc). The platform automatically matches Artists and Hosts based on their mutual profile preferences. Once matched, they are notified of the match, and prompted to discuss the details of booking a show together. Not only is Side Door a booking tool, but the online platform also has a booking contract and ticketing component that allows the Host to advertise and sell tickets. Fans will be able to visit the website or download the app to view shows in their area and shows they have been invited to, and they can buy tickets instantly online. Once the show is over the Host, Artist, and fans are all asked to provide feedback on the attended show.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F5://Food</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/f5-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/f5-food/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Measure and mix together:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1 cup of farmers&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;½ pound regional food distributors&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2 tbsp chefs&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1 cup food policy experts&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1 dash of deep concern about making our regional bounty more accessible&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stir in:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2 tbsp software developers&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;½ cup interactive designers&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4 tbsp marketers&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1 pound new media entrepreneurs&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stir new media ingredients into agricultural mixture. Mix thoroughly with a group of mentors. Broil for 48 hours. Serve hot to a group of judges.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Projects Roundup: Round Two</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 19:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-two/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us for &amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;Local Projects Roundup - Round Two&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;rdquo; a discussion about interesting local web projects, platforms, business, and techies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;media-object&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;thumbnail&#34;&gt;&#xA;            &lt;img style=&#34;max-width: 100px&#34; src= &#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/images/organization/valley-family-fun/icon.jpg&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Online Community Engagement&lt;/strong&gt; with Laura Churchill Duke&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;        &lt;p&gt;&#xA;    Laura is the owner and operator of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/valley-family-fun&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Valley Family Fun&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; which is a website for families living in the Annapolis Valley. It includes resources, ideas, information and a calendar of family-friendly events. Started in January 2012, it has grown to include a Facebook and Twitter site to form a web-based network of over 6000 followers.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Projects Roundup: Round One</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 19:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-one/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us for &lt;strong&gt;Local Projects Roundup - Round One&lt;/strong&gt;, a discussion about interesting local web projects, and initiatives supporting startups.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;media-object&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;thumbnail&#34;&gt;&#xA;            &lt;img style=&#34;max-width: 100px&#34; src= &#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/images/organization/hub-kentville/icon.jpg&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HUB Kentville&lt;/strong&gt; with Frances Schagen&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;        &lt;p&gt;&#xA;    Calling all forward-thinking entrepreneurs, start ups, creatives, artists, freelancers, coders and non-profits. &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        HUB Kentville&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; is a membership-based coworking spaces where people share an address, resources, equipment and community.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;media-object&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;thumbnail&#34;&gt;&#xA;            &lt;img style=&#34;max-width: 100px&#34; src= &#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/images/organization/harvesthand/icon.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;media-object-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HarvestHand&lt;/strong&gt; with Michael Caplan&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;        &lt;p&gt;&#xA;    Community Supported Agriculture (CSA) is a member based model for food production and distribution that unites local communities with local farms. &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/harvesthand&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        HarvestHand&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; is an Internet platform for CSA farms to communicate with and manage their community of members.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
