<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Art on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Art on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 10:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>f5://imagination</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;f5://imagination is a pop up exhibit focused on digital creativity.  This one day temporary exhibit features work from digital artists, makers, scratchers, computer scientists, engineers and pretendgineer, hardware hackers, lego robotics warriors, indy game developers, new media innovators, VR and AR pioneers&amp;hellip;  digital builders of all shapes, sizes, and credentials.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Schedule&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;    &lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10 AM to 12:30 PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;    &lt;dl&gt;Screening &amp; discussion of &lt;em&gt;Hidden Figures&lt;/em&gt;:  The story of a team of female African-American mathematicians who served a vital role in NASA during the early years of the U.S. space program.  Hosted by Dr. Randy Newman (Professor of Psychology, Acadia University.  &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Women in Science and Engineering at Acadia University&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;).  An area of Dr. Newman&#39;s work is in understanding factors responsible for the gender gap that persists in some areas of science, notably computer science and engineering.  &lt;strong&gt;Limited Space: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.eventbrite.ca/e/f5imagination-hidden-figures-screening-discussion-tickets-40998671129&#34;&gt;get your free ticket to secure your spot&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&#xA;    &lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1 PM to 4:00 PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;    &lt;dl&gt;f5://imagination reception. Artists will be in attendance, light refreshments served.&lt;/dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Submissions are being accepted until midnight December 13.  To submit, fill out the below form (bottom of the page).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
