<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Persons on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>http://refreshav.github.io/person/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Persons on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://refreshav.github.io/person/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Jordan</title>
      <link>http://refreshav.github.io/person/chris-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshav.github.io/person/chris-jordan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chris is a software developer with 16+ years experience with Henry Schein.  Not to be pigeonholed, he&amp;rsquo;s got his hand in all sorts of things: Top tier support for an installation base spanning 2000+ customers, Brand development, Application planning and development, Database design, Documentation, Testing, Training, Training material development: web, print and video, Customer support, Installer creation, Phone system programming.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frances Schagen</title>
      <link>http://refreshav.github.io/person/frances-schagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshav.github.io/person/frances-schagen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Frances is a small business innovator. She geeks out over business strategy, business models and building entrepreneurial ecosystems. She believe that&amp;rsquo;s the kind of thinking we need to save the world. Frances helps create places where entrepreneurship can thrive within our business and within our community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business innovation is essential for us to solve our biggest issues and to succeed in the world today. Business theory was developed for large business and small business is not a little big business. Frances has been on this quest for decades, talking to 1000&amp;rsquo;s of business owners and reading 1000&amp;rsquo;s of books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your Effortless Business is her book where she outlines how you can make your business work better and be more entrepreneurial Hint:you don&amp;rsquo;t need an MBA to succeed in small business, in fact it will get in the way.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justin Bezanson</title>
      <link>http://refreshav.github.io/person/justin-bezanson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshav.github.io/person/justin-bezanson/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since 2000 I have continued to expand my knowledge and skills and worked hard to be the best developer I can be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I enjoy meeting challenges and working hard to find creative and user friendly solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My goal is to continually improve my development process, delivering higher quality and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specialties: PHP, ASP.NET MVC, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, CodeIgniter, Zend Framework, AJAX, Windows, Linux, MySQL, SQL Server, WordPress, ASP.NET&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Caplan</title>
      <link>http://refreshav.github.io/person/michael-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshav.github.io/person/michael-caplan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mike has been active as a web application developer and web designer for 16 years, working in the non-profit, university, retail, agricultural, and dental industries. He is a founding partner of &lt;a href=&#34;http://refreshav.github.io/organization/harvesthand&#34;&gt;
    
        HarvestHand
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, a platform that services Community Shared Agriculture farms. More recently, Mike founded &lt;a href=&#34;http://refreshav.github.io/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley&#34;&gt;
    
        Refresh Annapolis Valley
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, a new media professional association to help grow the Valley&amp;rsquo;s technology industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike is the Software Development Manager for the &lt;a href=&#34;http://refreshav.github.io/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems&#34;&gt;
    
        Labnet Dental Lab Systems
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 division of Henry Schein - a Fortune 300 company with a small footprint here in Wolfville.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Richards</title>
      <link>http://refreshav.github.io/person/paul-richards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshav.github.io/person/paul-richards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Paul Richards is &lt;a href=&#34;http://refreshav.github.io/organization/innovacorp&#34;&gt;
    
        innovacorp&amp;#39;s
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 regional manager for Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s Annapolis Valley and South Shore. In this role, Paul focuses on enabling knowledge-based companies to accelerate their growth and helping foster a dynamic high-growth entrepreneurial culture in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paul spent over 10 years working with the Acadia Centre for Social and Business Entrepreneurship (ACSBE) assisting businesses in rural Nova Scotia. In this role, Paul also worked to build the entrepreneurial capacity and infrastructure of several developing economies in Africa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining Innovacorp, Paul worked with the Atlantic Canadian Opportunities Agency, where he worked with several priority industry sectors, provided commercialization advice to academic researchers, and developed many innovative community projects designed to stimulate economic improvement across Nova Scotia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paul holds an economics degree from Acadia University.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pierre Clouthier</title>
      <link>http://refreshav.github.io/person/pierre-clouthier/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshav.github.io/person/pierre-clouthier/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Co-founder, CTO Progeny Software, specialising in computer graphics software for genealogy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>