<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>people on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/</link>
    <description>Recent content in people on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Avery Schrader</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/avery-schrader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/avery-schrader/</guid>
      <description>Whoop Whoop! You found me.
I have been starting businesses since I was 12, When I hijacked my moms old laptop to entertain myself while we lived in a barn. A few months later I accidentally started a business connecting people online playing a game that I loved. As a kid I sold Christmas trees, made maple syrup, started volunteer groups, and played in the woods.
Now I have an amazing team and a real vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richelle Brown Redden</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/richelle-brown-redden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/richelle-brown-redden/</guid>
      <description>The Valley Regional Enterprise Network is the only publicly funded organization dedicated to supporting the local economic development of five municipalities and one First Nation in the Annapolis Valley region. Through the Valley Regional Enterprise Network’s BusinessNOW program Richelle helps businesses assess their needs, plan for success and fight the right resources. As a publicly funded resource, the BusinessNOW services are offered at not cost to local businesses. A combination of experience and passion to see the region grow, bring insight and dedication to her work with the BusinessNOW program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teric Greenan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/teric-greenan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/teric-greenan/</guid>
      <description>Teric grew up in Halifax, Nova Scotia. He ran a small vegetable farm in Lunenburg County, Nova Scotia for three years. He observed there were a lot of repetitive tasks on farms that were consuming farmers’ resources. These repetitive tasks seemed like good candidates to be automated. After talking with other vegetable farmers, it became clear that weeding was a massive problem that could be solved by a robot. In May of 2017, Teric founded Nexus Robotics with his close friend who is a computer engineer, Jad Tawil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alexander Petkov</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/alexander-petkov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/alexander-petkov/</guid>
      <description>Alexander Petkov is a high school student who attends Horton High School and is one of the co-founders of Spark West Network, a non-profit organization that aims to pull together the diverse organizations, events, and opportunities present in the Annapolis Valley. He is also the Chief Marketing Officer for Refresh Annapolis Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anne Stieger</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anne-stieger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anne-stieger/</guid>
      <description>Anne is a process geek, facilitator and trainer with a knack for creative, collaborative processes and deep play. She is trained and experienced in a diverse range of facilitation practices including the Art of Hosting, Design Thinking, Dynamic Governance and Appreciative Inquiry. Anne was first introduced to Design Thinking when she was a teacher at Duisburg-Essen University in Germany through a project that connects High School &amp;amp; University students to solve local sustainability challenges through Design Thinking, and she has been hooked ever since by the power of the approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashley Greene</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ashley-greene/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ashley-greene/</guid>
      <description>Ashley Greene, J.D., is the Founder &amp;amp; CEO of Instratify, a growth-focused customer research firm for software and e-commerce businesses. Ashley is known for using her legal training to help companies get inside their customers’ heads, so they can achieve and maintain sustainable hypergrowth.
Ashley’s advised dozens of tech companies and has worked on projects with businesses from Fortune 500 companies to tech startups. Ashley writes and speaks on growth / customer insight, and has served as an advisor/trainer for leading startup organizations including Ryerson, Volta, and Communitech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duncan Ebata</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/duncan-ebata/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/duncan-ebata/</guid>
      <description>I’ve worked primarily with food social enterprises and tech startups, so adaption and collaboration are in my bag. Whether it be branding for food social enterprises, promoting local investment funds, implementing community economic development strategies, hosting food community events, building entrepreneurial culture: building food communities and promoting social enterprises is what I do.
I’ve been on the ground growing food and beverage start-ups reach their first $100k in sales, promoting local investment funds to reach their first $1 million, and growing multi-million dollar retail food businesses with 30%+ yearly growth rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evan Hill</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/evan-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/evan-hill/</guid>
      <description>Evan works with small to medium businesses in solving marketing hurdles, content creation, product launches, and digital growth. After working as an analyst in the hedge fund industry, he co-found an apparel design &amp;amp; distribution company that focused on student travel. Then spent 3 years in Toronto and the US with a content marketing company that generated digital athletic training content for young athletes. He’s worked with clients &amp;amp; brands such as Recode, Cut, @Dunk, Hyperice, APL Athletics, Sports1Marketing, Susar Lee Restaurants, and Nova Scotia Fisherman Bodycare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katelyn Bourgoin</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/katelyn-bourgoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/katelyn-bourgoin/</guid>
      <description>Katelyn Bourgoin is a 3X founder/business owner turned growth strategist. She helps frustrated marketers and business owners to figure out why customers aren’t buying and how they can fix it.
When companies know who their best customers are and what they really want, it becomes much easier to create awesome products and sell more of them. The result? Happier customers and more money in the bank.
Katelyn’s past clients include startups, small businesses, and Fortune 500s like Target and Holiday Inn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adam Conner</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/adam-conner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/adam-conner/</guid>
      <description>Adam is a teacher at Northeast Kings Education Centre in Canning, NS. He teaches math, technology, and computer programming. Adam been experimenting with the world of Making and 3D Printing for the past 18 months. Working with students at NKEC, he has been helping them create, print, and selling products designed and 3D printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex Sanford</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/alex-sanford/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/alex-sanford/</guid>
      <description>Alex is a software developer, musician, coffee enthusiast, and space geek. He was born and raised here in the Valley, and has a long time passion for science, technology, and lifelong learning.
Currently, Alex is a Code Wrangler for Automattic, the creators of WordPress.com. Automattic has close ties with the WordPress open source project, which powers 33% of the websites on the internet. Automattic’s mission is to make the web a better place by advocating openness, freedom, diversity, and inclusivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Button</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</guid>
      <description>After a 15 year career with various businesses and economic development organizations, Andrew felt it was about time to move from being a ‘cheerleader’ and ‘curator’ of entrepreneurship to doing something that actually produced more entrepreneurs in rural communities.
​In 2014 he founded Mashup Lab; a for-more-than-profit company that activates rural ideas. That same year he launched a chapter of the Awesome Foundation in his community. Andrew has since gone on to launch another social enterprise - CO3  , a fresh new coworking space for Freelancers, Entrepreneurs, and Independents located in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anita Kirkbride</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anita-kirkbride/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anita-kirkbride/</guid>
      <description>She&amp;rsquo;s on a mission to help small businesses understand how to use social media to serve their clients and grow sales.
Trying to keep up with ever-changing social media trends is exhausting, even for the most caffeinated among us. But Twirp Communications founder Anita Kirkbride is here to help you save all that coffee money.
Anita’s social media experience extends all the way back to the 90s, when she joined the first generation of bloggers, launching a crafting blog in a flurry of cardstock, buttons, and fabric swatches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aristides Milios</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/aristides-milios/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/aristides-milios/</guid>
      <description>Aristides is a highly motivated university student passionate about entrepreneurship, innovation, and web development.
CTO MicroCent Technologies and Co-Founder of Hoist Halifax, Aristides is full stack web developer who loves public speaking and is a natural leader. Smokin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barry Gander</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/barry-gander/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/barry-gander/</guid>
      <description>For 25 years Barry Gander has helped jump-start the development of advanced technology organizations in Canada and abroad. Working with companies, associations, the public sector and academia, Barry has established a network of leaders who thrive on leading-edge initiatives. As EVP of Canada’s largest high-tech association, the Canadian Advanced Technology Alliance (CATA) Barry has helped showcase the best of Canadian innovation to global markets. The i-CANADA program, which he co-founded, aims to create an “Intelligent Nation” by establishing a grass-roots movement of communities that network at ultra-fast speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cassie Josephine</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cassie-josephine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cassie-josephine/</guid>
      <description>With “a voice that sits between Roy Orbison and Dolly Parton,” Cassie Josephine provides a vintage sound to her deeply personal narratives (Jeff Liberty - CBC). Her latest collection of songs, Only Half Blue, is one she thinks of fondly as a fairytale of middle-aged proportions. With her backing band, The Cry If I Want To’s, Cassie’s dreamy anthems are brought to life with soaring harmonies, violin, piano, and electric guitar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catherine Vardy</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/catherine-vardy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/catherine-vardy/</guid>
      <description>Catherine Vardy joined the Canadian Intellectual Property Office  (CIPO) in 2015. As a Business Development Officer for the Atlantic Region, Catherine enjoys working with people to identify and highlight the value of IP.
As the Network Liaison and Program Manager at Springboard Atlantic, Catherine worked closely with innovative SMEs, universities and colleges. Catherine also worked in Atlantic Canada as a Research and Innovation Development Officer with the Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council (NSERC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Greene</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/charlie-greene/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/charlie-greene/</guid>
      <description>Charlie is a senior software developer at The REDspace. He is alumni from Colibri Software  where he worked for two years, ever since graduating from Acadia University with a Honors degree in Computer Science with Co-Op option.
Charlie&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by the work of Ruby the painting elephant. True story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Jordan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/chris-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/chris-jordan/</guid>
      <description>Chris is a software developer with 16+ years experience with Henry Schein. Not to be pigeonholed, he&amp;rsquo;s got his hand in all sorts of things: Top tier support for an installation base spanning 2000+ customers, Brand development, Application planning and development, Database design, Documentation, Testing, Training, Training material development: web, print and video, Customer support, Installer creation, Phone system programming.
Chris&#39; profile pic is a mashup of a picture of his swiped from Facebook and R2D2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cindy Trudel</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel/</guid>
      <description>Cindy Trudel is an Instructor in Acadia University&amp;rsquo;s Departments of Computer Science, Business and Mathematics. Her primary research interest is in developing retention programs for students who have self-selected Computer Science as an area of study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Duke</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/david-duke/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/david-duke/</guid>
      <description>David Duke is an Associate Professor in the Department of History and Classics and as Coordinator of the university&amp;rsquo;s recently-established Environmental and Sustainability Studies program. His academic areas of expertise are the history of Russia and the USSR, the history of science, and environmental history, and he teaches in all these areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Daniel Silver</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-daniel-silver/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-daniel-silver/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Daniel L. Silver is the Director of the Acadia Institute for Data Analytics  . He is also a Professor in and currently the Acting-Director of the Jodrey School of Computer Science  at Acadia University. His areas of research and application are machine learning, data mining, and data analytics. His expertise is in Lifelong Machine Learning and Transfer Learning. He has published over 65 scientific papers and has co-chaired or been part of program committees for a number of national and international conferences, seminars and workshops on data mining and machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Darcy Benoit</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-darcy-benoit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-darcy-benoit/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Darcy Benoit is a Professor in and the Director of the Jodrey School of Computer Science at Acadia University. His areas of research include mobile application development, database management systems, and computer science education. An avid supporter educational outreach, Darcy oversees the Acadia Robotics program, a province-wide outreach program that sees approximately 400 students from grades 9-18 compete in two international robot programming competitions. His outreach work resulted in him collaborating with the Nova Scotia Department of Education and Early Childhood Development on the implementation of computer programming in the public school system from grades 7-12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Randy Newman</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-randy-newman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-randy-newman/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Newman is a Cognitive Neuroscientist whose primary research interest is in understanding the brain mechanisms responsible for reading and speech processes using event-related potentials and eye tracking techniques. Current research is examining the impact of a word&amp;rsquo;s spelling on how quickly we recognize spoken words.
A secondary area of interest is in understanding factors responsible for the gender gap that persists in some areas of science, notably computer science and engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Garrett</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/elizabeth-garrett/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/elizabeth-garrett/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Just like becoming an expert in wine - you learn by drinking it, the best you can afford - you learn great food by finding the best there is, whether simply or luxurious. Then you savor it, analyze it, discuss it with your companions, and you compare it with other experiences&amp;rdquo; - Julia Child, Mastering the Art of French Cooking</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emily Konrath</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/emily-konrath/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/emily-konrath/</guid>
      <description>Emily is a small business enthusiast with a passion for homegrown talent. Emily was born and raised in Wolfville, studied her Bachelor of Commerce degree at Saint Mary’s University and obtained her Masters in International Business from Jönköping, Sweden. Emily has lived and studied in cities across Canada and abroad in Germany and Sweden.
Emily is an Economic Development Officer with the Valley Regional Enterprise Network, a municipal corporation that works as a catalyst for regional economic development in the Annapolis Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frances Schagen</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/frances-schagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/frances-schagen/</guid>
      <description>Frances is a small business innovator. She geeks out over business strategy, business models and building entrepreneurial ecosystems. She believe that&amp;rsquo;s the kind of thinking we need to save the world. Frances helps create places where entrepreneurship can thrive within our business and within our community.
Business innovation is essential for us to solve our biggest issues and to succeed in the world today. Business theory was developed for large business and small business is not a little big business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gary Morton</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/gary-morton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/gary-morton/</guid>
      <description>Gary is a business development consultant/coach that for over 30 years has worked with farms, business and organization clients to find and develop new value added ideas, profit and success from what they do. This includes product development, commercialization, business planning, market development (domestic and export), product launch, training programs and managing business growth around new products and services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genevieve Allen Hearn</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/genevieve-allen-hearn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/genevieve-allen-hearn/</guid>
      <description>Genevieve is an arts administrator, specializing in organizing cultural events and festivals. Currently, Genevieve is working for the Atlantic Public Arts Funders, organizing an Indigenous Arts Symposium for Atlantic Canada. She is part-owner and Operations Manager of The Grapevine, the Annapolis Valley’s bi-weekly arts and culture publication. Her volunteer work includes serving on the board of Uncommon Common Art, the Kentville Art Gallery Society, and the Youth Engagement Working Group for the Municipality of the County of Kings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geoff Crouse</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</guid>
      <description>Geoff has more than 17 years of combined Software Engineering and Information Technology Consulting experience.
  Technical Sales Engineer, specializing in medium to large scale Drupal CMS projects including new development, site audits and analysis, and expert support services.
  Account Management, coordinating customer projects with engineering and support teams from initial conception to final delivery, and continued support.
  Geoff&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hope Latta</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/hope-latta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/hope-latta/</guid>
      <description>Hope is in her senior year of Computer Science at Acadia University. She loves teaching and encouraging people to learn computer science. While in her undergrad, she worked two co-op terms in the security industry. This past summer she studied web design and directing at Harvard University. Locally, she won the Best Overall Physical Sciences Project grades 7-12 two years in a row at the Annapolis Valley Regional Science Fair. She also represented Nova Scotia at the Canada Wide National Science Fair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian McKay</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ian-mckay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ian-mckay/</guid>
      <description>“Creative Technician”&amp;hellip;what the heck is that?
I see my role, primarily, as that of a possibilitist. I listen closely to your ideas, what you hope to create, the problem you are working and then share with you the possibilities technology may offer. My years of immersion in Maker culture, joyfully exploring new and unusual uses for the wonders of emerging and age-old tech, provide me with a deep pool of possible solutions to your creative problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy Lutes</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/jeremy-lutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/jeremy-lutes/</guid>
      <description>Jeremy Lutes is a Partner at Equilibrium Engineering. Jeremy has been successfully managing and operating businesses since 1998. Previous to Equilibrium, Jeremy was the Business Analyst for Internetworking Atlantic (IAI), a private Halifax based telecommunications company.
From a volunteer perspective, Jeremy was previously on the Board of Directors of the Halifax Pop Explosion for twelve years, and the Music Nova Scotia Board of Directors for three years. These positions illustrate a long-standing passion for the arts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Frost</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/john-frost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/john-frost/</guid>
      <description>John Frost is a Senior Manager, Satellite Products, at PrecisionHawk. John worked extensively in geophysical research and exploration before returning to university to complete studies in International Relations/Intercultural Studies. With broad national and international project exposure, he is a cross-cultural specialist in technology adaptation. Through the Aerhyve brand, the company focused on the analysis of UAV data with Machine Learning, providing actionable intelligence for agricultural and industrial applications. An entrepreneur and technophile, John is always pursuing opportunities which make a local-global impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Josh Smith</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/josh-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/josh-smith/</guid>
      <description>Front End Engineer at Chalk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justin Bezanson</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/justin-bezanson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/justin-bezanson/</guid>
      <description>Since 2000 I have continued to expand my knowledge and skills and worked hard to be the best developer I can be.
I enjoy meeting challenges and working hard to find creative and user friendly solutions.
My goal is to continually improve my development process, delivering higher quality and efficiency.
Specialties: PHP, ASP.NET MVC, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, CodeIgniter, Zend Framework, AJAX, Windows, Linux, MySQL, SQL Server, WordPress, ASP.NET
Justin, pictured here, is The Thing from the Fantastic Four.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keegan Francis</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/keegan-francis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/keegan-francis/</guid>
      <description>My name is Keegan Francis, i have been working with, interested in, and invested in cryptocurrencies and blockchain since 2014.
 Invested in bitcoin and dogecoin in 2014 Graduated with a degree in computer science in 2015 Built my first mining rig in 2017 Have given several lectures and presentations to Nova Scotia universities in 2017 and 2018 Attended an international blockchain conference in Shanghai, China, 2018 Co-founded Atlantic Blockchain Company Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keith Diehl</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/keith-diehl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/keith-diehl/</guid>
      <description>Keith got his first glimpse of HTML with NCSA&amp;rsquo;s Mosaic browser in 1994. A few “View Sources” later and he was hooked.
Soon after, he got his first web job as Webmaster for the Arizona Daily Wildcat. Over the years, Keith has worked for several newspapers and Fortune 500 companies including Coca Cola and Aflac insurance. He has been the Webmaster for North America&amp;rsquo;s premiere training provider CED Solutions for over 15 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laura Simpson</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson/</guid>
      <description>Lover of music and truth. Listen to the poets. Founder of The Syrup Factory, Make.Do.Camp. and Side Door.
Laura Simpson is a music industry professional, living with her family in Halifax, Nova Scotia. She founded The Syrup Factory, which began hosting house concerts 2011 and offering strategy and services to artists in 2015.
She has been an organizer in the arts scene since she was 14, going to all-ages shows and then eventually taking live music photography and freelance writing about shows and artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leanne Strathdee</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/leanne-strathdee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/leanne-strathdee/</guid>
      <description>Leanne Strathdee is the Manager of Innovation and Incubation for Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre  . In this role, she manages the Rural Innovation Centre – an incubator for start-up companies at Acadia University  , that are connected to the services and amenities that Acadia offers in research, data analytics, tidal energy or business - skills development. Additionally, she manages all the student entrepreneurship programming through the provincial sandbox, launchbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lori Shepherd</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/lori-shepherd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/lori-shepherd/</guid>
      <description>Lori builds games. Lori also builds teams from the ground up, ensuring the effectiveness of the team through collaboration.
Lori creates military based games, combining her security training, and creativity into realistic and engrossing experiences. Encompassing criminal elements, espionage, law enforcement, cyberwarfare, intelligence, and tactics.
Lori’s audience, in the security forum, have included police agencies, government, military and defense, legal professionals, technology sectors, consultants, and private investigators.
International law enforcement and security organizations have worked with her in understanding and preparing for virtual world culture and threats to games associated with crime in online gaming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maggie Neilson</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/maggie-neilson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/maggie-neilson/</guid>
      <description>Maggie Neilson is an Academic Librarian at Acadia University’s Vaughan Memorial Library. Her role primarily revolves around liaison responsibilities with the Jodrey School of Computer Science, the Ivan Curry School of Engineering, the Earth and Environmental Science Department, the Environmental and Sustainability Studies Programme, and the School of Kinesiology. In addition to the collection development services, instructional sessions and research assistance she provides to these disciplines, Maggie also has coordinating responsibilities in government documents, the library’s discovery layer, and geospatial and numeric data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Margaret Hopkins</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/margaret-hopkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/margaret-hopkins/</guid>
      <description>Margaret Hopkins is a third year math and music major at Acadia University with an interest in promoting mathematics and technology education for youth in the Annapolis Valley. She is a founding member and now coach of the Horton High Robats, an all-girls&#39; robotics team; coaches Wolfville School&amp;rsquo;s First Lego League team, Robo Lobo Wired; and volunteers with WISE Acadia and other organizations in the region to promote STEM education for all students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Davis</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-davis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-davis/</guid>
      <description>Founder / CEO at colovo and co-founder of The HUB Yarmouth  .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Richards</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-richards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-richards/</guid>
      <description>Mark has been working in the field of education for over 20 years. For the past four years Mark has been the AVRSB Consultant of Technology integration and Student Data. Prior to that, Mark spent 10 years teaching high school science/technology, was a high school vice principal and was project manager for the provincial PowerSchool implementation. Mark wrote the original Computer Programming 12 curriculum document for the province of Nova Scotia in the early 2000’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Hall</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matt-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matt-hall/</guid>
      <description>I make stuff happen at Agile*, an independent geoscience idea factory in Canada.
We build awesome knowledge engines for organizations (mostly wikis), and we hone our skills in subsurface science&amp;hellip; We have most recently been working on geothermal reservoir description. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked the Montney tight gas of Alberta and BC, frontier exploration in the Canadian Beaufort Sea, the Athabasca oil sands, the Norwegian North Sea. I also worked in software for several years, as an advocate of integrated volume visualization and interpretation and viz room pilot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Doucette</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matthew-doucette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matthew-doucette/</guid>
      <description>I am a video game developer (Xbox 360 &amp;amp; PC). Check out my video game company, Xona Games, and my first professional video game, Duality ZF, for more information. My only parter is my twin brother, Jason Doucette.
Here is the Duality ZF April 2009 trailer:
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max Caplan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/max-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/max-caplan/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, he was born. What happened after this is the interesting part. Relatively speaking. After his long and tedious early childhood, Max found himself being introduced to the fascinating world of technology. One of his earliest experiences was with the beginner programming environment known as Scratch. After a couple of years of making awesome scratch projects, Max moved on to explore more that tech had to offer. Through his School he found himself on a Lego Robotics team for a couple years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Caplan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-caplan/</guid>
      <description>Mike has been active as a web application developer and designer since the late 90s, working in the non-profit, university, retail, agricultural, and health care industries. He was a founding partner of HarvestHand  , a platform that services Community Shared Agriculture farms. Mike founded Refresh Annapolis Valley  , a new media professional association.
Mike is the Software Development Manager for the Labnet Dental Lab Systems  division of Henry Schein - a solutions company for health care professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Macmillan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-macmillan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-macmillan/</guid>
      <description>Michael is an SEO and marketing specialist, focusing on consultancy for software &amp;amp; service companies and specializing in troubleshooting. He built his first website in 1996 and was a working professional in the digital world by 1999. Having held various roles in the digital world, he transitioned to an SEO role in 2009. Since then he has held SEO roles in-house, as leadership for an agencies SEO team, and as an independent consultant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Downs</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mike-downs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mike-downs/</guid>
      <description>Mike has over eighteen years of Internet marketing strategy and product management experience helping create, shape, and launch technology products on the Web. Mike is very passionate about how human beings use computers. Focusing on usability and user experience for the last 10 years, Mike has helped retail giants like Macy&amp;rsquo;s and The Gap as well as government organizations like Tourism British Columbia and Service Nova Scotia deliver experiences that engage their audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mrugakshee Palwe</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mrugakshee-palwe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mrugakshee-palwe/</guid>
      <description>My name is Mrugakshee Palwe. I started investing my time in understanding the blockchain technology in mid-2018.
 Graduated with a degree in computer science in spring 2018 Received a scholarship for Consensys academy’s 2018 Developer Bootcamp in October 2018. Certificate of Proficiency from Ethereum Blockchain Developer Bootcamp - Feb 2019 Forked and customized the Bitshares, Graphene, and Peerplays blockchains Co-founded Atlantic Blockchain Company Inc. in November 2018  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nick Baskwill</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/nick-baskwill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/nick-baskwill/</guid>
      <description>Nick is a grade 5 teacher at Kingston Elementary school in Kingston, NS. He has been teaching for 10 years. Nick completed his B. Sc from Lyndon State College, his B. Ed from Acadia University, and his M. Ed from Mount Saint Vincent University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noah Tomkins</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/noah-tomkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/noah-tomkins/</guid>
      <description>Originally from Dartmouth, Nova Scotia, Noah Tompkins is a fourth-year Entrepreneurship &amp;amp; Innovation major at Acadia University. His passion for sustainability and social enterprise has lead Noah to working as the Marketing Coordinator for Just Us! Coffee Roasters, becoming a project manager and presenter for Enacts Acadia, and the President of Fair Trade Acadia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Richards</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/paul-richards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/paul-richards/</guid>
      <description>Paul Richards is innovacorp&amp;#39;s  regional manager for Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s Annapolis Valley and South Shore. In this role, Paul focuses on enabling knowledge-based companies to accelerate their growth and helping foster a dynamic high-growth entrepreneurial culture in the region.
Paul spent over 10 years working with the Acadia Centre for Social and Business Entrepreneurship (ACSBE) assisting businesses in rural Nova Scotia. In this role, Paul also worked to build the entrepreneurial capacity and infrastructure of several developing economies in Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philip Kerr</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/philip-kerr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/philip-kerr/</guid>
      <description>Philip is a Canadian lawyer, and Canadian patent and trademark agent with 29 years of experience. He is a partner in the Canadian patent firm of Kerr &amp;amp; Nadeau  (offices in Halifax and Ottawa).
Philip is also the president of PCTxs Inc., a firm that provides an online marketplace for selling/licensing patent application rights, particularly unexpired PCT national phase rights and unexpired Paris Convention patent application rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pierre Clouthier</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/pierre-clouthier/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/pierre-clouthier/</guid>
      <description>Co-founder, President, Progeny Genealogy Inc., specialising in computer graphics software for genealogy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raina Noel</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/raina-noel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/raina-noel/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sandy McFadden</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sandy-mcfadden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sandy-mcfadden/</guid>
      <description>Sandy started playing with and building things for the web in 1999. At some point along the way he started trying out different content management systems to help make things easier. After trying to write his own very basic one he settled on WordPress and has been using it to build web sites for years.
Now he works for Automattic helping people everyday to use their sites on WordPress.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sara Baxter</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sara-baxter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sara-baxter/</guid>
      <description>A fourth year Accounting major, Sara Baxter from Moncton, New Brunswick, exercises her entrepreneurial skillset through Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre as the Community Entrepreneurship Developer. Her desire to create change and have a positive impact on society has led her to become a Project Co-Manager for Enacts Acadia&amp;rsquo;s Project Regenerate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Ryan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sarah-ryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sarah-ryan/</guid>
      <description>A graduate of Mount Saint Vincent University, Sarah has worked in the science enrichment and education fields for over nine years. For the past three years, Sarah has been Program Director at Brilliant Labs Nova Scotia, a not-for-profit organization that supports students and educators with innovative ways to make learning fun and relevant by using tools, materials and technologies to solve everyday challenges. In this role, she is responsible for delivering programming to enhance digital literacy skills and support project-based learning initiatives for teachers, students, and community groups across Nova Scotia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott Olszowiec</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/scott-olszowiec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/scott-olszowiec/</guid>
      <description>Scott Olszowiec is creative partner that has been building solutions to communicate ideas and inspiration for over 17 years.
From digital content creation to educational technology, he is somewhere between what you might call &amp;ldquo;artsy&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;techie.&amp;rdquo;
He has worked in a variety of ways with expedition travellers, universities, NSCC and private career colleges, global finance, non-profits, indigenous economic development and education organizations in Canada.
Most recently, Scott has partnered with Ulnooweg to assist in the implementation of a bold new project that aims to transform science and digital education for Mi’kmaw children and youth living on reserves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terry Weatherbee</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/terry-wetherbee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/terry-wetherbee/</guid>
      <description>Terry Weatherbee is a Professor in the Manning School of Business at Acadia University, and has a number of different research areas of interest including the negative impacts of technology use in organizations and the historiography of management thought. His most current research focuses on the disruptive impact of Maker Technology and its opportunities for economic development and academic/economic partnership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cooper</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tim-cooper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tim-cooper/</guid>
      <description>Tim Cooper is part of Henry Schein&amp;rsquo;s Global Innovation Center as a Software Developer. He is a member of the small team located in Nova Scotia, Canada, that develops primarily web-based software. The team&amp;rsquo;s mandate is to explore and prototype innovative ways that technology can be applied to the world of dental and health care. As a hobby, Tim enjoys contributing to Free Software projects and answering Stack Overflow questions. He graduated from Acadia University with a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Avery</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/trevor-avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/trevor-avery/</guid>
      <description>Trevor Avery is a marine biologist (Ph.D.) and biostatistician (P.Stat.) with a variety of research interests. U. of Guelph was home for his undergraduate Honours, Acadia U. for an M.Sc. (under Mike Dadswell) and Memorial U. for his Ph.D. (with Joe Brown, r.i.p.); Currently he is back with Acadia as an Associate Professor cross appointed within the faculties of Biology and Mathematics &amp;amp; Statistics.
Technology and analysis techniques (statistics) play a significant role in most of his research projects, but not all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Farmer</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tyler-farmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tyler-farmer/</guid>
      <description>For the last year and a half, Tyler has lead Digital Nova Scotia’s projects and skill development programs across Nova Scotia. Through this role, Tyler has had the opportunity to connect with a wide variety of ICT &amp;amp; digital tech companies, professional service providers, community leaders, and government agencies which has enabled him to build an effective grassroots network with a birds-eye perspective of the economic challenges facing the province. Prior to diving into the rewarding work of economic development through Nova Scotia’s IT association, Tyler coordinated inspection, expediting, and project management services for many of Canada’s leading oil and gas companies in Alberta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia/</guid>
      <description>Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia (BA, MA) is the President &amp;amp; CEO of Digital Nova Scotia  . She’s a multilingual senior level executive with over 20 years of combined experience in the private, public &amp;amp; academic sectors. Her career spans five geographic regions: America (North), Africa (South), Middle East, Asia &amp;amp; Europe.
Ulrike thrives on challenges! With a proven track record in International Marketing, Business &amp;amp; Economic Development, Channel Management, Government/Stakeholder Relations, Board Governance, Fundraising, Organizational Growth &amp;amp; Public Speaking, she&amp;rsquo;s a true game-changer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wes Booth</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/wes-booth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/wes-booth/</guid>
      <description>Wes Booth literally grew up during the birth of social media. In 2006, he signed on Facebook for the first time and in 2013 he sent his first Snap. Wes started his first business when he was 14 and is now working on a project to better connect and support brands and creative talent in Nova Scotia through his social media community called We Are NS. Wes believes in Atlantic Canada 100% and is determined social media is a good place to start telling our stories.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
