<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Persons on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Persons on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Button</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a 15 year career with various businesses and economic development organizations, Andrew felt it was about time to move from being a ‘cheerleader’ and ‘curator’ of entrepreneurship to doing something that actually produced more entrepreneurs in rural communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​In 2014 he founded &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mashuplab.ca/&#34;&gt;Mashup Lab&lt;/a&gt;; a for-more-than-profit company that activates rural ideas.  That same year he launched a chapter of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.awesomesouthshore.ca/&#34;&gt;Awesome Foundation&lt;/a&gt; in his community. Andrew has since gone on to launch another social enterprise - &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3&#34;&gt;
    
        CO3
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, a fresh new coworking space for Freelancers, Entrepreneurs, and Independents located in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andrew&amp;rsquo;s work with over 1,000 Entrepreneurs located in rural has convinced him that great ideas can come from anywhere. His passion and energy is focused on one thing: unleashing entrepreneurial potential in rural communities that has yet to be inspired into action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Andrew&amp;rsquo;s banner image is a Captain Canuck inspired rendition of artwork blatantly ripped off the Mashup Lab website.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catherine Vardy</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/catherine-vardy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/catherine-vardy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Catherine Vardy joined the &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office&#34;&gt;
    
        Canadian Intellectual Property Office
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 (CIPO) in 2015. As a Business Development Officer for the Atlantic Region, Catherine enjoys working with people to identify and highlight the value of IP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Network Liaison and Program Manager at Springboard Atlantic, Catherine worked closely with innovative SMEs, universities and colleges. Catherine also worked in Atlantic Canada as a Research and Innovation Development Officer with the Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council (NSERC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When she’s not travelling, Catherine usually hangs out at her office at &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/innovacorp&#34;&gt;
    
        Innovacorp
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, in Halifax, Nova Scotia.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Greene</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/charlie-greene/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/charlie-greene/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Charlie is a senior software developer at The REDspace. He is alumni from &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/colibri-software&#34;&gt;
    
        Colibri Software
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 where he worked for two years, ever since graduating from Acadia University with a Honors degree in Computer Science with Co-Op option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlie&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by the work of Ruby the painting elephant.  True story.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Jordan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/chris-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/chris-jordan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chris is a software developer with 16+ years experience with Henry Schein.  Not to be pigeonholed, he&amp;rsquo;s got his hand in all sorts of things: Top tier support for an installation base spanning 2000+ customers, Brand development, Application planning and development, Database design, Documentation, Testing, Training, Training material development: web, print and video, Customer support, Installer creation, Phone system programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chris&amp;rsquo; profile pic is a mashup of a picture of his swiped from Facebook and R2D2.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Garrett</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/elizabeth-garrett/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/elizabeth-garrett/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Just like becoming an expert in wine - you learn by drinking it, the best you can afford - you learn great food by finding the best there is, whether simply or luxurious. Then you savor it, analyze it, discuss it with your companions, and you compare it with other experiences&amp;rdquo; - Julia Child, &lt;em&gt;Mastering the Art of French Cooking&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frances Schagen</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/frances-schagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/frances-schagen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Frances is a small business innovator. She geeks out over business strategy, business models and building entrepreneurial ecosystems. She believe that&amp;rsquo;s the kind of thinking we need to save the world. Frances helps create places where entrepreneurship can thrive within our business and within our community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business innovation is essential for us to solve our biggest issues and to succeed in the world today. Business theory was developed for large business and small business is not a little big business. Frances has been on this quest for decades, talking to 1000&amp;rsquo;s of business owners and reading 1000&amp;rsquo;s of books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your Effortless Business is her book where she outlines how you can make your business work better and be more entrepreneurial Hint:you don&amp;rsquo;t need an MBA to succeed in small business, in fact it will get in the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frances&amp;rsquo; profile picture was created by software trained in the fine art of pastels.  Header image a pic of Jacob Epstein&amp;rsquo;s sculpture &lt;em&gt;The Rush of Green or The Bowater House Group&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geoff Crouse</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Geoff has more than 17 years of combined Software Engineering and Information Technology Consulting experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technical Sales Engineer, specializing in medium to large scale Drupal CMS projects including new development, site audits and analysis, and expert support services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Account Management, coordinating customer projects with engineering and support teams from initial conception to final delivery, and continued support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Geoff&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove.  Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove pic care of Wikipedia.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian McKay</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ian-mckay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ian-mckay/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“Creative Technician”&amp;hellip;what the heck is that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see my role, primarily, as that of a possibilitist. I listen closely to your ideas, what you hope to create, the problem you are working and then share with you the possibilities technology may offer. My years of immersion in Maker culture, joyfully exploring new and unusual uses for the wonders of emerging and age-old tech, provide me with a deep pool of possible solutions to your creative problems. While I am happy to help suggest solutions and inform you of the possibilities and challenges, I always keep in mind that the piece is YOUR work and will strive to help YOUR vision come to fruition. In those cases where a more collaborative model is what you are seeking, I would love to work with you to make our ideas a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ian&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://deepdreamgenerator.com/ddream/56b79f0b2d&#34;&gt;banner image&lt;/a&gt; is a photo of his home at Scots Bay&amp;hellip; reinterpreted by a machine influenced by the work of &lt;a href=&#34;http://hollycarr.weebly.com/&#34;&gt;Holly Carr&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justin Bezanson</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/justin-bezanson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/justin-bezanson/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since 2000 I have continued to expand my knowledge and skills and worked hard to be the best developer I can be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I enjoy meeting challenges and working hard to find creative and user friendly solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My goal is to continually improve my development process, delivering higher quality and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specialties: PHP, ASP.NET MVC, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, CodeIgniter, Zend Framework, AJAX, Windows, Linux, MySQL, SQL Server, WordPress, ASP.NET&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Justin, pictured here, &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; The Thing from the Fantastic Four.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keith Diehl</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/keith-diehl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/keith-diehl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Keith got his first glimpse of HTML with NCSA&amp;rsquo;s Mosaic browser in 1994.  A few “View Sources” later and he was hooked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon after, he got his first web job as Webmaster for the Arizona Daily Wildcat.  Over the years, Keith has worked for several newspapers and Fortune 500 companies including Coca Cola and Aflac insurance.  He has been the Webmaster for North America&amp;rsquo;s premiere training provider CED Solutions for over 15 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keith has been fortunate to be able to combine the connectivity of the web with his love of travel.   During his travels, he met a lovely Canadian who convinced him to move to Canada and get married.  He lives in Nova Scotia with his wife and young son.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laura Churchill Duke</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-churchill-duke/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-churchill-duke/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Laura is a freelance Communications Specialist and Writer.  She is a stay-at-home mom who does not stay at home! She works various contracts while working from home. Her primary job is running the website &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/valley-family-fun&#34;&gt;
    
        Valley Family Fun
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 which is a resource for families living in the Valley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is very involved with her community and participates in many volunteer activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Laura&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by software inspired by her painting inspired by Monet.  The cover pic was created by the same software re-interpreting her painting with Monet&amp;rsquo;s Starry Night as a reference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Davis</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-davis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-davis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Founder / CEO at &lt;a href=&#34;http://colovo.com/&#34;&gt;colovo&lt;/a&gt; and co-founder of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-yarmouth&#34;&gt;
    
        The HUB Yarmouth
    
&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Hall</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matt-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matt-hall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I make stuff happen at Agile*, an independent geoscience idea factory in Canada.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We build awesome knowledge engines for organizations (mostly wikis), and we hone our skills in subsurface science&amp;hellip; We have most recently been working on geothermal reservoir description. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked the Montney tight gas of Alberta and BC, frontier exploration in the Canadian Beaufort Sea, the Athabasca oil sands, the Norwegian North Sea. I also worked in software for several years, as an advocate of integrated volume visualization and interpretation and viz room pilot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since 2001 I&amp;rsquo;ve been a registered professional Geologist and professional Geophysicist in Alberta. I review technical papers for SEG&amp;rsquo;s journal Geophysics. I sometimes teach university courses. With my Agile colleague, I write a blog at agilegeoscience.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specialties: Seismic interpretation and analysis, sedimentology, sequence stratigraphy, geoscience software, integrated reservoir description, knowledge sharing, writing&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Doucette</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matthew-doucette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matthew-doucette/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a video game developer (Xbox 360 &amp;amp; PC). Check out my video game company, &lt;a href=&#34;http://xona.com/&#34;&gt;Xona Games&lt;/a&gt;, and my first professional video game, &lt;a href=&#34;http://dualityzf.com/&#34;&gt;Duality ZF&lt;/a&gt;, for more information. My only parter is my twin brother, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jasondoucette.com/&#34;&gt;Jason Doucette&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the Duality ZF April 2009 trailer:&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/7TkG6J2CWvU&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Caplan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-caplan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mike has been active as a web application developer and web designer for 16 years, working in the non-profit, university, retail, agricultural, and dental industries. He is a founding partner of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/harvesthand&#34;&gt;
    
        HarvestHand
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, a platform that services Community Shared Agriculture farms. More recently, Mike founded &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley&#34;&gt;
    
        Refresh Annapolis Valley
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, a new media professional association to help grow the Valley&amp;rsquo;s technology industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike is the Software Development Manager for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems&#34;&gt;
    
        Labnet Dental Lab Systems
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 division of Henry Schein - a Fortune 300 company with a small footprint here in Wolfville.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>