<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thinking About Design - Creative Strategies</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/thinking-about-design-creative-strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/thinking-about-design-creative-strategies/</guid>
      <description>Design Thinking is being used by large innovative companies to create exceptional products and experiences (think Google Glass, AirBnB, your arrival experience with major airlines, and, of course, toilet paper). It can also be applied at much smaller scales - in education, to find solutions for sustainability challenges, and of course in tech companies of any size. Join Anne Stieger for an introduction to this powerful toolbox, process and mindset for user-centered design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anne Stieger</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anne-stieger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anne-stieger/</guid>
      <description>Anne is a process geek, facilitator and trainer with a knack for creative, collaborative processes and deep play. She is trained and experienced in a diverse range of facilitation practices including the Art of Hosting, Design Thinking, Dynamic Governance and Appreciative Inquiry. Anne was first introduced to Design Thinking when she was a teacher at Duisburg-Essen University in Germany through a project that connects High School &amp;amp; University students to solve local sustainability challenges through Design Thinking, and she has been hooked ever since by the power of the approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoist Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/hoist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/hoist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hoist Annapolis Valley is a tech club for teens interested in coding, design and entrepreneurship. If you’re age 12 to 19 and have an interest in startups or coding, then come check it out! Everyone is welcome, and it’s free!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Meet up with Hoist members once per month at Acadia University&amp;rsquo;s Rural Innovation Centre &amp;ndash; like attending an tech + entrepreneurship class at university.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labs</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/labs/</guid>
      <description>The Refresh Annapolis Valley Labs is a playground where adventurous builders come to create. Labs initiatives are community driven digital technology projects that tend to be entrepreneurial in nature. In the lab, Refreshers work on building and applying their skills all while pursuing the objectives of their projects.&#xA;Refresh Annapolis Valley Labs is hosted at the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre Rural Innovation Centre. We meet on Saturdays from 12:30 to 3:30 starting January 26.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Meetups</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/meetups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/meetups/</guid>
      <description>Our monthly Refresh meetup is where the Annapolis Valley community of designers, developers and innovators come hang out. Those interested in the creative, technical, and professional culture of digital technology endeavours in the Annapolis Valley meet and talk about all things design, technology, and entrepreneurship.&#xA;Refresh meets the second Tuesday evening of each month in the Wolfville area. These are casual affairs with short, member-interest talks followed by an opportunity to mingle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max Caplan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/max-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/max-caplan/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Max! I&amp;rsquo;m a full stack web developer and designer with over 3 years of freelance experience and a lifetime of passion for building things!&#xA;I really enjoy learning new things and problem solving as a developer. As a designer, I love creating unique and engaging experiences. I am a very detail oriented person who puts a lot of emphasis into how people interact with the things I make.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
