<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Acadia University on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/acadia-university/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Acadia University on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/acadia-university/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Where Did All The Women Go?  Retaining Women in Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/where-did-all-the-women-go-retaining-women-in-computer-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/where-did-all-the-women-go-retaining-women-in-computer-science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the last 30 years, the number of women entering Computer Science university programs has dropped from 50% to around 10%. Once in the program, women have a higher drop out rate than men.  And women graduating with Computer Science degrees often leave the field and pursue alternate careers. &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-randy-newman&#34;&gt;Dr Randy Newman&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel&#34;&gt;Cindy Trudel&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; have been actively researching this phenomenon over the last few years. In this Refresh Annapolis Valley talk, Randy and Cindy will discuss the problem, the programs that Acadia has in place, and the needs for the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIY Usability Lab: Testing With Little Or No Budget</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/diy-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/diy-usability/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Usability testing uncovers problem areas with your website. But not many do it, or do too little because of perceived complexity and cost. When you have limited time and budget, build your own usability lab and get results. A low-cost usability lab will be demonstrated using readily available hardware and software and results from testing our Acadia University library website will be shared.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cindy Trudel</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cindy Trudel is an Instructor in Acadia University&amp;rsquo;s Departments of Computer Science, Business and Mathematics. Her primary research interest is in developing retention programs for students who have self-selected Computer Science as an area of study.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr Randy Newman</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-randy-newman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-randy-newman/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Newman is a Cognitive Neuroscientist whose primary research interest is in understanding the brain mechanisms responsible for reading and speech processes using event-related potentials and eye tracking techniques. Current research is examining the impact of a word&amp;rsquo;s spelling on how quickly we recognize spoken words.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A secondary area of interest is in understanding factors responsible for the gender gap that persists in some areas of science, notably computer science and engineering. Current research is examining the impact of girls only science-based activities (e.g., camps) on girls&amp;rsquo; career aspirations in science, as well as on their self-efficacy and their sense of belonging in science-based disciplines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maggie Neilson</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/maggie-neilson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/maggie-neilson/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Maggie Neilson is an Academic Librarian at Acadia University’s Vaughan Memorial Library. Her role primarily revolves around liaison responsibilities with the Jodrey School of Computer Science, the Ivan Curry School of Engineering, the Earth and Environmental Science Department, the Environmental and Sustainability Studies Programme, and the School of Kinesiology. In addition to the collection development services, instructional sessions and research assistance she provides to these disciplines, Maggie also has coordinating responsibilities in government documents, the library’s discovery layer, and geospatial and numeric data.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Margaret Hopkins</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/margaret-hopkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/margaret-hopkins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Margaret Hopkins is a third year math and music major at Acadia University with an interest in promoting mathematics and technology education for youth in the Annapolis Valley. She is a founding member and now coach of the Horton High Robats, an all-girls&amp;rsquo; robotics team; coaches Wolfville School&amp;rsquo;s First Lego League team, Robo Lobo Wired; and volunteers with WISE Acadia and other organizations in the region to promote STEM education for all students. She also plays the trumpet and carries out interdisciplinary research that combines mathematics and music.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scott Olszowiec</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/scott-olszowiec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/scott-olszowiec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Scott Olszowiec is creative partner that has been building solutions to communicate ideas and inspiration for over 17 years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From digital content creation to educational technology, he is somewhere between what you might call &amp;ldquo;artsy&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;techie.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He has worked in a variety of ways with expedition travellers, universities, NSCC and private career colleges, global finance, non-profits, indigenous economic development and education organizations in Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most recently, Scott has partnered with Ulnooweg to assist in the implementation of a bold new project that aims to transform science and digital education for Mi’kmaw children and youth living on reserves.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry Weatherbee</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/terry-wetherbee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/terry-wetherbee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Terry Weatherbee is a Professor in the Manning School of Business at Acadia University, and has a number of different research areas of interest including the negative impacts of technology use in organizations and the historiography of management thought. His most current research focuses on the disruptive impact of Maker Technology and its opportunities for economic development and academic/economic partnership.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEAM Powered! Maker Space / FabLab @AcadiaU</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/steam-powered-maker-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/steam-powered-maker-space/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The recent and explosive growth in maker-culture combined with the emergence of 3D Printing in Fabrication Laboratories (or “FabLabs”) presents an opportunity for the province to prepare for the future by investing in economic and cultural change in rural Nova Scotia. Acting in concert with the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre and the Centre for Rural Innovation, Acadia’s new STEAM Space is working toward the creation of a Maker Space/FabLab on the Acadia University campus. It will be based on the combination of Acadia’s knowledge in Science and Technology with expertise in business for the purposes of developing an Entrepreneurial culture of innovation for Artisanal Making. It is designed to turn disruption into opportunity for the local and regional community in which Acadia is embedded. David and Terry will talk about the potential of maker spaces, as well as provide some 3D printing show and tell.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
