<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Organizations on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Organizations on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Computer Science Society</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-computer-science-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-computer-science-society/</guid>
      <description>The Acadia Computer Science Society welcomes not only Computer Science students but all students enrolled at Acadia University. We endeavour to be an advocate for students with interests in computer science and technology. We plan events like banquets, CaCHe, LAN parties, and seminars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</guid>
      <description>AEC has been developing and delivering workshops for business professionals, entrepreneurs, and not-for-profits for over 25 years. AEC continues to innovate and develop new and relevant programs for today’s business professional.&#xA;Rural Innovation Centre The Rural Innovation Centre (RIC) supports entrepreneurs and businesses in the Annapolis Valley and on the South Shore by providing training, advisory and consulting services to small businesses, government and not-for-profit organizations. The Rural Innovation Centre is an incubator for start up companies to access working space and support, networking events, mentors and connect to Acadia faculty and facilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Institute for Data Analytics</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-institute-for-data-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-institute-for-data-analytics/</guid>
      <description>Rural Canada feeds our nation literally, economically, and environmentally. It provides the food, fiber, minerals, water and other bio-resources and natural resources on which our country depends and the arteries of transportation by which they are delivered. Digital technologies and data analytics can help us shape how we work with these resources and their impact on our local communities and our planet.&#xA;Mission To advance knowledge in data analytics through collaborative and interdisciplinary research, education and outreach and to foster the ethical application and commercialization of data analytic solutions to challenges facing industry, government and society in rural Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Robotics Program</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</guid>
      <description>The Robot Programming Competition mission is to increase interest in building digital technology and computer science by engaging Nova Scotia students in annual robotics programming competitions and related activities that feature problem solving and teamwork.&#xA;The Acadia Robotics Program, through the Jodrey School of Computer Science, depends heavily on financial support from external organizations and the committed volunteers who annually contribute to the season from late August through to mid-June. We have a junior program, FIRST® LEGO® League, and a senior program, Robofest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acadia School of Business</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-school-of-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-school-of-business/</guid>
      <description>Acadia BBA students majoring in Entrepreneurship and Innovation are given the tools needed to succeed as entrepreneurs as well as to manage entrepreneurship for continuous innovation, sustainable competitive advantage and growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acadia University</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>Far above the dykes of Fundy&#xA;And its basin blue&#xA;Stands our noble alma mater&#xA;Glorious to view&#xA;Lift the chorus&#xA;Speed it onward&#xA;Sing it loud and free&#xA;Hail to thee our alma mater&#xA;Acadia, hail to thee&#xA;Far above the busy highway&#xA;And the sleepy town&#xA;Raised against the arch of heaven&#xA;Looks she proudly down</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Women in Technology Society</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-women-in-technology-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-women-in-technology-society/</guid>
      <description>We are a group of driven people dedicated toward the goal of supporting women in achieving success and promoting an inclusive feeling in STEM at Acadia.&#xA;Pictured above are 2 of the 6 women who where the first and primary programmers of the ENIAC, the world&amp;rsquo;s first digital computer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACENET</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acenet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acenet/</guid>
      <description>Advanced computing - computing beyond the capabilities of a traditional laptop - can remove years from innovation timelines. Use it to create complex models, develop and test algorithms, run large-scale simulations, and test scalability. ACENET provides access to advanced computing infrastructure through your desktop, along with ongoing support, expertise and training. If your computing needs are outgrowing your laptop, you&amp;rsquo;re having difficulty using a commercial cloud platform, or you&amp;rsquo;re just not ready to purchase expensive hardware and software, call us!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annapolis Cider Company</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-cider-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-cider-company/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re all about local. Our apples are grown in nearby orchards, pressed into juice just down the road, and fermented into cider at our cidery in downtown Wolfville. Come for a tour, enjoy a tasting and tap into the valley.&#xA;The Annapolis Valley is who we are, it’s where we live and we couldn’t be more proud to call it home.&#xA;Annapolis Cider Company is a supporter of Refresh Annapolis Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-valley-chamber-of-commerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-valley-chamber-of-commerce/</guid>
      <description>Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce is a strong united voice for business and works to ensure that business thrives in the Annapolis Valley.&#xA;AVCC is a not-for-profit organization that provides member businesses with access to a variety of services such as group insurance, professional development and networking opportunities. AVCC celebrates and promotes the accomplishments of business people and their contribution to the valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annapolis Valley STEAMspace</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-valley-steamspace/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-valley-steamspace/</guid>
      <description>A place for Annapolis Valley Makers, inventors, artists, entrepreneurs, tinkerers and the like to meet, share ideas and work towards establishing the proposed Acadia University STEAMspace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Blockchain Company</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/atlantic-blockchain-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/atlantic-blockchain-company/</guid>
      <description>We are the Atlantic Blockchain Company Atlantic Blockchain Company Inc. is an education based company operating out of Halifax, Nova Scotia, in Atlantic Canada.&#xA;Who do we help? We consult with businesses of all sizes to determine the possible adoption of blockchain technology into their existing business infrastructure.&#xA;We deliver educational seminars to universities and private venues to give the common individual the tools and definitions they need to make sense of the “crypto phenomenon” that is sweeping the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVCC Young Business Leaders</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/young-business-leaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/young-business-leaders/</guid>
      <description>Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce Young Business Leaders is a new committee that is exploring ways to connect to established business leaders for advice and mentorship. The AVCC Young Business Leaders Committee will recognize, encourage and engage future business leaders. The Young Business Leaders meet the last Tuesday of each month at noon at Gates Insurance, New Minas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Intellectual Property Office </title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office/</guid>
      <description>The Canadian Intellectual Property Office (CIPO), a Special Operating Agency (SOA) associated with Innovation, Science and Economic Development Canada, is responsible for the administration and processing of the greater part of intellectual property in Canada. CIPO&amp;rsquo;s areas of activity include:&#xA;Patents cover new inventions (process, machine, manufacture, composition of matter), or any new and useful improvement of an existing invention;&#xA;A trademark is a word (or words), a design, or a combination of these, used to identify the goods or services of one person or organization and to distinguish these goods or services from those of others in the marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canopy Creative</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canopy-creative/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canopy-creative/</guid>
      <description>We are a team of marketing consultants that work with small businesses to plan and strategize for marketing growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CO3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3/</guid>
      <description>CO3 is a fresh bew co-working space for freelancers, entrepreneurs and independents.&#xA;CO3 Is a concept created by ​Andrew Button , a social entrepreneur based in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;The mission is to create a space that further cultivates rural Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s freelance economy.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Through the success of his own company Mashup Lab and other social ventures ​he&amp;rsquo;s discovered a lot of hidden talent in the Maritimes which he feels needs more room to grow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colibri Software</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/colibri-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/colibri-software/</guid>
      <description>Colibri Software builds awesome software. We work with our clients to understand their needs and then produce a simple and effective solution to their problems. Our focus is on making a product easy to use, from websites to mobile apps, we like it when we hear “this is easy”.&#xA;We have a special affinity for mapping projects and have send rugged phone apps as far as Nunavut to help collect data for the hunting community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Good Solutions</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/common-good-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/common-good-solutions/</guid>
      <description>Common Good Solutions (CGS) is a company focused on growing the social enterprise movement in Nova Scotia, Canada, and beyond. CGS operates a social enterprise incubator aimed at launching and supporting over 100 social businesses by 2019, and offers a full range of social enterprise consulting, mentoring and training services. Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s first Community Interest Company, CGS devotes 60% of all profits toward its social mission of growing the social enterprise sector in Nova Scotia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nova Scotia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/digital-nova-scotia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/digital-nova-scotia/</guid>
      <description>Engaging both members and stakeholders in the region, Digital Nova Scotia provides advocacy, multi-sectoral industry intelligence, facilitates connections between industry and talent, and delivers high-level programming to ensure Nova Scotia’s $1.5 billion digital industry (which boasts an additional $1 billion in spin-offs) continues to flourish.&#xA;IT starts here. IT stays here. IT grows here. As the industry association for the fastest growing sector in the province with the highest number of ICT graduates per capita in Canada, Digital Nova Scotia encourages our tech talent and growing ecosystem of digital businesses to start here, stay here, and grow here!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enactus Acadia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/enactus-acadia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/enactus-acadia/</guid>
      <description>Enactus Acadia is a small chapter of a global organization that unites students with academic and business leaders. We implement various projects in the community that help improve the quality of life and standard of living for those in need. Enactus Acadia currently has multiple projects underway, which fit into categories such as eco-living, youth empowerment, financial literacy, and entrepreneurship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusion Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/fusion-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/fusion-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>Fusion AV is a non-profit, community engagement organization that’s mission to engage with young professionals in the Annapolis Valley. We aim to give them opportunities to connect and build their personal and professional network to ensure the long term success of this great place we all call home. Thus ENGAGE CONNECT SUCCEED</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HarvestHand</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/harvesthand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/harvesthand/</guid>
      <description>HarvestHand is a community platform dedicated to strengthening regional food systems. We&amp;rsquo;re passionate about supporting farms with CSA&amp;rsquo;s to become more profitable using HarvestHand CSA Software, helping communities eat better through the HarvestHand Community, creating good jobs in rural communities, and building new media solutions that make sharing the harvest easier.&#xA;Our vision is to create new media solutions that strengthen regional food systems&amp;rsquo; ability to succeed in value oriented approaches to production, distribution, consumption and community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUB Kentville</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville/</guid>
      <description>Get Inspired, Get Connected, Get involved. HUB spaces provide an inspirational home to members and are a focal point for change within the local communities.&#xA;What is the Hub? The HUB is about the power of innovation through collaboration.&#xA;We believe there is no shortage of good ideas to solve the issues of our time. But there is an acute lack of collaboration and support structures to help make them happen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i-Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/i-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/i-valley/</guid>
      <description>i-Valley is a not-for-profit collaboration of Mayors, Wardens, business leaders, civic planners and academia, dedicated to facilitating the transformation of the Annapolis Valley to a Smart Region. The goal of “Smart Annapolis Valley” is to drive efficiencies is such vital areas as energy, healthcare, business, and social engagement. Smart Communities are those which use digital tools and services to achieve the higher employment, better income, more sustainable environment and better education that are universal traits of such communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>innovacorp</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/innovacorp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/innovacorp/</guid>
      <description>Innovacorp is Nova Scotia’s early stage venture capital organization. We work to find, fund and foster innovative Nova Scotia start-ups that strive to change the world. Early stage investment is at the core of our business model. We also give entrepreneurs access to world-class incubation facilities, expert advice and other support to help them accelerate their companies.&#xA;Target industries include clean technology, information technology, life sciences and ocean technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jodrey School of Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>The Jodrey School of Computer Science prepares students for today&amp;rsquo;s ever changing world of technology in a unique, fully mobile computing environment. Students develop a thorough understanding of computer systems software, modern software design methods and computer systems software.&#xA;Students in all degree programs complete a self-directed project during the course of their studies. This provides students with the opportunity to work closely with professors and to apply knowledge acquired through experiment and real-life application.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kerr &amp; Nadeau</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/kerr--nadeau/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/kerr--nadeau/</guid>
      <description>At Kerr &amp;amp; Nadeau our job is to de-mystify and to simplify the rules for you, to offer you sound professional advice and superior legal services that will enable you, whether you are an inventor, an entrepreneur or a corporate executive, to execute your business plan, to protect your legal rights and to realize your strategic objectives while mitigating risk and ensuring compliance. Risk is the bane and Achilles heel of most business enterprises, and the single greatest obstacle to achieving your mission critical goals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labnet Dental Lab Systems</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems/</guid>
      <description>Labnet Dental Lab Systems offers the Dental Lab industry&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive and powerful management systems with solutions suited for labs of all sizes and budgets. Whether your lab is a thriving multi-site corporation or a one-technician miracle lab, we have a perfect fit for you.&#xA;As a Henry Schein company, you can depend on Labnet Dental Lab Systems for stability and providing your dentists with the latest technological advancements. When you are operating within tight deadlines, the last thing you should worry about is your software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launchbox</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/launchbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/launchbox/</guid>
      <description>Launchbox is the centre for student entrepreneurs, located on the 4th floor of Patterson Hall at Acadia University. We support students in their entrepreneurial pursuits by providing free programming, networking, access to mentors, and other entrepreneurs, working space and competitions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mashup Lab</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/mashup-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/mashup-lab/</guid>
      <description>Mashup Lab is a for-more-than-profit company that works with people to figure out if there is a great business to be built around their great ideas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morton Horticultural Associates</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/morton-horticultural-associates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/morton-horticultural-associates/</guid>
      <description>Morton Horticultural Associates was established in 1982 to provide specialized consulting, advisory and coaching services to clients in the horticulture, agriculture and the agri-food industry. The company focus is on helping agriculture businesses and organizations chart a clear path to the future and to develop the business management skills that will get them there. The areas of expertise include industry analysis, new value-added product development and commercialization, direct marketing, agritourism, business development, strategic and business planning and market innovation strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nexus Robotics</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nexus-robotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nexus-robotics/</guid>
      <description>Nexus Robotics is a Nova Scotian technology startup, developing autonomous robotic solutions for Agriculture using machine learning. Nexus provides farmers with a reliable and cost-effective way to produce crops. The Nexus Robotics team created an autonomous machine called R2-Weed2, which uses a camera system to differentiate between weeds and crops. The machine will be capable of cutting and spraying weeds, as well as able to fertilize crops and collect data about the crop and growing conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nova Scotia Community College</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nscc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nscc/</guid>
      <description>The School of IT &amp;amp; Creative Industries offers many dynamic programs that prepare you for a range of IT and creative careers.&#xA;Our instructors are professionals who remain current in their fields of expertise. They’re ready to teach you the latest industry techniques so you’ll graduate with the creativity and know-how to excel in the workforce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nova Scotia Works</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nova-scotia-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nova-scotia-works/</guid>
      <description>Nova Scotia Works employment services centres help Nova Scotians understand, prepare for, and fill the needs of the province’s job market. Nova Scotia Works also helps businesses recruit, manage and develop the talent they need to be more productive here at home and around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Office of Industry &amp; Community Engagement - Acadia University</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/office-of-industry--community-engagement---acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/office-of-industry--community-engagement---acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>Acadia’s Office of Industry &amp;amp; Community Engagement (ICE), identifies and connects Acadia’s researchers with industry, government and community groups interested in research, commercialization, outreach and entrepreneurship activities. As a member of Springboard Atlantic, ICE works with other universities in Atlantic Canada, as well as incubators and accelerators to ensure Acadia is making a strong contribution to the development and prosperity of our local and regional communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PrecisionHawk</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/precisionhawk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/precisionhawk/</guid>
      <description>PrecisionHawk is the leading provider of aerial data and safety platforms for drones. The Lancaster is PrecisionHawk’s fixed-wing, autonomous drone built to collect the highest quality terrestrial data using a host of integrated sensors including visual, thermal, LiDAR, multispectral and hyperspectral. PrecisionHawk houses three divisions that support its mission: DataMapper aerial mapping and analysis software, TerraServer satellite imagery and LATAS (Low Altitude Traffic and Airspace Safety).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progeny Genealogy</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/progeny-genealogy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/progeny-genealogy/</guid>
      <description>Progeny Genealogy is the leading developer of family tree software and other useful, easy-to-use genealogy research resources, including Charting Companion™, Genelines™ and Map My Family Tree™. More than pretty charts, our genealogy software programs are also powerful research tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R-bar</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/r-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/r-bar/</guid>
      <description>R-bar is Acadia University&amp;rsquo;s scientific programming study group. They cover everything R: a programming language and software environment for statistical computing and graphics.&#xA;WHAT WE DO Skill Sharing: Share your favorite coding skills and tools with your friends and colleagues in friendly, no-pressure work-alongs.&#xA;Co-Working: Get together to work on your coding projects, help each other out and share your work.&#xA;Community Building: Meet new people in your field, organization or community - and find out what we can do when we work together.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>Refresh is a community of designers, developers and innovators working to refresh the creative, technical, and professional culture of digital technology endeavours in the Annapolis Valley while promoting design, technology, and entrepreneurship.&#xA;Refresh Annapolis Valley was founded to create a cultural and educational space for our regional digital technology professionals, both current and future, to grow their skills and build regional synergies.&#xA;We believe deeply in the digital economy as a component of a strong diversified Nova Scotian economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScotiaCom</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/scotiacom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/scotiacom/</guid>
      <description>ScotiaCom (aka Scotia Computer Resources Inc.) is a small, independent business located in the Annapolis Valley, Nova Scotia. What started as an educational software development company has become a leader in the development and deployment of services that allow organizations, groups, individuals and small businesses to take full advantage of the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shift! Mobile Interactive</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/shift-mobile-interactive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/shift-mobile-interactive/</guid>
      <description>Digital media technology changes weekly. We help you understand digital marketing and how to use it to grow your business.&#xA;Organizations typically approach us because they are:&#xA;Feeling overwhelmed by all the digital marketing options Sick of getting “marketing tactics,” without effective and efficient methods to implement them On the “marketing hamster wheel” spending too much time and or ad money on digital media channels and they want better results Looking to rebrand or launch a brand Looking to launch a website Getting people to their website, but people aren’t converting or purchasing Needing a marketing planning template plan, implement, measure, and adjust as things change Any of these sound familiar?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Side Door</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/side-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/side-door/</guid>
      <description>Platform matching artists with spaces to create shows anytime, anywhere.&#xA;Side Door is a curated digital booking and ticketing platform used to facilitate booking and ticketing micro-performances in homes and other alternative venues in Canada and around the world. As a website and future mobile app, this technology-based company is innovating the traditional touring model for performers, live performances, and fan experiences.&#xA;Artists and Hosts sign up for free online through the Side Door website by creating profiles and answering questions about their preferences for performing or presenting a show in a house or alternative space (think bookstores, warehouses, parks, libraries, community centres, etc).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spark West Network</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/spark-west-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/spark-west-network/</guid>
      <description>We believe that rural Nova Scotia is a great place to be an entrepreneur. However, there is much need for improvement. There are gaps in our Western Nova rural ecosystem that we wish to tackle:&#xA;Unified Voice There is no unifying voice that pulls together the diverse organizations, events, and opportunities present in the Annapolis Valley, and sister municipalities. As individuals interested in what this community offers to entrepreneurs and creative professionals, it can be challenging to keep on top of what is going on of interest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The HUB South Shore</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-south-shore/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-south-shore/</guid>
      <description>The HUB South Shore is a coworking space that connects progressive businesses and people together so innovation and enterprise can thrive. We enjoy the freedom to run our own lives and depend on the motivation, productivity, and creativity that comes from working with others.&#xA;Our vision is for a self-reliant rural economy rooted in the collaboration of local entrepreneurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The HUB Yarmouth</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-yarmouth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-yarmouth/</guid>
      <description>Creative shared space The Hub is a co-working space for creative and social entrepreneurs in Yarmouth, Nova Scotia, Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Valley Regional Enterprise Network</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/valley-regional-enterprise-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/valley-regional-enterprise-network/</guid>
      <description>The Valley Regional Enterprise Network (Valley REN) was incorporated in March 2014 under the Municipal Government Act. The partnership comprises the Glooscap First Nation; Municipality of the County of Kings; Municipality of the District of West Hants; and the Towns of Berwick, Kentville, Middleton, Windsor and Wolfville. It is led by a volunteer Board of Directors, drawn mostly from the private sector and bringing to the table a wealth of experience in business and economic leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valley Family Fun</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/valley-family-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/valley-family-fun/</guid>
      <description>People who are new to the area (and some who are not) often ask Laura Churchill Duke what they can do with their families in the Valley.&#xA;This made her realize that there isn’t one central place to look for information. Valley Family Fun is a compilation of what she&amp;rsquo;s discovered! Follow VFF on their Facebook group too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Are NS</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/we-are-ns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/we-are-ns/</guid>
      <description>Nova Scotia’s portfolio of the very best people, products, and places. We Are NS&amp;rsquo; mission is to celebrate the very best brands and creative talent Nova Scotia has to offer one story at a time. Our vision is to create a vibrant community of people who build confidence among Nova Scotians by challenging themselves and supporting others to be better every day.&#xA;Join us and use the hashtag #WeAreNS to help us share our story to the world!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women in Science and Engineering at Acadia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>WISE (Women in Science and Engineering) at Acadia is a group of female faculty members from the Faculty of Pure and Applied Science and Kinesiology who gather together to address the unique issues that women in academia face. The group has supported learning opportunities and award applications for Acadia women faculty members. After a gathering held in October 2014 additional WISE priorities have been identified related to mentoring, science camps for young women, and a course offering for undergraduates in Women and Science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women&#39;s and Gender Studies</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-and-gender-studies-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-and-gender-studies-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>In 1973, Acadia University became one of the first universities in Canada to offer a course in Women&amp;rsquo;s Studies. The course, entitled Women in the Modern World, was the cornerstone of a program which in three decades has developed a multi-disciplinary approach to teaching and research in gender-related issues. Faculty members from the Arts, Pure and Applied Sciences, Education, Kinesiology, and Theatre contribute to the program on a rotational basis.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
