<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Organizations on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Organizations on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Computer Science Society</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-computer-science-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-computer-science-society/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Need some info&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;AEC has been developing and delivering workshops for business professionals, entrepreneurs, and not-for-profits for over 25 years. AEC continues to innovate and develop new and relevant programs for today’s business professional.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;rural-innovation-centre&#34;&gt;Rural Innovation Centre&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Rural Innovation Centre (RIC) supports entrepreneurs and businesses in the Annapolis Valley and on the South Shore by providing training, advisory and consulting services to small businesses, government and not-for-profit organizations. The Rural Innovation Centre is an incubator for start up companies to access working space and support, networking events, mentors and connect to Acadia faculty and facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;launchbox&#34;&gt;Launchbox&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Launchbox is the centre for student entrepreneurs, located on the 4th floor of Patterson Hall at Acadia University. We support students in their entrepreneurial pursuits by providing free programming, networking, access to mentors, and other entrepreneurs, working space and competitions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Robotics Program</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Robot Programming Competition mission is to increase interest in building digital technology and computer science by engaging Nova Scotia students in annual robotics programming competitions and related activities that feature problem solving and teamwork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Acadia Robotics Program, through the Jodrey School of Computer Science, depends heavily on financial support from external organizations and the committed volunteers who annually contribute to the season from late August through to mid-June.  We have a junior program, FIRST® LEGO® League, and a senior program, Robofest. All the outreach throughout the season culminates in a Provincial Robot Programming Championship here at Acadia Unversity each February, involving over 400 participants, 100 volunteers, media and many organizations.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/qA3L8_KJB4c&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Intellectual Property Office </title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Canadian Intellectual Property Office (CIPO), a Special Operating Agency (SOA) associated with Innovation, Science and Economic Development Canada, is responsible for the administration and processing of the greater part of intellectual property in Canada. CIPO&amp;rsquo;s areas of activity include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patents cover new inventions (process, machine, manufacture, composition of matter), or any new and useful improvement of an existing invention;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A trademark is a word (or words), a design, or a combination of these, used to identify the goods or services of one person or organization and to distinguish these goods or services from those of others in the marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Copyright provide protection for artistic, dramatic, musical or literary works (including computer programs), and three other subject-matter known as: performance, sound recording and communication signal;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Industrial designs are the visual features of shape, configuration, pattern or ornament (or any combination of these features), applied to a finished article of manufacture;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Integrated circuit topographies refer to the three-dimensional configurations of electronic circuits embodied in integrated circuit products or layout designs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colibri Software</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/colibri-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/colibri-software/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Colibri Software builds awesome software. We work with our clients to understand their needs and then produce a simple and effective solution to their problems. Our focus is on making a product easy to use, from websites to mobile apps, we like it when we hear “this is easy”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a special affinity for mapping projects and have send rugged phone apps as far as Nunavut to help collect data for the hunting community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nova Scotia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/digital-nova-scotia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/digital-nova-scotia/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Engaging both members and stakeholders in the region, Digital Nova Scotia provides advocacy, multi-sectoral industry intelligence, facilitates connections between industry and talent, and delivers high-level programming to ensure Nova Scotia’s $1.5 billion digital industry (which boasts an additional $1 billion in spin-offs) continues to flourish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;it-starts-here-it-stays-here-it-grows-here&#34;&gt;IT starts here. IT stays here. IT grows here.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the industry association for the fastest growing sector in the province with the highest number of ICT graduates per capita in Canada, Digital Nova Scotia encourages our tech talent and growing ecosystem of digital businesses to start here, stay here, and grow here! We believe that Nova Scotia’s digital technologies sector has the potential to be what the oil and gas sector is for Alberta. Nova Scotia has the “IT” factor: globally competitive talent, an ecosystem of support, advanced digital infrastructure, and a drive to push our economic boundaries. We are going for growth on a global scale!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HUB Kentville</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Get Inspired, Get Connected, Get involved. HUB spaces provide an inspirational home to members and are a focal point for change within the local communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-the-hub&#34;&gt;What is the Hub?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HUB is about the power of innovation through collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe there is no shortage of good ideas to solve the issues of our time. But there is an acute lack of collaboration and support structures to help make them happen. The HUB was founded to address this need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We set out to create spaces that combine the best of a trusted community, innovation lab, business incubator and the comforts of home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spaces with all the tools and trimmings needed to grow and develop innovative ventures for the world. But above all, spaces for meaningful encounters, exchange and inspiration, full of diverse people doing amazing things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea has been spreading like wildfire and resulted in the emergence of a global movement. To date, there are 25+ open HUBs and many more in the making, from London to San Francisco, Johannesburg, Melbourne and Sao Paulo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;mission&#34;&gt;Mission&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To become a global network of connected communities that enable collaborative ventures for a better world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the HUB, people from every profession, background and culture are being united by one thing: the imagination and drive to pursue enterprising ideas for the world. These are the people who see and do things differently and have entrepreneurial passion to create sustainable impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HUB is becoming the place they call home.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HarvestHand</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/harvesthand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/harvesthand/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HarvestHand is a community platform dedicated to strengthening regional food systems. We&amp;rsquo;re passionate about supporting farms with CSA&amp;rsquo;s to become more profitable using HarvestHand CSA Software, helping communities eat better through the HarvestHand Community, creating good jobs in rural communities, and building new media solutions that make sharing the harvest easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our vision is to create new media solutions that strengthen regional food systems&amp;rsquo; ability to succeed in value oriented approaches to production, distribution, consumption and community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Mandate is to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the profitability of Community Shared Agriculture (CSA) farms through the ease and functionality of HarvestHand CSA Software Platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create localized and fairly paid employment opportunities in rural communities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make it easy for citizens to locate, join and remain a member of a CSA farm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a space for exploration of ideas, identification of problems and creation of solutions related to local food systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build out best of regional food tooling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;flex-video&#34;&gt;
    &lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/qNxWThFGa5M&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jodrey School of Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Jodrey School of Computer Science prepares students for today&amp;rsquo;s ever changing world of technology in a unique, fully mobile computing environment. Students develop a thorough understanding of computer systems software, modern software design methods and computer systems software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Students in all degree programs complete a self-directed project during the course of their studies. This provides students with the opportunity to work closely with professors and to apply knowledge acquired through experiment and real-life application. Many students work on projects that end up in the public domain as open-source applications, free for everyone to download. Some students complete research work that becomes an integral part of their supervisor&amp;rsquo;s research, leading to publications in conferences and journals.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kerr &amp; Nadeau</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/kerr--nadeau/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/kerr--nadeau/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At Kerr &amp;amp; Nadeau our job is to de-mystify and to simplify the rules for you, to offer you sound professional advice and superior legal services that will enable you, whether you are an inventor, an entrepreneur or a corporate executive, to execute your business plan, to protect your legal rights and to realize your strategic objectives while mitigating risk and ensuring compliance. Risk is the bane and Achilles heel of most business enterprises, and the single greatest obstacle to achieving your mission critical goals. We have adopted a business model at Kerr &amp;amp; Nadeau that puts us in touch with our clients. We believe the best way for us to serve you better is for us to know you better. Each of the partners at Kerr &amp;amp; Nadeau has over 21 years of relevant, accomplished legal experience, with a rich array of clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are an IP-centric business law boutique with expertise in IP, IT, Corporate-Commercial and Government Contracting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Labnet Dental Lab Systems</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Labnet Dental Lab Systems offers the Dental Lab industry&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive and powerful management systems with solutions suited for labs of all sizes and budgets. Whether your lab is a thriving multi-site corporation or a one-technician miracle lab, we have a perfect fit for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Henry Schein company, you can depend on Labnet Dental Lab Systems for stability and providing your dentists with the latest technological advancements. When you are operating within tight deadlines, the last thing you should worry about is your software. Stability in your software means consistency and piece of mind in your lab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Henry Schein’s commitment to software in dentistry is unparalleled. No other company is in the unique position of developing software for both dentists and laboratories. The internet link between the labs and dentists shows the foresight one expects from industry leaders Labnet Dental Lab Systems and Dentrix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://labnet.net/products/labnet/index.html&#34;&gt;Labnet&lt;/a&gt;: The most powerful lab management software ever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://labnet.net/products/supplynet/index.html&#34;&gt;Supplynet&lt;/a&gt;: The leading inventory management application in our industry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.labnext.net/&#34;&gt;Labnext&lt;/a&gt;: Web based lab management software designed specifically for digital dentistry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ddxdental.com/&#34;&gt;DDX&lt;/a&gt;: Share pertinent information with your accounts at your convenience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progeny Genealogy</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/progeny-genealogy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/progeny-genealogy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Progeny Genealogy is the leading developer of family tree software and other useful, easy-to-use genealogy research resources, including &lt;a href=&#34;http://progenygenealogy.com/Products/FamilyTreeCharts.aspx&#34;&gt;Charting Companion&lt;/a&gt;™, &lt;a href=&#34;http://progenygenealogy.com/Products/TimelineCharts.aspx&#34;&gt;Genelines&lt;/a&gt;™ and &lt;a href=&#34;http://progenygenealogy.com/Products/FamilyMaps.aspx&#34;&gt;Map My Family Tree&lt;/a&gt;™. More than pretty charts, our genealogy software programs are also powerful research tools.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;terminal-error&#34;&gt;Terminal Error&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recursive meta loop&lt;/strong&gt;.  Stack overflow.  Core now being dumped&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/80845533@N00/1376527668&#34;&gt;Chocobot&lt;/a&gt; icon remixed with your bad dreams.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ScotiaCom</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/scotiacom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/scotiacom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ScotiaCom (aka Scotia Computer Resources Inc.) is a small, independent business located in the Annapolis Valley, Nova Scotia. What started as an educational software development company has become a leader in the development and deployment of services that allow organizations, groups, individuals and small businesses to take full advantage of the Internet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valley Family Fun</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/valley-family-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/valley-family-fun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;People who are new to the area (and some who are not) often ask &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-churchill-duke&#34;&gt;Laura Churchill Duke&lt;/a&gt;
 what they can do with their families in the Valley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This made her realize that there isn’t one central place to look for information. Valley Family Fun is a compilation of what she&amp;rsquo;s discovered!  Follow &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/groups/valleyfamilyfun/&#34;&gt;VFF on their Facebook group too&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>