<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 10:30:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build: Arcade - March Break Intensive</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/break-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 10:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/break-2025/</guid>
      <description>Build: Arcade is an introductory Computer Science course for Middle (grades 5 to 8) and High School learners. Using Makecode Arcade, we will build retro style video games. While exploring the early history of video games, we will learn the fundamentals of the Makecode Arcade game development engine.&#xA;Makecode Arcade is a great first step into the world of video game development, as well as the larger world of Computer Science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refresh 2024 - 2025 Youth Cohort</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/cohort-2024-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/cohort-2024-2025/</guid>
      <description>For the past several years, Refresh Annapolis Valley has been offering courses to small cohorts of learners over the academic year. The courses offered include:&#xA;Creative Computing: An introductory Computer Science course for younger learners using the Scratch programming environment. Scratch Masters: Advanced course for young learners focused on Scratch, physical hardware programming with Microbits, and retro video game development. Build Arcade: An introductory Computer Science course for High School learners using Makecode Arcade to build retro style video games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Fall 2023</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-fall-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 14:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-fall-2023/</guid>
      <description>Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to the computer sciences. This course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid young people (grades 4 to 6) in learning the basics of software development. Scratch is used over the world by students to easily create interactive artwork, interactive stories, and video games while acting as a stepping stone to the more advanced world of computer science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scratch Masters Course 2023</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/masters-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 14:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/masters-2023/</guid>
      <description>Scratch Masters is the next level course for graduates of the Creative Computing program. Within this course we continue to explore the world of the computer sciences. This course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid young people (grades 4 to 6) in learning the more advanced concepts of Scratch software development. Scratch is used over the world by students to easily create interactive artwork, interactive stories, and video games while acting as a stepping stone to the more advanced world of computer science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Summer Bootcamp 2023</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-summer-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 14:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-summer-2023/</guid>
      <description>Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to the computer sciences. This course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid young people (grades 4 to 6) in learning the basics of software development. Scratch is used over the world by students to easily create interactive artwork, interactive stories, and video games while acting as a stepping stone to the more advanced world of computer science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Video Games</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/building-video-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 19:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/building-video-games/</guid>
      <description>Our last 6-week intensive intro to video game development with godot left a waiting list of others behind who wanted in. We are opening up a section for a new small cohort.&#xA;Are you interested in video games, programming, or creating virtual experiences? Take your skills to the next level with this beginner Godot course! Learn the fundamentals of game design, the ins and outs of the Godot game engine, and create your own video game in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Game Dev With Godot</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/video-game-development-with-godot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 19:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/video-game-development-with-godot/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in video games, programming, or creating virtual experiences? Take your skills to the next level with this beginner Godot course! Learn the fundamentals of game design, the ins and outs of the Godot game engine, and create your own video game in the process.&#xA;What is Godot Godot is a free game engine that enables you to create any 2D or 3D experience you can dream up. It’s an all in one tool for building games for many different platforms such as desktop, mobile, and the web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scratch Masters 2023 - 2024</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 14:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2023/</guid>
      <description>We are thrilled to be opening up our Winter 2023 Creative Computing Course for registration for the Wolfville School community. This is our 6th year offering this popular course. Unlike other years, we will be running 1 cohort of learners for free for Wolfville School Students. Registration is open until Jan. 27.&#xA;Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to the computer sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comp Sci Education Week - Build a micro:bit Mini Crane</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creating-mini-crane-with-the-microbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creating-mini-crane-with-the-microbit/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in robotics or do you enjoy messing around with electronics? In this workshop, you&amp;rsquo;ll assemble both the hardware and software needed to create a miniature crane controlled by the micro:bit microcontroller.&#xA;Join us as we kick off Computer Science Education Week with this hands on workshop. We are limited to 10 spots, so act fast!&#xA;What is a micro:bit? The micro:bit is a small, compact computer based on a 43 mm × 52 mm circuit board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Enter the Side Door</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-enter-the-side-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 18:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-enter-the-side-door/</guid>
      <description>Side Door is a digital platform that matches performing artists with venues to create shows anytime, anywhere, on their own terms. Come meet CEO &amp;amp; Co-Founder Laura Simpson for a fireside chat and live performance with Cassie Josephine (Indie Folk Country princess). Laura and Cassie will talk about the challenges artists in the music business face and how Side Door &amp;rsquo;s unique digital platform is defining a new business model capitalizing on the power of a networked community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Entrepreneur Chat over Beers</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-influencing-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 16:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-influencing-markets/</guid>
      <description>For this popup Startup Life entrepreneur chat over beers, we will be hosting Avery Schrader, a Nova Scotian living abroad in Tallinn, Estonia. Estonia, for those not in the know, is a tiny Baltic state, but in tech terms it&amp;rsquo;s a giant. It has a population of just 1.3 million, yet produces more start-ups per head than any other country in Europe.&#xA;Avery is the founder of Modash, a tool that enables marketing teams to find and verify the audiences of over 50,000,000 influencers globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Meet R2-Weed2</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-r2-weed2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-r2-weed2/</guid>
      <description>Technology-driven agricultural experimentation. Iterative product testing. Validated machine learning. Pivot. Pivot. Pivot. Welcome to the ag-tech startup world of Teric Greenan and Nexus Robotics .&#xA;With Nexus Robotics , Teric is applying Artificial Intelligence to building a reliable and cost-effective way to produce crops. Their autonomous robot R2-Weed2 is capable of cutting and spraying weeds, fertilizing crops, and collect data about growing conditions. Teric will talk about his team&amp;rsquo;s start up journey, and the amazing technological innovations they are applying to revolutionize agriculture as we know it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Ladies Learning Code Day: Intro to UX Design</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-user-experience-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 10:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-user-experience-design/</guid>
      <description>Join thousands of Canadians coast to coast to coast taking their first steps learning about application development.&#xA;With great design comes great responsibility. User experience (UX) design isn’t just about creating pretty or functioning websites - it’s about creative solutioning and trying to make people&amp;rsquo;s lives and experiences better.&#xA;As application designers, we need to remember that we aren&amp;rsquo;t designing products for ourselves, but for other people. Being a UX designer allows you to work with and problem solve for a variety of different people, and empathy plays a huge part in this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUILD: Computer Science Camp for Girls</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/camp-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 08:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/camp-2019/</guid>
      <description>BUILD is a week long dive into the world of Computer Science for girls 11 to 14. We will explore the basics of software development while building interactive artwork and literature, video games, and software that interacts with the physical world. Through our exploration we will also journey through use of hardware, refine our ideation skills and turn our ideas into software. Campers will also connect with Computer Scientists in our community who are changing the world one algorithm at a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Camp 2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/camp-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 08:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/camp-2019/</guid>
      <description>Creative Computing Camp is a week long adventure into the world of Computer Science. Using the popular Scratch programming environment as a starting point, we will build interactive artwork and stories, video games, and software that interacts with the physical world. Through our exploration of the creativity of software development, we will learn about where ideas come from, and how to turn ideas into action. We will explore the world beyond Scratch, including 3D design, printing, and virtual reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of Our Digital Nation: Digital Nova Scotia 2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-our-digital-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-our-digital-nation/</guid>
      <description>Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s digital economy is currently valued at $2.5 billion. Tyler Farmer, Project Manager at Digital Nova Scotia, will present a state of our digital nation, reflecting on trends and opportunities, both urban and rural. Join us for our last Refresh meetup for the 2018-2019 year for discussion and drinks care of our host, Annapolis Cider Company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Innovating on The Internet</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/innovating-on-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/innovating-on-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>Have the next (big or small) idea, no budget, or development skills? No problem &amp;ndash; you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t start with building anyway.&#xA;In this hands on workshop we will explore pre-product design tools that anyone can pick up to express their app idea. With these tools you will walk away with a means to engage your user base to test concepts, gather feedback quickly, very inexpensively, and early on in the product cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming Hardware with Python</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/programming-hardware-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 12:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/programming-hardware-with-python/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to know how to make code interact with the real world? In this introductory workshop to Python programming, you’ll learn the vital stepping stones to controlling hardware using the Circuit Playground microcontroller (microcomputer) with one of the most robust, versatile, and popular programming languages.&#xA;What is a Circuit Playground? The Circuit Playground is a microcontroller, or a tiny computer. This computer can easily be programmed to interact with hardware that you connect to it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#ScratchFest</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2019/</guid>
      <description>Calling all Digital Builders #ScratchFest is a weekend (April 6th and April 7th) Build-a-thon for kids and teens interested in creating amazing original work with digital technologies, such as the Scratch programming environment, Processing, Virtual Reality, and more.&#xA;During #ScartchFest, participants will brainstorm an idea, develop their project, and showcase a final prototype. This weekend warrior event provides an excellent opportunity for coders to invent their own projects and demonstrate their knowledge within a collaborative, creative, and playful environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro Game Carnival</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/retro-game-fest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 17:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/retro-game-fest/</guid>
      <description>Calling All Classic Gamers! The Retro Game Carnival is a celebration of the video games of yesteryear. From the 1970s to early 2000s, we will explore the arcade, console, and PC games that defined eras gone by. Our game fest will include a pop-up museum, fan-made DIY retro arcade, game tournaments, and workshops.&#xA;Young and inspired? Be sure to join us for #ScratchFest 2019 the following day and put your creativity towards building your own retro influenced games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency and Blockchain: The Crash Course</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/blockchain-the-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 17:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/blockchain-the-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>This 4 hour crash course will get attendees up-to-speed on the world of cryptocurrency and the technology that powers much of it: Blockchain.&#xA;This unique opportunity runs from 5PM to 9PM, and is limited to 20 attendees. Dinner and snacks provided.&#xA;Part 1: Intro to Blockchain Fintech The Bitcoin Blockchain just had its 10 year anniversary on January 3rd, 2019. With several monumental crashes and rushes in its market, no one could say with certainty whether or not the network would be a success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women in Technology: Uncensored</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/women-in-technology-uncensored/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/women-in-technology-uncensored/</guid>
      <description>Join Acadia Women in Technology Society and Refresh Annapolis Valley for an evening of networking, refreshments, and discussion. Guest speakers Lori Shepherd , Chief Creative Officer Cold Furnace Studios, and Cindy Trudel , Instructor in Acadia University’s Jodrey School of Computer Science, will lead a discussion about hacking the male dominated computer science academy and industry to work for women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blogging to Be Found</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/blogging-to-be-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/blogging-to-be-found/</guid>
      <description>How to use a business blog to improve search engine ranking Upon learning simple strategies for business blogging, Anita Kirkbride &amp;rsquo;s WordPress business blog (https://twirp.ca/) went from ZERO to HERO in a matter of weeks and she&amp;rsquo;s coming to share with you her best tips for using a business blog to be found. Anita will share her best strategies, and walk you through how to use WordPress to get your search engine placement scores up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ag &#43; Tech = Innovation</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ag-tech-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ag-tech-innovation/</guid>
      <description>Agriculture globally is a 12 trillion dollar annual industry ripe for technology startups looking to bring new hi-tech innovations to market. Where does digital technology and agriculture meet, and what are the opportunities?&#xA;Gary Morton (Morton Horticultural Associates, Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce Agriculture Committee) will discuss this exciting technology space, and the over $160,000 (cash and in-kind services) that the AVCC has awarded locally to spark agriculture innovation. Dr. Danny Silver (Acadia Institute for Data Analytics) will look at the opportunities around ag.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winning at Search Engines</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/winning-at-search-engines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/winning-at-search-engines/</guid>
      <description>What’s the point of having a website if you’re not getting any traffic?&#xA;With over half of the average website’s traffic coming from search engines, it’s important to rank in search results for keywords that are not only searched frequently but also have high intent.&#xA;You’ve taken the first step, you’ve built a website you’re happy with – now, it’s time to take out the guesswork and help your target market find what they are looking for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Course 2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 23:59:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2019/</guid>
      <description>We are thrilled to be opening up our 2019 Creative Computing Course for registration. This is our 3rd year offering this popular course. Unlike other years, we will be running 2 cohorts of learners for free. One cohort will be a mixed class of girls and boys. The second will be for girls. Registration is open until Jan. 2.&#xA;Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to the computer sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Digital to Physical: 3D Design and Printing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/from-digital-to-physical-3d-printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/from-digital-to-physical-3d-printing/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new world of of 3D printing, where you can produce 3D objects almost as easily as you can dream of them. In this hands on workshop we will:&#xA;Learn about how 3D printing is shaking up different industries Types of 3D printing technologies How to design for printing How to print your designs Bring a laptop and be prepared to roll up your sleeves. Space is limited to 20 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Developer Bootcamp: Part 3 of 3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-3-of-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-3-of-3/</guid>
      <description>In this teen Hoist mini series, you will learn about how to build your own web application. Web applications are unlike traditional websites. Traditional websites are largely informational (like the Refresh Annapolis Valley website) where web applications solve particular problems (think Gmail for email).&#xA;In part 1, you will learn the ins-and-outs of building app interfaces In part 2, you will learn how to add interactivity to your web app In part 3, you will learn how to manage app data If you haven&amp;rsquo;t attended part 1 or 2, you can jump right into part 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Developer Bootcamp: Part 2 of 3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-2-of-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-2-of-3/</guid>
      <description>In this teen Hoist mini series, you will learn about how to build your own web application. Web applications are unlike traditional websites. Traditional websites are largely informational (like the Refresh Annapolis Valley website) where web applications solve particular problems (think Gmail for email).&#xA;In part 1, you will learn the ins-and-outs of building app interfaces In part 2, you will learn how to add interactivity to your web app In part 3, you will learn how to manage app data If you haven&amp;rsquo;t attended part 1, you can jump right into part 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The School in the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-school-in-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 18:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-school-in-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>What is the future of education in a networked world?&#xA;In this documentary screening and discussion, we will discuss Indian professor Sugata Mitra&amp;rsquo;s calls for a revolution in how and what we learn. With a global network of information a few clicks away, Mitra argues that the Victorian model on which our school systems are based is obsolete.&#xA;School In The Cloud follows a three-year experiment as Mitra installs unmanned internet kiosks in locations ranging from remote villages in West Bengal to a school in northeast England, to enable children to self-organize their learning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Developer Bootcamp: Part 1 of 3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-1-of-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-1-of-3/</guid>
      <description>In this teen Hoist mini series, you will learn about how to build your own web application. Web applications are unlike traditional websites. Traditional websites are largely informational (like the Refresh Annapolis Valley website) where web applications solve particular problems (think Gmail for email).&#xA;In part 1, you will learn the ins-and-outs of building app interfaces In part 2, you will learn how to add interactivity to your web app In part 3, you will learn how to manage app data Pizza + workshop + building</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Succeeding at Failing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/succeeding-at-failing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/succeeding-at-failing/</guid>
      <description>Behind every entrepreneurial success lie the stories of numerous failures. As a mindset, entrepreneurship is characterized by risk-taking, experimentation, and continually challenging oneself to produce meaningful results. It is also about learning from failure, and, where possible, finding new ways to tackle problems that eventually lead to success.&#xA;Join Katelyn Bourgoin , a 3X founder/business owner turned growth strategist, for a discussion about how to think about entrepreneurship. Come mingle with a wide cross section of Annapolis Valley entrepreneurs for drinks, networking, and old fashioned discussion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Learn to Code Day: Build a Browser Extension!</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-browser-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 12:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-browser-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Join thousands of Canadians coast to coast to coast taking their first steps learning about Computer Science.&#xA;At this &amp;ldquo;Women Learning Code&amp;rdquo; event, we will learn how to build web browser extensions with JavaScript. Browser extensions extend your web browser with additional features, modify web pages, and integrate your browser with the other services you use. Extensions can help customize our browsing experience or increase productivity by reducing repetitive tasks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap 2018-2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/bootstrap-2018-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/bootstrap-2018-2019/</guid>
      <description>Refresh Annapolis Valley has been rocking the world of Computer Science and New Media circa 2012. We&amp;rsquo;ve built friendships, business relationships, helped form new statups, educated each other, helped rear the next generation&amp;hellip;. We&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished tons.&#xA;The 2018 - 2019 season is upon us! Organizers, visionaries, and supporters of all descriptions, come join us for an action oriented discussion on what our new season should look like. What sort of monthly meetup topics would you like to see?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUILD: Computer Science Camp for Girls</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/camp-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 08:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/camp-2018/</guid>
      <description>BUILD is a week long dive into the world of Computer Science for girls 11 to 13. We will explore the basics of software development while building interactive artwork and stories, video games, and software that interacts with the physical world. Through our exploration we will also journey through use of hardware, refine our ideation skills and turn our ideas into software. Campers will also connect with Computer Scientists in our community who are changing the world one algorithm at a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Camp 2018</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/camp-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 08:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/camp-2018/</guid>
      <description>Creative Computing Camp is a week long adventure into the world of Computer Science. Using the popular Scratch programming environment to master the basics of software development, we will build interactive artwork and stories, video games, and software that interacts with the physical world. Through our exploration of the creativity of software development, we will learn about where ideas come from, and how to turn ideas into action. Campers will also connect with Computer Scientists in our community who are changing the world one algorithm at a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#ScratchFest</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2018/</guid>
      <description>Calling all Digital Builders #ScratchFest is a weekend (June 23th and June 24th) Build-a-thon for kids and teens interested in creating amazing original work with digital technologies, such as the Scratch programming environment, Processing, Virtual Reality, and more.&#xA;During #ScartchFest, participants will brainstorm an idea, develop their project, and showcase a final prototype. This weekend warrior event provides an excellent opportunity for coders to invent their own projects and demonstrate their knowledge within a collaborative, creative, and playful environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scratch For Educators</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/scratch-for-educators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 12:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/scratch-for-educators/</guid>
      <description>Scratch is being used in thousands of schools around the world to teach kids about the Computer Sciences. Since its launch over 10 years ago, kids from Elementary to High School have created over 6 million projects. In this crash course, adults (parents and educators) will learn about the Scratch programming environment and how it might be used to introduce learners to the Computer Sciences. No coding experience required.&#xA;Please register in advance so we know how much pizza to order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching a Computer To See</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/teaching-a-computer-to-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/teaching-a-computer-to-see/</guid>
      <description>Machine&amp;rsquo;s can learning amazing things when we train them. In this Hoist workshop, teens will will explore Artificial Intelligence by learning how to build a program that can guess what it sees in a picture. No coding experience? No worries. This fun introductory workshop is meant for the beginner. Using cutting edge machine learning tools, participants will learn how software is being used to create amazing programs that learn along the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using DNA to Reverse-Engineer Your Family Tree</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/using-dna-to-reverse-enginee--your-family-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/using-dna-to-reverse-enginee--your-family-tree/</guid>
      <description>Recent advances in consumer genetics have enabled genealogists to solve mysteries in their family tree. Adoptees are finding their biological families by sharing the results of DNA tests with Websites that match millions of individuals.&#xA;Progeny Genealogy&amp;rsquo;s Charting Companion software displays the relationship distance of family members, as a number in an easy to understand chart. CC can also empirically find an adoptee&amp;rsquo;s family with an algorithm that simulates placement and compares theoretical to laboratory DNA results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Hardware - Programming The Physical World </title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hacking-hardware-programming-the-physical-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hacking-hardware-programming-the-physical-world/</guid>
      <description>Interactive jewelry, DIY laser tag, robots you design and build. In this Hoist workshop, teens will explore electronics by learning how to build and program robots . No coding or electronics experience? No worries. This fun introductory workshop is meant for the beginner. Using the Circuit Playground, participants will learn how coding and circuits are being used to create amazing creations. This workshop is for teens with no prior experience with programming required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Game Making and Circuitry</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/video-game-making-and-circuitry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 16:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/video-game-making-and-circuitry/</guid>
      <description>Building games is a great way to experience game play from the perspective of the creator. In this creative computing workshop, kids will learn how to program a computer to build their own games and build their own game controllers. Kids will learn basic coding and circuitry concepts in a fun beginner friendly environment. Using Scratch, a visual programming environment, kids will be exposed to an international community of coders making a wide range of games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking About Design - Creative Strategies</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/thinking-about-design-creative-strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/thinking-about-design-creative-strategies/</guid>
      <description>Design Thinking is being used by large innovative companies to create exceptional products and experiences (think Google Glass, AirBnB, your arrival experience with major airlines, and, of course, toilet paper). It can also be applied at much smaller scales - in education, to find solutions for sustainability challenges, and of course in tech companies of any size. Join Anne Stieger for an introduction to this powerful toolbox, process and mindset for user-centered design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animating Stories - Interactive Stories with Scratch</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/animating-stories-interactive-stories-with-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 16:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/animating-stories-interactive-stories-with-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Animating is a great way to bring a story to life. In this Creative Computing workshop, kids will learn how to program a computer to create animations for their own stories. Kids will learn basic coding concepts in a fun beginner friendly environment. Using Scratch, a visual programming environment, kids will be exposed to an international community of coders making a wide range of animation based projects. This intro workshop is for kids as young as 8 with no prior experience with Scratch required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art Making with Your Computer!</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/art-making-with-your-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 16:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/art-making-with-your-computer/</guid>
      <description>Art is made with a variety of media - even computers! In this Creative Computing workshop, kids will learn how to program a computer to make interactive artwork. Kids will learn basic coding concepts in a fun beginner friendly environment. Using Scratch, a visual programming environment, kids will be exposed to an international community of coders making a wide range of interactive art projects. This intro workshop is for kids as young as 8 with no prior experience with Scratch required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring your Visual Art Alive with Computers - Intro to Processing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/intro-to-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/intro-to-processing/</guid>
      <description>Do you enjoy painting or drawing? In this Hoist workshop, teens will learn how to program a computer to build generative art. We will learn how how simple math equations can be used to create beautiful and engaging outcomes. No coding experience? No worries. This fun introductory workshop is meant for the beginner coder with a visual arts interest. Using OpenProcessing, participants will be exposed to an international community of coder-artists making a wide range of digital creations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Did All The Women Go?  Retaining Women in Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/where-did-all-the-women-go-retaining-women-in-computer-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/where-did-all-the-women-go-retaining-women-in-computer-science/</guid>
      <description>Over the last 30 years, the number of women entering Computer Science university programs has dropped from 50% to around 10%. Once in the program, women have a higher drop out rate than men. And women graduating with Computer Science degrees often leave the field and pursue alternate careers. Dr Randy Newman and Cindy Trudel have been actively researching this phenomenon over the last few years. In this Refresh Annapolis Valley talk, Randy and Cindy will discuss the problem, the programs that Acadia has in place, and the needs for the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Course 2018</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 18:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2018/</guid>
      <description>Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to the computer sciences. Broken up into 7 units, this course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid young people (aged 8 to 13) in learning the basics of software development. Scratch is used over the world by students to easily create interactive artwork, interactive stories, and video games while acting as a stepping stone to the more advanced world of computer science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refreshing Marketing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/refreshing-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/refreshing-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Marketing is forever changing. What works one week does not necessarily work the next. Join Duncan Ebata , Evan Hill , and Ashley Greene for a marketing insiders discussion on how to stay on the curve. They will explore why and how empathizing and understanding customers can be game changing; how to &amp;ldquo;growth hack&amp;rdquo; your marketing to double your results at half the cost; and time saving and low cost tools for marketing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revved Up!</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/revved-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 14:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/revved-up/</guid>
      <description>March 23 to 24th is launchbox&amp;rsquo;s Start It Up! - a weekend business ideation competition with 10K in prizes to be won. If you are interested in playing with new business ideas, this event is for you. While an University event, we have had youth teams (and winning youth teams!) at several Start It Up! competitions. This year is no different. If you are interested in learning more about this business ideation event, come to this information session and beef up on your skills to help you compete.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of Computer Science Education</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-computer-science-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-computer-science-education/</guid>
      <description>With an estimated 218,000 new skilled ICT workers needed in Canada by 2020 to meet the short term demands of our digital economy, focus on our educational system to address this challenge is paramount. The profound lack of diversity within the digital tech economy further complicates the response required. With changes in our provincial educational pipeline well under way, we are still early on in deploying a comprehensive response.&#xA;Join our panel discussion focused on defining challenges and solutions for Computer Science education today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Go</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/getting-started-with-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 18:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/getting-started-with-go/</guid>
      <description>Computer programming is the art, craft and science of writing programs which define how computers operate. This workshop, lead by Jodrey School of Computer Science alumn Tim Cooper , will teach you how to write computer programs using a programming language designed by Google named Go. Learn the basics as we design an AI to interact in a multiplayer game with the other participants in the workshop.&#xA;Go is a general purpose programming language with advanced features and a clean syntax.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>f5://imagination</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 10:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</guid>
      <description>f5://imagination is a pop up exhibit focused on digital creativity. This one day temporary exhibit features work from digital artists, makers, scratchers, computer scientists, engineers and pretendgineer, hardware hackers, lego robotics warriors, indy game developers, new media innovators, VR and AR pioneers&amp;hellip; digital builders of all shapes, sizes, and credentials.&#xA;Schedule 10 AM to 12:30 PM Screening &amp; discussion of Hidden Figures: The story of a team of female African-American mathematicians who served a vital role in NASA during the early years of the U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digitized Reality</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/digitized-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/digitized-reality/</guid>
      <description>Come slap on a headset and enter the world of virtual reality. In this workshop, we will explore virtual reality by both examining the capabilities of commercial headsets, as well as learn how to build our own VR environments. If you can, bring a smart phone to test your uniquely constructed VR world. We can only accommodate a limited number of people for this event, so get your free ticket fast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seed: Hacking Entrepreneurship in the Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/seed-hacking-entrepreneurship-in-the-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 18:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/seed-hacking-entrepreneurship-in-the-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>Seed is a documentary that follows an international group of programmer entrepreneurs at AngelHack: one of the most competitive global hackathons and digital business ideation competitions. Three minutes to pitch. One shot to fund their proposals.&#xA;Seed is also a gathering of our Annapolis Valley startup community. The event will feature the diversity of associations, businesses, and individuals who comprise our digital tech startup community. An assembly of our entrepreneurial family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Entrepreneurship: Turning Ideas into Action</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creative-entrepreneurship-turning-ideas-into-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creative-entrepreneurship-turning-ideas-into-action/</guid>
      <description>Problems and solutions. In between are the numerous ideas that eventually lead to innovative solutions and new business opportunities. Join the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre for a talk all about ideas. Where do they come from? How do we nurture them? How can we turn them into problem solving new business?&#xA;Build your mad ideation skills at this workshop, then take them to Start It Up: our business ideation competition with $10K in prizes on the line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founders Meetup: Lets Start a Business</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/founders-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 13:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/founders-meetup/</guid>
      <description>For this Hoist meetup, we will be doing something a little different. We are looking for a few budding teen entrepreneurs to start a business. This is the pitch:&#xA;Services supporting the business startup space in Rural Nova Scotia are diverse and not well represented as a whole. Our business aims to unify the Western Nova business startup ecosystem by building a coherent communication platform. By doing so, we will encourage entrepreneurship within our community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Smart Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/smart-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/smart-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>The Smart Communities movement involves villages, towns and cities getting ubiquitously connected to the Internet, and using the connection to involve citizens in networked activities. This movement argues that all the economic wealth created since WW2 has come from innovation - a networking activity that Smart Communities excel at. Smart Communities have better economic growth, more sustainable life-styles, and better health care.&#xA;i-Valley, a non-for-profit group working to put fast broadband networks into our communities, is bringing the Smart Community movement to our rural and remote regions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Learn to Code Day: Intro to AI and Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-ai-and-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-ai-and-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Join hundreds of Canadians coast to coast to coast taking their first steps learning about Computer Science. National Learn to Code Day was launched by Ladies Learning Code 5 years ago!&#xA;At this &amp;ldquo;Women Learning Code&amp;rdquo; event, we will learn about Artificial intelligence and machine learning. From Siri on your iPhone to Google Map suggestions, to recommendations for purchases during your Amazon check-out, AI is all around us.&#xA;AI and machine learning at its core is about data - and ways to make meaning of data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Printing: From Concept to the Palm of Your Hand</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/3d-printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/3d-printing/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new world of of 3D printing, where you can produce 3D objects almost as easily as you can dream of them. Emoji figurines, jewellery, nick nacks, to the more practical, in this hands on workshop you will learn how to design a 3D project. We will cap off the event by printing your original work.&#xA;Pizza + workshop + building&#xA;Bring your own laptop. A small number of laptops will be available to borrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIY Usability Lab: Testing With Little Or No Budget</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/diy-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/diy-usability/</guid>
      <description>Usability testing uncovers problem areas with your website. But not many do it, or do too little because of perceived complexity and cost. When you have limited time and budget, build your own usability lab and get results. A low-cost usability lab will be demonstrated using readily available hardware and software and results from testing our Acadia University library website will be shared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#ScratchFest</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2017/</guid>
      <description>Calling all Scratchers #ScratchFest is a weekend (June 24th and June 25th) Scratch-a-thon for kids interested in creating amazing original work with the Scratch programming environment.&#xA;During #ScartchFest, kids will brainstorm an idea, develop their project, and showcase a final prototype. This weekend warrior event provides an excellent opportunity for Scratch coders to invent their own projects and demonstrate their knowledge in Scratch within a collaborative, creative, and playful environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against Flat Screens: Learn 3D Design</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/against-flat-screens-learn-3d-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/against-flat-screens-learn-3d-design/</guid>
      <description>In this Hoist teen design talk, Max Caplan will introduce us to 3D design using Blender. Blender is a professional 3D computer graphics software used for creating animated films, visual effects, art, 3D printed models, interactive 3D applications and video games. Max will walk us through installing, using, and designing your first Blender project: an awesome robot.&#xA;Pizza + workshop + building&#xA;Bring your own laptop. A small number of laptops will be available to borrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digitizing Your Mouth: 2 Decades of Digital Dentistry in Wolfville</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/digitizing-your-mouth-2-decades-of-digital-dentistry-in-wolfville/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/digitizing-your-mouth-2-decades-of-digital-dentistry-in-wolfville/</guid>
      <description>Henry Schein is a distributor and producer of health care products and services with a presence in 33 countries. The company is a Fortune World’s Most Admired Company and is ranked number one in its industry for social responsibility. Its Wolfville operation is at the forefront of digitizing dentistry with its wide range of home grown software solutions.&#xA;Come help the Henry Schein Woflville team christen its new office. Product Manager Sandy Macdonald will talk about the state of digital dentistry and how our Wolfville team is working on pushing its edges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrapping The Web</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/bootstrapping-the-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/bootstrapping-the-web/</guid>
      <description>For our first Hoist meetup, we&amp;rsquo;ll be learning how to use the Twitter Bootstrap code library to create beautiful front-end websites. Bootstrap is a combination of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript that allow you to write very little but get a whole lot. We&amp;rsquo;ll start with the basics of HTML and CSS and then dive into using Bootstrap to jump-start your web project.&#xA;Pizza + workshop + building&#xA;Bring your own laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life:  Youth Gone Wild</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-youth-gone-wild/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-youth-gone-wild/</guid>
      <description>Aristides Milios is possessed. In 2014 he co-founded Microcent Technologies. As CTO he focused on incubating hyper-local location technology for use in small-to-mid sized businesses. In 2015, he co-founded Hoist Halifax: a monthly series of workshops for teens interested in design, entrepreneurship and tech. That same year, he graduated from Propel ICT Accelerator Program. In 2016 he graduated from High School.&#xA;In this fireside chat, come learn what drives Aristides towards the tech startup trenches, and how he is building a youth entrepreneurship culture in Nova Scotia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Sucks</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/project-management-sucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/project-management-sucks/</guid>
      <description>Project management seems to be one of those areas of necessary evil. Disconnected project managers who don&amp;rsquo;t really understand your work coupled with never ending meetings, charts, spreadsheets, forms, paperwork, complicated management software&amp;hellip; Project management can feel like it is more of a barrier than a help to team productivity.&#xA;In this talk, Mike Caplan, a reluctant Software Development Manager, will explore a lightweight tool for overseeing the project processes. Based on a simple board, this technique helps visualize workflow, expose operational problems, and reduce wasted time from excessive multitasking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maker Meetup</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/maker-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/maker-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Calling all makers, inventors, artists, entrepreneurs, tinkerers, and the like. Join Refresh Annapolis Valley and Annapolis Valley STEAMspace for what we hope will be a regular meetup for the Valley maker community to gather, share ideas, and build community.&#xA;Projects galore to explore!&#xA;Ian McKay will be demoing a magic cauldron, CNC stuff and a possible new product. Max Caplan will show off a homebrew handheld gaming console. And you&amp;hellip;?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting: Using Machine Learning Techniques in Energy, Environment and Agriculture</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/forecasting-using-machine-learning-techniques-in-energy-environment-and-agriculture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/forecasting-using-machine-learning-techniques-in-energy-environment-and-agriculture/</guid>
      <description>Dr Daniel Silver will review a series of projects undertaken by the Acadia Institute for Data Analytics . These amazing projects can estimate crop yield from smart phone images, do solar energy forecasting, manage building energy, determine stream flow rate and aquifer recharge prediction, sales forecasting, and classifying objects in UAV agriculture field images.&#xA;Many of these problems utilize high resolution observed and forecasted weather, high definition and multi-spectral digital images, and 5 minute through 60 minute data flow rates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Course 2017</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 18:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2017/</guid>
      <description>Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to the computer sciences. Broken up into 7 units, this course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid young people (aged 8 to 13) in learning the basics of software development. Scratch is used over the world by students to easily create animations and games while acting as a stepping stone to the more advanced world of computer science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Feel The Frost Byte</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-feel-the-frost-byte/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-feel-the-frost-byte/</guid>
      <description>Business-hypothesis-driven experimentation. Iterative product releases. Validated learning. Pivot. Pivot. Pivot. Welcome to the tech startup world of John Frost .&#xA;From the early days of Frostbyte Interactive, Aerhyve Aerial Technologies, and now PrecisionHawk, John&amp;rsquo;s pursuit of innovative products and services in the digital tech space runs years long. Join us for a fireside chat with John where we will explore the inner working of a person committed to the startup life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding The World Through R</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/understanding-the-world-through-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/understanding-the-world-through-r/</guid>
      <description>The world is bubbling over with data. When analyzed, data can provide the inquiring mind with useful information that can suggest outcomes and support decision-making. Be it the data generated about business practices, human behaviours, the biological world; being able to understand what your data is telling you is incredibly empowering. &amp;ldquo;R&amp;rdquo; is a free, accessible, and powerful programming language that offers a suite of tools for data analysis.&#xA;Our tour guide, Trevor Avery — biostatistician, faculty member at Acadia University, and coordinator of R-bar — will provide us a primer on R.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Ideas for Your Next Social Media Campaign</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/10-ideas-for-your-next-social-media-campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/10-ideas-for-your-next-social-media-campaign/</guid>
      <description>Wes Booth will break down and share 10 tips he&amp;rsquo;s learned over his 10 year experience in the world of social media. Everything from emerging platforms and tools you can use to promote your business, to specific tips for boosting your marketing campaign success, and how to go above and beyond for your audience and customers. Wes won&amp;rsquo;t promise you life changing results because that&amp;rsquo;s not possible, but what he can do is prepare you to be in a position to have success and offer you practical things to take away and test out on your business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Realtime Web: Intro To Node.js</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-realtime-web-intro-to-node-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-realtime-web-intro-to-node-js/</guid>
      <description>Node.js is a rapidly growing technology that has been making big waves in the world of web development. Node lets you easily build fast and scalable network applications perfect for the realtime web. In this workshop you’ll learn how to get started using Node, its background and history, and the problems it seeks to address. We’ll get our hands dirty building a realtime chat server to get a feel for the amazing power of Node.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UX Fist Fighting - Designing For Usability</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ux-fist-fighting-designing-for-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ux-fist-fighting-designing-for-usability/</guid>
      <description>10 years of picking fights and getting kicked out of a meetings - Mike Downs shares his personal quest to define &amp;ldquo;usability.&amp;rdquo; Mike will dive deep in to describing why usability is important for your websites and web applications. He will offer up pointers on how to think about your own projects with a user focused mind.&#xA;Mike has over eighteen years of Internet marketing strategy and product management experience helping create, shape, and launch technology products on the Web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CODE: Debugging the Gender Gap</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</guid>
      <description>CODE: Debugging The Gender Gap exposes the dearth of female and minority software engineers and explores the reasons for this gender gap and digital divide.&#xA;Tech jobs are growing three times faster than our colleges are producing computer science graduates. By 2019 there will be 182,000 jobs in information and communications technology that will go unfilled by homegrown Canadian talent because not enough people will have the right skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ballmer Peak</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ballmer-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ballmer-peak/</guid>
      <description>When surveying a bunch of #Refreshers what we should do for July:&#xA;A) Take off and enjoy the sun (47.1%)&#xA;B) Keep on trucking - regular Refresh meetup for July (35.3%)&#xA;C) Other - drink beer (17.6%)&#xA;&amp;hellip; so we drink beer!&#xA;Join us for a crazy selection of craft beer, pizza and banter. Bring your laptop and we can put the Ballmer Peak to the test**. Come chat about the BIG plans for Refresh in September and beyond&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspiration. Imitation. Innovation: Transforming The Physical World With Open Source Hardware</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/inspiration-imitation-innovation-transforming-the-physical-world-with-open-source-hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/inspiration-imitation-innovation-transforming-the-physical-world-with-open-source-hardware/</guid>
      <description>Powered by open source hardware and software, students, engineers, and garage tinkerers alike are hacking the physical world. Using inexpensive “mini computers” like the Arduino, these makers are building interactive devices that can sense and control other physical objects. In this presentation, we will look at opportunity the Open Source Hardware Movement has created for everyday people to hack our technological world. Ian McKay will introduce us to hacking the Arduino with a newbie how-to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IP Matters</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ip-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ip-matters/</guid>
      <description>Take an engaging journey into the world of intellectual property (IP) and software. What IP do you have and how can you protect it? Is it better to use a trademark, copyright or a patent? How long does it take and what does it cost? This presentation will introduce you to the types of IP and why they matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Work: Coworking</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</guid>
      <description>There is lots of buzz around coworking spaces as a new way for independent and SME creative professionals to engage work. Coworking is about shared office space for professionals, but it is also about a style of work that suggests there are greater opportunities working in a diverse community setting. Coworking spaces themself are diverse in structure, ranging from the community powered, real-estate centric, to highbred business incubators.&#xA;In rural Nova Scotia, numerous coworking spaces are springing up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to WordPress</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/introduction-to-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/introduction-to-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is a free content management system used by more than 23.3% of the top 10 million websites. In this talk, Sandy McFadden and Raina Noel will show us what is it, what it can do for you, and how you can start using it to get your message online.&#xA;You&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to install WordPress and get it setup using Posts, Pages, Widgets, and Menus. Raina and Sandy will also show us how you can extend Wordpress functionality and change the way your site looks with Plugins and Themes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEAM Powered! Maker Space / FabLab @AcadiaU</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/steam-powered-maker-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/steam-powered-maker-space/</guid>
      <description>The recent and explosive growth in maker-culture combined with the emergence of 3D Printing in Fabrication Laboratories (or “FabLabs”) presents an opportunity for the province to prepare for the future by investing in economic and cultural change in rural Nova Scotia. Acting in concert with the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre and the Centre for Rural Innovation, Acadia’s new STEAM Space is working toward the creation of a Maker Space/FabLab on the Acadia University campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTML5 and Semantic Markup</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/html5-and-semantic-markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/html5-and-semantic-markup/</guid>
      <description>Come join us for &amp;ldquo;HTML5 and Semantic Markup,&amp;rdquo; a discussion about HTML5, markup, and HTML5 websites that rock.&#xA;Open Web Platform: HTML5 and Semantic Markup Mike Caplan will give a talk about HTML5&amp;rsquo;s new elements and attributes that allow us to define semantically meaningful HTML. Semantics you say? What is the meaning of this? Come find out.&#xA;HTML5 Websites Show and Tell Dust off your favorite website that uses anything under the HTML5 sun – offline storage, connectivity, file access, semantics, audio/video, 3D/graphics, presentation, performance, big features, or small.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Projects Roundup: Round Two</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 19:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-two/</guid>
      <description>Come join us for &amp;ldquo;Local Projects Roundup - Round Two,&amp;rdquo; a discussion about interesting local web projects, platforms, business, and techies.&#xA;Online Community Engagement with Laura Churchill Duke Laura is the owner and operator of Valley Family Fun which is a website for families living in the Annapolis Valley. It includes resources, ideas, information and a calendar of family-friendly events. Started in January 2012, it has grown to include a Facebook and Twitter site to form a web-based network of over 6000 followers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Projects Roundup: Round One</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 19:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-one/</guid>
      <description>Come join us for Local Projects Roundup - Round One, a discussion about interesting local web projects, and initiatives supporting startups.&#xA;HUB Kentville with Frances Schagen Calling all forward-thinking entrepreneurs, start ups, creatives, artists, freelancers, coders and non-profits. HUB Kentville is a membership-based coworking spaces where people share an address, resources, equipment and community. HarvestHand with Michael Caplan Community Supported Agriculture (CSA) is a member based model for food production and distribution that unites local communities with local farms.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
