<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>innovacorp on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/innovacorp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in innovacorp on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/innovacorp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Richards</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/paul-richards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/paul-richards/</guid>
      <description>Paul Richards is innovacorp&amp;#39;s  regional manager for Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s Annapolis Valley and South Shore. In this role, Paul focuses on enabling knowledge-based companies to accelerate their growth and helping foster a dynamic high-growth entrepreneurial culture in the region.
Paul spent over 10 years working with the Acadia Centre for Social and Business Entrepreneurship (ACSBE) assisting businesses in rural Nova Scotia. In this role, Paul also worked to build the entrepreneurial capacity and infrastructure of several developing economies in Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Projects Roundup: Round One</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 19:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/local-projects-roundup-round-one/</guid>
      <description>Come join us for Local Projects Roundup - Round One, a discussion about interesting local web projects, and initiatives supporting startups.
  HUB Kentville with Frances Schagen  Calling all forward-thinking entrepreneurs, start ups, creatives, artists, freelancers, coders and non-profits. HUB Kentville  is a membership-based coworking spaces where people share an address, resources, equipment and community.     HarvestHand with Michael Caplan  Community Supported Agriculture (CSA) is a member based model for food production and distribution that unites local communities with local farms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>