<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>STEAM on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/steam/</link>
    <description>Recent content in STEAM on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/steam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>David Duke</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/david-duke/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/david-duke/</guid>
      <description>David Duke is an Associate Professor in the Department of History and Classics and as Coordinator of the university&amp;rsquo;s recently-established Environmental and Sustainability Studies program. His academic areas of expertise are the history of Russia and the USSR, the history of science, and environmental history, and he teaches in all these areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terry Weatherbee</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/terry-wetherbee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/terry-wetherbee/</guid>
      <description>Terry Weatherbee is a Professor in the Manning School of Business at Acadia University, and has a number of different research areas of interest including the negative impacts of technology use in organizations and the historiography of management thought. His most current research focuses on the disruptive impact of Maker Technology and its opportunities for economic development and academic/economic partnership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STEAM Powered! Maker Space / FabLab @AcadiaU</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/steam-powered-maker-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/steam-powered-maker-space/</guid>
      <description>The recent and explosive growth in maker-culture combined with the emergence of 3D Printing in Fabrication Laboratories (or “FabLabs”) presents an opportunity for the province to prepare for the future by investing in economic and cultural change in rural Nova Scotia. Acting in concert with the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre and the Centre for Rural Innovation, Acadia’s new STEAM Space is working toward the creation of a Maker Space/FabLab on the Acadia University campus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
