<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Entrepreneurship on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/entrepreneurship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entrepreneurship on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 18:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/entrepreneurship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Enter the Side Door</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-enter-the-side-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-enter-the-side-door/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Side Door is a digital platform that matches performing artists with venues to create shows anytime, anywhere, on their own terms.  Come meet CEO &amp;amp; Co-Founder &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson&#34;&gt;Laura Simpson&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; for a fireside chat and live performance with &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cassie-josephine&#34;&gt;Cassie Josephine&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; (Indie Folk Country princess).  Laura and Cassie will talk about the challenges artists in the music business face and how &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/side-door&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Side Door&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&amp;rsquo;s unique digital platform is defining a new business model capitalizing on the power of a networked community.  Learn how Side Door is poised to hit $1 million in annual ticket sales by the end of 2020.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Entrepreneur Chat over Beers</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-influencing-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-influencing-markets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this popup Startup Life entrepreneur chat over beers, we will be hosting Avery Schrader, a Nova Scotian living abroad in Tallinn, Estonia.  Estonia, for those not in the know, is a tiny Baltic state,  but in tech terms it&amp;rsquo;s a giant. It has a population of just 1.3 million, yet produces more start-ups per head than any other country in Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Avery is the founder of Modash, a tool that enables marketing teams to find and verify the audiences of over 50,000,000 influencers globally. Modash has raised $300,000 in funding from successful founders who have started companies like Pipedrive, Veriff, Yes.com and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Meet R2-Weed2</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-r2-weed2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-r2-weed2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Technology-driven agricultural experimentation.  Iterative product testing. Validated machine learning.  Pivot. Pivot. Pivot.  Welcome to the ag-tech startup world of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/teric-greenan&#34;&gt;Teric Greenan&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nexus-robotics&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Nexus Robotics&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/nexus-robotics&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Nexus Robotics&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;, Teric is applying Artificial Intelligence to building a reliable and cost-effective way to produce crops. Their autonomous robot R2-Weed2 is capable of cutting and spraying weeds, fertilizing crops, and collect data about growing conditions.  Teric will talk about his team&amp;rsquo;s start up journey, and the amazing technological innovations they are applying to revolutionize agriculture as we know it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avery Schrader</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/avery-schrader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/avery-schrader/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Whoop Whoop! You found me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have been starting businesses since I was 12, When I hijacked my moms old laptop to entertain myself while we lived in a barn. A few months later I accidentally started a business connecting people online playing a game that I loved. As a kid I sold Christmas trees, made maple syrup, started volunteer groups, and played in the woods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now I have an amazing team and a real vision.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richelle Brown Redden</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/richelle-brown-redden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/richelle-brown-redden/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Valley Regional Enterprise Network is the only publicly funded organization dedicated to supporting the local economic development of five municipalities and one First Nation in the Annapolis Valley region. Through the Valley Regional Enterprise Network’s BusinessNOW program Richelle helps businesses assess their needs, plan for success and fight the right resources.  As a publicly funded resource, the BusinessNOW services are offered at not cost to local businesses.  A combination of experience and passion to see the region grow, bring insight and dedication to her work with the BusinessNOW program.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of Our Digital Nation: Digital Nova Scotia 2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-our-digital-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-our-digital-nation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s digital economy is currently valued at $2.5 billion.  Tyler Farmer, Project Manager at Digital Nova Scotia, will present a state of our digital nation, reflecting on trends and opportunities, both urban and rural.  Join us for our last Refresh meetup for the 2018-2019 year for discussion and drinks care of our host, Annapolis Cider Company.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Innovating on The Internet</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/innovating-on-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/innovating-on-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have the next (big or small) idea, no budget, or development skills?  No problem &amp;ndash; you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t start with building anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this hands on workshop we will explore pre-product design tools that anyone can pick up to express their app idea.  With these tools you will walk away with a means to engage your user base to test concepts, gather feedback quickly, very inexpensively, and early on in the product cycle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Succeeding at Failing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/succeeding-at-failing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/succeeding-at-failing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Behind every entrepreneurial success lie the stories of numerous failures. As a mindset, entrepreneurship is characterized by risk-taking, experimentation, and continually challenging oneself to produce meaningful results. It is also about learning from failure, and, where possible, finding new ways to tackle problems that eventually lead to success.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Join &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/katelyn-bourgoin&#34;&gt;Katelyn Bourgoin&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;, a 3X founder/business owner turned growth strategist, for a discussion about how to think about entrepreneurship.  Come mingle with a wide cross section of Annapolis Valley entrepreneurs for drinks, networking, and old fashioned discussion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katelyn Bourgoin</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/katelyn-bourgoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/katelyn-bourgoin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Katelyn Bourgoin is a 3X founder/business owner turned growth strategist. She helps frustrated marketers and business owners to figure out why customers aren’t buying and how they can fix it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When companies know who their best customers are and what they &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; want, it becomes much easier to create awesome products and sell more of them. The result? Happier customers and more money in the bank.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Katelyn’s past clients include startups, small businesses, and Fortune 500s like Target and Holiday Inn. Suffice to say, she’s seen it all.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seed: Hacking Entrepreneurship in the Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/seed-hacking-entrepreneurship-in-the-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/seed-hacking-entrepreneurship-in-the-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seed&lt;/strong&gt; is a documentary that follows an international group of programmer entrepreneurs at AngelHack: one of the most competitive global hackathons and digital business ideation competitions. Three minutes to pitch. One shot to fund their proposals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seed&lt;/strong&gt; is also a gathering of our Annapolis Valley startup community.  The event will feature the diversity of associations, businesses, and individuals who comprise our digital tech startup community.  An assembly of our entrepreneurial family.  Come mingle and build your network.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Entrepreneurship: Turning Ideas into Action</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creative-entrepreneurship-turning-ideas-into-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creative-entrepreneurship-turning-ideas-into-action/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Problems and solutions.  In between are the numerous ideas that eventually lead to innovative solutions and new business opportunities.  Join the  &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; for a talk all about ideas.  Where do they come from?  How do we nurture them?  How can we turn them into problem solving new business?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Build your mad ideation skills at this workshop, then take them to &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.startituplaunchbox.com/&#34;&gt;Start It Up&lt;/a&gt;: our business ideation competition with $10K in prizes on the line.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founders Meetup: Lets Start a Business</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/founders-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/founders-meetup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this Hoist meetup, we will be doing something a little different.  We are looking for a few budding teen entrepreneurs to start a business.  This is the pitch:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Services supporting the business startup space in Rural Nova Scotia are diverse and not well represented as a whole.  Our business aims to unify the Western Nova business startup ecosystem by building a coherent communication platform.  By doing so, we will encourage entrepreneurship within our community.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoist Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/hoist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/hoist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hoist Annapolis Valley is a tech club for teens interested in coding, design and entrepreneurship. If you’re age 12 to 19 and have an interest in startups or coding, then come check it out! Everyone is welcome, and it’s free!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Meet up with Hoist members once per month at Acadia University&amp;rsquo;s Rural Innovation Centre &amp;ndash; like attending an tech + entrepreneurship class at university.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labs</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/labs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Refresh Annapolis Valley Labs is a playground where adventurous builders come to create.  Labs initiatives are community driven digital technology projects that tend to be entrepreneurial in nature.  In the lab, Refreshers work on building and applying their skills all while pursuing the objectives of their projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Refresh Annapolis Valley Labs is hosted at the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre Rural Innovation Centre.  We meet on Saturdays from 12:30 to 3:30 starting January 26.  Bring your laptop.  Pizza will be served.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Meetups</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/meetups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/meetups/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our monthly Refresh meetup is where the Annapolis Valley community of designers, developers and innovators come hang out.  Those interested in the creative, technical, and professional culture of digital technology endeavours in the Annapolis Valley meet and talk about all things design, technology, and entrepreneurship.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Refresh meets the second Tuesday evening of each month in the Wolfville area. These are casual affairs with short, member-interest talks followed by an opportunity to mingle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AEC has been developing and delivering workshops for business professionals, entrepreneurs, and not-for-profits for over 25 years. AEC continues to innovate and develop new and relevant programs for today’s business professional.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;rural-innovation-centre&#34;&gt;Rural Innovation Centre&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Rural Innovation Centre (RIC) supports entrepreneurs and businesses in the Annapolis Valley and on the South Shore by providing training, advisory and consulting services to small businesses, government and not-for-profit organizations. The Rural Innovation Centre is an incubator for start up companies to access working space and support, networking events, mentors and connect to Acadia faculty and facilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-valley-chamber-of-commerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/annapolis-valley-chamber-of-commerce/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce is a strong united voice for business and works to ensure that business thrives in the Annapolis Valley.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AVCC is a not-for-profit organization that provides member businesses with access to a variety of services such as group insurance, professional development and networking opportunities.  AVCC celebrates and promotes the accomplishments of business people and their contribution to the valley.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVCC Young Business Leaders</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/young-business-leaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/young-business-leaders/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce Young Business Leaders is a new committee that is exploring ways to connect to established business leaders for advice and mentorship.  The AVCC Young Business Leaders Committee will recognize, encourage and engage future business leaders.  The Young Business Leaders meet the last Tuesday of each month at noon at Gates Insurance, New Minas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cassie Josephine</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cassie-josephine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cassie-josephine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With “a voice that sits between Roy Orbison and Dolly Parton,” Cassie Josephine provides a vintage sound to her deeply personal narratives (Jeff Liberty - CBC). Her latest collection of songs, Only Half Blue, is one she thinks of fondly as a fairytale of middle-aged proportions. With her backing band, The Cry If I Want To’s, Cassie’s dreamy anthems are brought to life with soaring harmonies, violin, piano, and electric guitar.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy Lutes</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/jeremy-lutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/jeremy-lutes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jeremy Lutes is a Partner at Equilibrium Engineering. Jeremy has been successfully managing and operating businesses since 1998. Previous to Equilibrium, Jeremy was the Business Analyst for Internetworking Atlantic (IAI), a private Halifax based telecommunications company.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From a volunteer perspective, Jeremy was previously on the Board of Directors of the Halifax Pop Explosion for twelve years, and the Music Nova Scotia Board of Directors for three years. These positions illustrate a long-standing passion for the arts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launchbox</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/launchbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/launchbox/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Launchbox is the centre for student entrepreneurs, located on the 4th floor of Patterson Hall at Acadia University. We support students in their entrepreneurial pursuits by providing free programming, networking, access to mentors, and other entrepreneurs, working space and competitions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laura Simpson</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lover of music and truth. Listen to the poets. Founder of The Syrup Factory, Make.Do.Camp. and Side Door.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Laura Simpson is a music industry professional, living with her family in Halifax, Nova Scotia. She founded The Syrup Factory, which began hosting house concerts 2011 and offering strategy and services to artists in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She has been an organizer in the arts scene since she was 14, going to all-ages shows and then eventually taking live music photography and freelance writing about shows and artists. That led her to be a journalist for seven years, working for CBC and Rogers Radio.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah Tomkins</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/noah-tomkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/noah-tomkins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Originally from Dartmouth, Nova Scotia, Noah Tompkins is a fourth-year Entrepreneurship &amp;amp; Innovation major at Acadia University. His passion for sustainability and social enterprise has lead Noah to working as the Marketing Coordinator for Just Us! Coffee Roasters, becoming a project manager and presenter for Enacts Acadia, and the President of Fair Trade Acadia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sara Baxter</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sara-baxter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sara-baxter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A fourth year Accounting major, Sara Baxter from Moncton, New Brunswick, exercises her entrepreneurial skillset through Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre as the Community Entrepreneurship Developer. Her desire to create change and have a positive impact on society has led her to become a Project Co-Manager for Enacts Acadia&amp;rsquo;s Project Regenerate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Side Door</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/side-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/side-door/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Platform matching artists with spaces to create shows anytime, anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Side Door is a curated digital booking and ticketing platform used to facilitate booking and ticketing micro-performances in homes and other alternative venues in Canada and around the world. As a website and future mobile app, this technology-based company is innovating the traditional touring model for performers, live performances, and fan experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Artists and Hosts sign up for free online through the Side Door website by creating profiles and answering questions about their preferences for performing or presenting a show in a house or alternative space (think bookstores, warehouses, parks, libraries, community centres, etc). The platform automatically matches Artists and Hosts based on their mutual profile preferences. Once matched, they are notified of the match, and prompted to discuss the details of booking a show together. Not only is Side Door a booking tool, but the online platform also has a booking contract and ticketing component that allows the Host to advertise and sell tickets. Fans will be able to visit the website or download the app to view shows in their area and shows they have been invited to, and they can buy tickets instantly online. Once the show is over the Host, Artist, and fans are all asked to provide feedback on the attended show.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Farmer</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tyler-farmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tyler-farmer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the last year and a half, Tyler has lead Digital Nova Scotia’s projects and skill development programs across Nova Scotia. Through this role, Tyler has had the opportunity to connect with a wide variety of ICT &amp;amp; digital tech companies, professional service providers, community leaders, and government agencies which has enabled him to build an effective grassroots network with a birds-eye perspective of the economic challenges facing the province. Prior to diving into the rewarding work of economic development through Nova Scotia’s IT association, Tyler coordinated inspection, expediting, and project management services for many of Canada’s leading oil and gas companies in Alberta. In his spare time, Tyler is often found running all over Halifax training for the Scotiabank Bluenose Marathon, scouting for the perfect photo opportunity in Cape Breton or passionately keeping up with the growing Canadian independent journalism and startup scenes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
