<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R-bar on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/r-bar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R-bar on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/r-bar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding The World Through R</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/understanding-the-world-through-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/understanding-the-world-through-r/</guid>
      <description>The world is bubbling over with data. When analyzed, data can provide the inquiring mind with useful information that can suggest outcomes and support decision-making. Be it the data generated about business practices, human behaviours, the biological world; being able to understand what your data is telling you is incredibly empowering. &amp;ldquo;R&amp;rdquo; is a free, accessible, and powerful programming language that offers a suite of tools for data analysis.
Our tour guide, Trevor Avery &amp;mdash; biostatistician, faculty member at Acadia University, and coordinator of R-bar  &amp;mdash; will provide us a primer on R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Avery</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/trevor-avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/trevor-avery/</guid>
      <description>Trevor Avery is a marine biologist (Ph.D.) and biostatistician (P.Stat.) with a variety of research interests. U. of Guelph was home for his undergraduate Honours, Acadia U. for an M.Sc. (under Mike Dadswell) and Memorial U. for his Ph.D. (with Joe Brown, r.i.p.); Currently he is back with Acadia as an Associate Professor cross appointed within the faculties of Biology and Mathematics &amp;amp; Statistics.
Technology and analysis techniques (statistics) play a significant role in most of his research projects, but not all.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>