<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech-Ed on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/tech-ed/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech-Ed on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/tech-ed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Refresh 2025 - 2026 Youth Cohort</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/cohort-2025-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 12:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/cohort-2025-2026/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Refresh Annapolis Valley offers Computer Science courses to small cohorts of youth learners over the academic year.&#xA;The courses offered include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creative Computing&lt;/strong&gt;: An introductory Computer Science course for younger learners using the Scratch programming environment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scratch Masters&lt;/strong&gt;: Advanced course for young learners focused on Scratch, physical hardware programming with Microbits, and retro video game development.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Build Arcade&lt;/strong&gt;: An introductory Computer Science course for High School learners using Makecode Arcade to build retro style video games.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Build Web&lt;/strong&gt;: Advanced course for High School learners interested in building websites and web applications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build: Arcade - March Break Intensive</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/break-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/break-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Build: Arcade is an introductory Computer Science course for Middle (grades 5 to 8) or High School learners.  Using Makecode Arcade, we&#xA;will build retro style video games.  While exploring the early history of video games, we will learn the fundamentals of&#xA;the Makecode Arcade game development engine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Makecode Arcade is a great first step into the world of video game development, as well as the larger world of Computer&#xA;Science.  No prior coding experience necessary.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refresh 2024 - 2025 Youth Cohort</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/cohort-2024-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/cohort-2024-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the past several years, Refresh Annapolis Valley has been offering courses to small cohorts of learners over the academic year.&#xA;The courses offered include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creative Computing&lt;/strong&gt;: An introductory Computer Science course for younger learners using the Scratch programming environment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scratch Masters&lt;/strong&gt;: Advanced course for young learners focused on Scratch, physical hardware programming with Microbits, and retro video game development.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Build Arcade&lt;/strong&gt;: An introductory Computer Science course for High School learners using Makecode Arcade to build retro style video games.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Build Web&lt;/strong&gt;: Advanced course for High School learners interested in building websites and web applications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;format&#34;&gt;Format&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Class size is restricted to 6 maximum to facilitate a hands-on learning environment between mentors and learners.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Fall 2023</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-fall-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-fall-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to&#xA;the computer sciences.  This course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid&#xA;young people (grades 4 to 6) in learning the basics of software development.  Scratch is used over the world by&#xA;students to easily create interactive artwork, interactive stories, and video games while acting as a stepping stone&#xA;to the more advanced world of computer science.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scratch Masters Course 2023</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/masters-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/masters-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Scratch Masters is the next level course for graduates of the Creative Computing program.  Within this course we continue&#xA;to explore the world of the computer sciences.  This course uses the popular &lt;a href=&#34;https://scratch.mit.edu/&#34;&gt;Scratch&lt;/a&gt; programming environment to aid&#xA;young people (grades 4 to 6) in learning the more advanced concepts of Scratch software development.  Scratch is used over the world by&#xA;students to easily create interactive artwork, interactive stories, and video games while acting as a stepping stone&#xA;to the more advanced world of computer science.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Summer Bootcamp 2023</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-summer-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-summer-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to&#xA;the computer sciences.  This course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid&#xA;young people (grades 4 to 6) in learning the basics of software development.  Scratch is used over the world by&#xA;students to easily create interactive artwork, interactive stories, and video games while acting as a stepping stone&#xA;to the more advanced world of computer science.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Video Games</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/building-video-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/building-video-games/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/video-game-development-with-godot/&#34;&gt;last 6-week intensive intro to video game development with godot&lt;/a&gt; left&#xA;a waiting list of others behind who wanted in.  We are opening up a section for a new small cohort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are you interested in video games, programming, or creating virtual experiences? Take your skills to the next level with this beginner Godot course! Learn the fundamentals of game design, the ins and outs of the Godot game engine, and create your own video game in the process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Game Dev With Godot</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/video-game-development-with-godot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/video-game-development-with-godot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you interested in video games, programming, or creating virtual experiences? Take your skills to the next level with this beginner Godot course! Learn the fundamentals of game design, the ins and outs of the Godot game engine, and create your own video game in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-godot&#34;&gt;What is Godot&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Godot is a free game engine that enables you to create any 2D or 3D experience you can dream up. It’s an all in one tool for building games for many different platforms such as desktop, mobile, and the web. Godot is friendly to beginners, and gives you the power to make amazing things.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scratch Masters 2023 - 2024</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to be opening up our Winter 2023 Creative Computing Course for registration for the Wolfville&#xA;School community.  This is our 6th year offering this popular course.  Unlike other years, we will be running 1&#xA;cohort of learners for &lt;em&gt;free&lt;/em&gt; for Wolfville School Students. Registration is open until Jan. 27.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to&#xA;the computer sciences.  This course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid&#xA;young people (grades 4 to 6) in learning the basics of software development.  Scratch is used over the world by&#xA;students to easily create interactive artwork, interactive stories, and video games while acting as a stepping stone&#xA;to the more advanced world of computer science.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comp Sci Education Week - Build a micro:bit Mini Crane</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creating-mini-crane-with-the-microbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creating-mini-crane-with-the-microbit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you interested in robotics or do you enjoy messing around with electronics? In this workshop, you&amp;rsquo;ll assemble both the hardware and software needed to create a miniature crane controlled by the micro:bit microcontroller.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Join us as we kick off Computer Science Education Week with this hands on workshop.  We are limited to 10 spots, so act fast!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-a-microbit&#34;&gt;What is a micro:bit?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The micro:bit is a small, compact computer based on a 43 mm × 52 mm circuit board. The board is easy to program and has several cool hardware features such as a processor, radio and Bluetooth antenna, 25 LED lights, two buttons, a compass, an accelerometer, and, the best feature, an edge connector used to power a wide variety of external hardware.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUILD: Computer Science Camp for Girls</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/camp-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/camp-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BUILD is a week long dive into the world of Computer Science for girls 11 to 14.  We will explore the basics of software development while building interactive artwork and literature, video games, and software that interacts with the physical world.  Through our exploration we will also journey through use of hardware, refine our ideation skills and turn our ideas into software.  Campers will also connect with Computer Scientists in our community who are changing the world one algorithm at a time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Camp 2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/camp-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/camp-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Computing Camp is a week long adventure into the world of Computer Science.  Using the popular Scratch programming environment as a starting point, we will build interactive artwork and stories, video games, and software that interacts with the physical world.  Through our exploration of the creativity of software development, we will learn about where ideas come from, and how to turn ideas into action.  We will explore the world beyond Scratch, including 3D design, printing, and virtual reality.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming Hardware with Python</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/programming-hardware-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/programming-hardware-with-python/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wanted to know how to make code interact with the real world? In this introductory workshop to Python programming, you’ll learn the vital stepping stones to controlling hardware using the Circuit Playground microcontroller (microcomputer) with one of the most robust, versatile, and popular programming languages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-a-circuit-playground&#34;&gt;What is a Circuit Playground?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Circuit Playground is a microcontroller, or a tiny computer. This computer can easily be programmed to interact with hardware that you connect to it. Not only that, but the Circuit Playground comes equipped with various electronics and other hardware already built into it. It has multiple sensors (motion sensors, temperature sensors, sound sensors, etc), an infrared receiver/transmitter, push buttons, a speaker, input/output pins (by which you would attach external hardware to), a micro USB port, and several LEDs all on a 5 cm in diameter circuit board!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexander Petkov</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/alexander-petkov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/alexander-petkov/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Alexander Petkov is a high school student who attends Horton High School and is one of the co-founders of &lt;a href=&#34;https://sparkwest.network/&#34;&gt;Spark West Network&lt;/a&gt;, a non-profit organization that aims to pull together the diverse organizations, events, and opportunities present in the Annapolis Valley. He is also the Chief Marketing Officer for Refresh Annapolis Valley.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#ScratchFest</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;calling-all-digital-builders&#34;&gt;Calling all Digital Builders&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;#ScratchFest&lt;/em&gt; is a weekend (April 6th and April 7th) Build-a-thon for kids and teens interested in creating amazing original work with digital technologies, such as the Scratch programming environment, Processing, Virtual Reality, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During &lt;em&gt;#ScartchFest&lt;/em&gt;, participants will brainstorm an idea, develop their project, and showcase a final prototype.  This weekend warrior event provides an excellent opportunity for coders to invent their own projects and demonstrate their knowledge within a collaborative, creative, and playful environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Course 2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to be opening up our 2019 Creative Computing Course for registration.  This is our 3rd year offering this popular course.  Unlike other years, we will be running 2 cohorts of learners for &lt;em&gt;free&lt;/em&gt;.  One cohort will be a mixed class of girls and boys.  The second will be for girls.  Registration is open until Jan. 2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to the computer sciences.  Broken up into 7 units, this course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid young people (aged 8 to 12) in learning the basics of software development.  Scratch is used over the world by students to easily create interactive artwork, interactive stories, and video games while acting as a stepping stone to the more advanced world of computer science.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUILD: Computer Science Camp for Girls</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/camp-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/camp-2018/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img class=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/images/event/hoist/camp-2018/poster.png&#34; alt=&#34;Format&#34; align=&#34;right&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;BUILD is a week long dive into the world of Computer Science for girls 11 to 13.  We will explore the basics of software development while building interactive artwork and stories, video games, and software that interacts with the physical world.  Through our exploration we will also journey through use of hardware, refine our ideation skills and turn our ideas into software.  Campers will also connect with Computer Scientists in our community who are changing the world one algorithm at a time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Camp 2018</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/camp-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/camp-2018/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Computing Camp is a week long adventure into the world of Computer Science.  Using the popular Scratch programming environment to master the basics of software development, we will build interactive artwork and stories, video games, and software that interacts with the physical world.  Through our exploration of the creativity of software development, we will learn about where ideas come from, and how to turn ideas into action.  Campers will also connect with Computer Scientists in our community who are changing the world one algorithm at a time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#ScratchFest</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2018/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0O9qtmW4tSY?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;calling-all-digital-builders&#34;&gt;Calling all Digital Builders&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;#ScratchFest&lt;/em&gt; is a weekend (June 23th and June 24th) Build-a-thon for kids and teens interested in creating amazing original work with digital technologies, such as the Scratch programming environment, Processing, Virtual Reality, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During &lt;em&gt;#ScartchFest&lt;/em&gt;, participants will brainstorm an idea, develop their project, and showcase a final prototype.  This weekend warrior event provides an excellent opportunity for coders to invent their own projects and demonstrate their knowledge within a collaborative, creative, and playful environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Course 2018</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2018/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to the computer sciences.  Broken up into 7 units, this course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid young people (aged 8 to 13) in learning the basics of software development.  Scratch is used over the world by students to easily create interactive artwork, interactive stories, and video games while acting as a stepping stone to the more advanced world of computer science.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#ScratchFest</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/scratchfest-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/rpkvmw65RLI?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;calling-all-scratchers&#34;&gt;Calling all Scratchers&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;#ScratchFest&lt;/em&gt; is a weekend (June 24th and June 25th) Scratch-a-thon for kids interested in creating amazing original work with the Scratch programming environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During &lt;em&gt;#ScartchFest&lt;/em&gt;, kids will brainstorm an idea, develop their project, and showcase a final prototype.  This weekend warrior event provides an excellent opportunity for Scratch coders to invent their own projects and demonstrate their knowledge in Scratch within a collaborative, creative, and playful environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing Course 2017</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/cc/course-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Computing is a course developed by an international network of educators passionate about exposing kids to the computer sciences.  Broken up into 7 units, this course uses the popular Scratch programming environment to aid young people (aged 8 to 13) in learning the basics of software development.  Scratch is used over the world by students to easily create animations and games while acting as a stepping stone to the more advanced world of computer science.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Computing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/creative-computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/creative-computing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Computing is a series of programs (courses, workshops, and events) geared towards kids 8 to 13 focused on exposing them to the amazing world of computer science.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoist Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/hoist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/hoist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hoist Annapolis Valley is a tech club for teens interested in coding, design and entrepreneurship. If you’re age 12 to 19 and have an interest in startups or coding, then come check it out! Everyone is welcome, and it’s free!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Meet up with Hoist members once per month at Acadia University&amp;rsquo;s Rural Innovation Centre &amp;ndash; like attending an tech + entrepreneurship class at university.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labs</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/labs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Refresh Annapolis Valley Labs is a playground where adventurous builders come to create.  Labs initiatives are community driven digital technology projects that tend to be entrepreneurial in nature.  In the lab, Refreshers work on building and applying their skills all while pursuing the objectives of their projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Refresh Annapolis Valley Labs is hosted at the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre Rural Innovation Centre.  We meet on Saturdays from 12:30 to 3:30 starting January 26.  Bring your laptop.  Pizza will be served.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Robotics Program</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Robot Programming Competition mission is to increase interest in building digital technology and computer science by engaging Nova Scotia students in annual robotics programming competitions and related activities that feature problem solving and teamwork.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Acadia Robotics Program, through the Jodrey School of Computer Science, depends heavily on financial support from external organizations and the committed volunteers who annually contribute to the season from late August through to mid-June.  We have a junior program, FIRST® LEGO® League, and a senior program, Robofest. All the outreach throughout the season culminates in a Provincial Robot Programming Championship here at Acadia Unversity each February, involving over 400 participants, 100 volunteers, media and many organizations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr Daniel Silver</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-daniel-silver/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-daniel-silver/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Daniel L. Silver is the Director of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-institute-for-data-analytics&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Acadia Institute for Data Analytics&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;.  He is also a Professor in and currently the Acting-Director of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Jodrey School of Computer Science&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; at Acadia University.   His areas of research and application are machine learning, data mining, and data analytics.   His expertise is in Lifelong Machine Learning and Transfer Learning.   He has published over 65 scientific papers and has co-chaired or been part of program committees for a number of national and international conferences, seminars and workshops on data mining and machine learning.   He was the President of the Canadian Artificial Intelligence Association (CAIAC) from 2009-11. In 2011, he received the Science Champion Award from the Nova Scotia Discovery Center for his work on youth robotics and the advancement of STEM education.  In December, 2014, he became an Honorary Colonel in the RCAF attached to 14 Wing Software Engineering Squadron, in Greenwood, NS.  In June of 2016, was awarded Canadian AI’s Distinguished Service Award.  Danny has over 30 years of experience in information technology, project management and business administration.  Since 1993, he has worked on machine learning and data mining projects in the private and public sector providing situation analysis and problem definition, project management and guidance, and data mining services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr Darcy Benoit</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-darcy-benoit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-darcy-benoit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Darcy Benoit is a Professor in and the Director of the Jodrey School of Computer Science at Acadia University.  His areas of research include mobile application development, database management systems, and computer science education. An avid supporter educational outreach, Darcy oversees the Acadia Robotics program, a province-wide outreach program that sees approximately 400 students from grades 9-18 compete in two international robot programming competitions. His outreach work resulted in him collaborating with the Nova Scotia Department of Education and Early Childhood Development on the implementation of computer programming in the public school system from grades 7-12. Dr. Benoit is also involved in faculty development research, and is an avid promoter of teaching development, particularly as it pertains to teaching computer science.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ian McKay</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ian-mckay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ian-mckay/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“Creative Technician”&amp;hellip;what the heck is that?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I see my role, primarily, as that of a possibilitist. I listen closely to your ideas, what you hope to create, the problem you are working and then share with you the possibilities technology may offer. My years of immersion in Maker culture, joyfully exploring new and unusual uses for the wonders of emerging and age-old tech, provide me with a deep pool of possible solutions to your creative problems. While I am happy to help suggest solutions and inform you of the possibilities and challenges, I always keep in mind that the piece is YOUR work and will strive to help YOUR vision come to fruition. In those cases where a more collaborative model is what you are seeking, I would love to work with you to make our ideas a reality.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jodrey School of Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Jodrey School of Computer Science prepares students for today&amp;rsquo;s ever changing world of technology in a unique, fully mobile computing environment. Students develop a thorough understanding of computer systems software, modern software design methods and computer systems software.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Students in all degree programs complete a self-directed project during the course of their studies. This provides students with the opportunity to work closely with professors and to apply knowledge acquired through experiment and real-life application. Many students work on projects that end up in the public domain as open-source applications, free for everyone to download. Some students complete research work that becomes an integral part of their supervisor&amp;rsquo;s research, leading to publications in conferences and journals.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max Caplan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/max-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/max-caplan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Max! I&amp;rsquo;m a full stack web developer and designer with over 3 years of freelance experience and a lifetime of passion for building things!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I really enjoy learning new things and problem solving as a developer. As a designer, I love creating unique and engaging experiences. I am a very detail oriented person who puts a lot of emphasis into how people interact with the things I make.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mrugakshee Palwe</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mrugakshee-palwe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mrugakshee-palwe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Mrugakshee Palwe. I started investing my time in understanding the blockchain technology in mid-2018.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Graduated with a degree in computer science in spring 2018&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Received a scholarship for Consensys academy’s 2018 Developer Bootcamp in October 2018.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Certificate of Proficiency from  Ethereum Blockchain Developer Bootcamp - Feb 2019&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Forked and customized the Bitshares, Graphene, and Peerplays blockchains&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Co-founded Atlantic Blockchain Company Inc. in November 2018&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
