<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Ed on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshav.github.io/topics/tech-ed/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech Ed on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshav.github.io/topics/tech-ed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Robotics Program</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Robot Programming Competition mission is to increase interest in building digital technology and computer science by engaging Nova Scotia students in annual robotics programming competitions and related activities that feature problem solving and teamwork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Acadia Robotics Program, through the Jodrey School of Computer Science, depends heavily on financial support from external organizations and the committed volunteers who annually contribute to the season from late August through to mid-June.  We have a junior program, FIRST® LEGO® League, and a senior program, Robofest. All the outreach throughout the season culminates in a Provincial Robot Programming Championship here at Acadia Unversity each February, involving over 400 participants, 100 volunteers, media and many organizations.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/qA3L8_KJB4c&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jodrey School of Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Jodrey School of Computer Science prepares students for today&amp;rsquo;s ever changing world of technology in a unique, fully mobile computing environment. Students develop a thorough understanding of computer systems software, modern software design methods and computer systems software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Students in all degree programs complete a self-directed project during the course of their studies. This provides students with the opportunity to work closely with professors and to apply knowledge acquired through experiment and real-life application. Many students work on projects that end up in the public domain as open-source applications, free for everyone to download. Some students complete research work that becomes an integral part of their supervisor&amp;rsquo;s research, leading to publications in conferences and journals.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>