<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Max Caplan on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/people/max-caplan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Max Caplan on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 19:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/people/max-caplan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building Video Games</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/building-video-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 19:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/building-video-games/</guid>
      <description>Our last 6-week intensive intro to video game development with godot left a waiting list of others behind who wanted in. We are opening up a section for a new small cohort.&#xA;Are you interested in video games, programming, or creating virtual experiences? Take your skills to the next level with this beginner Godot course! Learn the fundamentals of game design, the ins and outs of the Godot game engine, and create your own video game in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Game Dev With Godot</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/video-game-development-with-godot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 19:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/hoist/video-game-development-with-godot/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in video games, programming, or creating virtual experiences? Take your skills to the next level with this beginner Godot course! Learn the fundamentals of game design, the ins and outs of the Godot game engine, and create your own video game in the process.&#xA;What is Godot Godot is a free game engine that enables you to create any 2D or 3D experience you can dream up. It’s an all in one tool for building games for many different platforms such as desktop, mobile, and the web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comp Sci Education Week - Build a micro:bit Mini Crane</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creating-mini-crane-with-the-microbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/creating-mini-crane-with-the-microbit/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in robotics or do you enjoy messing around with electronics? In this workshop, you&amp;rsquo;ll assemble both the hardware and software needed to create a miniature crane controlled by the micro:bit microcontroller.&#xA;Join us as we kick off Computer Science Education Week with this hands on workshop. We are limited to 10 spots, so act fast!&#xA;What is a micro:bit? The micro:bit is a small, compact computer based on a 43 mm × 52 mm circuit board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming Hardware with Python</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/programming-hardware-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 12:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/programming-hardware-with-python/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to know how to make code interact with the real world? In this introductory workshop to Python programming, you’ll learn the vital stepping stones to controlling hardware using the Circuit Playground microcontroller (microcomputer) with one of the most robust, versatile, and popular programming languages.&#xA;What is a Circuit Playground? The Circuit Playground is a microcontroller, or a tiny computer. This computer can easily be programmed to interact with hardware that you connect to it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Digital to Physical: 3D Design and Printing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/from-digital-to-physical-3d-printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/from-digital-to-physical-3d-printing/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new world of of 3D printing, where you can produce 3D objects almost as easily as you can dream of them. In this hands on workshop we will:&#xA;Learn about how 3D printing is shaking up different industries Types of 3D printing technologies How to design for printing How to print your designs Bring a laptop and be prepared to roll up your sleeves. Space is limited to 20 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Developer Bootcamp: Part 3 of 3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-3-of-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-3-of-3/</guid>
      <description>In this teen Hoist mini series, you will learn about how to build your own web application. Web applications are unlike traditional websites. Traditional websites are largely informational (like the Refresh Annapolis Valley website) where web applications solve particular problems (think Gmail for email).&#xA;In part 1, you will learn the ins-and-outs of building app interfaces In part 2, you will learn how to add interactivity to your web app In part 3, you will learn how to manage app data If you haven&amp;rsquo;t attended part 1 or 2, you can jump right into part 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Developer Bootcamp: Part 2 of 3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-2-of-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-2-of-3/</guid>
      <description>In this teen Hoist mini series, you will learn about how to build your own web application. Web applications are unlike traditional websites. Traditional websites are largely informational (like the Refresh Annapolis Valley website) where web applications solve particular problems (think Gmail for email).&#xA;In part 1, you will learn the ins-and-outs of building app interfaces In part 2, you will learn how to add interactivity to your web app In part 3, you will learn how to manage app data If you haven&amp;rsquo;t attended part 1, you can jump right into part 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Developer Bootcamp: Part 1 of 3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-1-of-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/app-developer-bootcamp-part-1-of-3/</guid>
      <description>In this teen Hoist mini series, you will learn about how to build your own web application. Web applications are unlike traditional websites. Traditional websites are largely informational (like the Refresh Annapolis Valley website) where web applications solve particular problems (think Gmail for email).&#xA;In part 1, you will learn the ins-and-outs of building app interfaces In part 2, you will learn how to add interactivity to your web app In part 3, you will learn how to manage app data Pizza + workshop + building</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>f5://imagination</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 10:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</guid>
      <description>f5://imagination is a pop up exhibit focused on digital creativity. This one day temporary exhibit features work from digital artists, makers, scratchers, computer scientists, engineers and pretendgineer, hardware hackers, lego robotics warriors, indy game developers, new media innovators, VR and AR pioneers&amp;hellip; digital builders of all shapes, sizes, and credentials.&#xA;Schedule 10 AM to 12:30 PM Screening &amp; discussion of Hidden Figures: The story of a team of female African-American mathematicians who served a vital role in NASA during the early years of the U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against Flat Screens: Learn 3D Design</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/against-flat-screens-learn-3d-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/against-flat-screens-learn-3d-design/</guid>
      <description>In this Hoist teen design talk, Max Caplan will introduce us to 3D design using Blender. Blender is a professional 3D computer graphics software used for creating animated films, visual effects, art, 3D printed models, interactive 3D applications and video games. Max will walk us through installing, using, and designing your first Blender project: an awesome robot.&#xA;Pizza + workshop + building&#xA;Bring your own laptop. A small number of laptops will be available to borrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maker Meetup</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/maker-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/maker-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Calling all makers, inventors, artists, entrepreneurs, tinkerers, and the like. Join Refresh Annapolis Valley and Annapolis Valley STEAMspace for what we hope will be a regular meetup for the Valley maker community to gather, share ideas, and build community.&#xA;Projects galore to explore!&#xA;Ian McKay will be demoing a magic cauldron, CNC stuff and a possible new product. Max Caplan will show off a homebrew handheld gaming console. And you&amp;hellip;?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
