<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Nova Scotia on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/digital-nova-scotia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Nova Scotia on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/digital-nova-scotia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>State of Our Digital Nation: Digital Nova Scotia 2019</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-our-digital-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-our-digital-nation/</guid>
      <description>Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s digital economy is currently valued at $2.5 billion. Tyler Farmer, Project Manager at Digital Nova Scotia, will present a state of our digital nation, reflecting on trends and opportunities, both urban and rural. Join us for our last Refresh meetup for the 2018-2019 year for discussion and drinks care of our host, Annapolis Cider Company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Succeeding at Failing</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/succeeding-at-failing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/succeeding-at-failing/</guid>
      <description>Behind every entrepreneurial success lie the stories of numerous failures. As a mindset, entrepreneurship is characterized by risk-taking, experimentation, and continually challenging oneself to produce meaningful results. It is also about learning from failure, and, where possible, finding new ways to tackle problems that eventually lead to success.&#xA;Join Katelyn Bourgoin , a 3X founder/business owner turned growth strategist, for a discussion about how to think about entrepreneurship. Come mingle with a wide cross section of Annapolis Valley entrepreneurs for drinks, networking, and old fashioned discussion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seed: Hacking Entrepreneurship in the Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/seed-hacking-entrepreneurship-in-the-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 18:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/seed-hacking-entrepreneurship-in-the-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>Seed is a documentary that follows an international group of programmer entrepreneurs at AngelHack: one of the most competitive global hackathons and digital business ideation competitions. Three minutes to pitch. One shot to fund their proposals.&#xA;Seed is also a gathering of our Annapolis Valley startup community. The event will feature the diversity of associations, businesses, and individuals who comprise our digital tech startup community. An assembly of our entrepreneurial family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CODE: Debugging the Gender Gap</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</guid>
      <description>CODE: Debugging The Gender Gap exposes the dearth of female and minority software engineers and explores the reasons for this gender gap and digital divide.&#xA;Tech jobs are growing three times faster than our colleges are producing computer science graduates. By 2019 there will be 182,000 jobs in information and communications technology that will go unfilled by homegrown Canadian talent because not enough people will have the right skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Farmer</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tyler-farmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/tyler-farmer/</guid>
      <description>For the last year and a half, Tyler has lead Digital Nova Scotia’s projects and skill development programs across Nova Scotia. Through this role, Tyler has had the opportunity to connect with a wide variety of ICT &amp;amp; digital tech companies, professional service providers, community leaders, and government agencies which has enabled him to build an effective grassroots network with a birds-eye perspective of the economic challenges facing the province. Prior to diving into the rewarding work of economic development through Nova Scotia’s IT association, Tyler coordinated inspection, expediting, and project management services for many of Canada’s leading oil and gas companies in Alberta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia/</guid>
      <description>Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia (BA, MA) is the President &amp;amp; CEO of Digital Nova Scotia . She’s a multilingual senior level executive with over 20 years of combined experience in the private, public &amp;amp; academic sectors. Her career spans five geographic regions: America (North), Africa (South), Middle East, Asia &amp;amp; Europe.&#xA;Ulrike thrives on challenges! With a proven track record in International Marketing, Business &amp;amp; Economic Development, Channel Management, Government/Stakeholder Relations, Board Governance, Fundraising, Organizational Growth &amp;amp; Public Speaking, she&amp;rsquo;s a true game-changer.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
