<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Nova Scotia on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshav.github.io/organizations/digital-nova-scotia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Nova Scotia on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:30:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshav.github.io/organizations/digital-nova-scotia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>CODE: Debugging the Gender Gap</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;figure class=&#34;float-right&#34;&gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/images/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/poster.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;CODE: Debugging the Gender Gap&#34; /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE: Debugging The Gender Gap&lt;/em&gt; exposes the dearth of female and minority
software engineers and explores the reasons for this gender gap and digital divide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tech jobs are growing three times faster than our colleges are producing computer science
graduates. By 2019 there will be 182,000 jobs in information and communications technology
that will go unfilled by homegrown Canadian talent because not enough people will have the right skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through compelling interviews, artistic animation and clever flashpoints in popular culture,
&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; examines the reasons why more girls and people of color are not seeking out
opportunities in computer science and explores how cultural mindsets, stereotypes,
educational hurdles, and sexism all play roles in this national crisis. Expert voices from the
worlds of tech, psychology, science, and education are intercut with personal stories of women
who are engaged in the fight to challenge complacency in the tech industry and have their
voices heard. &lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; aims to inspire change in mindsets, in the educational system, in startup
culture and in the way women see themselves in the field of coding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This screening will feature an introductory keynote address by &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia&#34;&gt;Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia&lt;/a&gt;
,
President and CEO of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/digital-nova-scotia&#34;&gt;
    
        Digital Nova Scotia
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, to provide Canadian context to the film.
&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; will also be followed by an interactive panel discussion.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/123004482&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Computer code forms the foundation of modern society. Cell phones, apps, navigation systems,
medical equipment, banking, movie animation… are all driven by code. The more diverse a
team of coders is, the broader their perspective of society’s needs, which can ultimately result
in products that serve a greater breadth of humanity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; takes a hard look at the pipeline question in technology: why aren’t there more women
and minority graduates in computer science? What is stopping them from getting to the
threshold? &lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; follows the various challenges faced by a new generation of women
programmers and the ingenious ways they are using their skills, drive, intellect and vision to
disrupt the traditional, male-dominated tech world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; looks to the past, delving into the history of computing to highlight women like Ada
Lovelace and Grace Hopper who set the stage for today’s technology. &lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; acknowledges that
women have been an important part of computing since the genesis of computers, but have
since been written out of this history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; is not afraid to ask the hard questions and does so with intelligence and a sense of
humor, examining our culture from high (the views of former Harvard President Larry Summers
on innate ability) to low (an app called &amp;ldquo;Titstare&amp;rdquo; presented to a room of tech heavyweights).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A blend of personal stories, expert voices, innovative animation, historic discoveries, and
moments from popular culture are complemented with a cutting edge musical score and
bolstered by a strong sense of purpose. &lt;em&gt;CODE&lt;/em&gt; reflects, at its heart, the interconnectedness of
the stories, the web, and by proxy, the shared vision of a new, more democratic community
made possible by the inclusion of more women in code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia (BA, MA) is the President &amp;amp; CEO of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/digital-nova-scotia&#34;&gt;
    
        Digital Nova Scotia
    
&lt;/a&gt;
. She’s a multilingual senior level executive with over 20 years of combined experience in the private, public &amp;amp; academic sectors. Her career spans five geographic regions: America (North), Africa (South), Middle East, Asia &amp;amp; Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ulrike thrives on challenges! With a proven track record in International Marketing, Business &amp;amp; Economic Development, Channel Management, Government/Stakeholder Relations, Board Governance, Fundraising, Organizational Growth &amp;amp; Public Speaking, she&amp;rsquo;s a true game-changer. Having lived, worked &amp;amp; studied in the USA, the UK, the Netherlands, Germany, Israel &amp;amp; now Canada, Ulrike has combined her passion for inclusive diversity, entrepreneurship, innovation, new technologies &amp;amp; STEAM-education with her keen ambition to help individuals &amp;amp; businesses succeed in local &amp;amp; global markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ulrike has worked in executive leadership roles at the headquarters of prominent technology multinationals, SMEs &amp;amp; Startups, including Intel, Compaq/HP, RAD Data Communications, Commtouch Software, McAfee &amp;amp; Seaside Wireless. Her diverse sector expertise in software, hardware &amp;amp; networking products in ICT companies &amp;amp; software development in med-tech, aerospace &amp;amp; defense industries, provides her with first-hand experience &amp;amp; insight into the multi-sectoral facets of the ICT sector &amp;amp; its magnitude of opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2015: Ulrike was honoured with the WXN Canada’s Most Powerful Women: Top 100 Award, the RBC Top 25 Canadian Immigrant Award, the national WCT Top 15 Leadership Excellence Award: Innovator &amp;amp; the Atlantic Business Magazine Top 50 CEO Award. 2014: Ulrike was a recipient of the Progress Women of Excellence Award: Innovator/Entrepreneur, named 1 of Canada’s top 40 Change-Makers by Canadian Living, and received the Mannesmann Teaching Award (USA) &amp;amp; Fulbright Scholarship (USA) while pursuing her M.A.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ulrike is an elected member of the International Women’s Forum &amp;amp; sits on Industry Advisory Boards with Dalhousie University &amp;amp; the Saint Mary&amp;rsquo;s University Sobey School of Business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ulrike is married and has two children. She moved with her family from Israel to Nova Scotia in 2002.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>