<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 12:30:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Computer Science Course For Girls Announced</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/post/free-computer-science-course-for-girls-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/post/free-computer-science-course-for-girls-announced/</guid>
      <description>Wolfville, NS, (Dec. 19, 2018) — Coming into its third year running, Refresh Annapolis Valley has opened registration for its popular Creative Computing course for kids. Unlike previous years, the program is now free for participants. Beginning in January of 2019, Refresh’s Creative Computing course will be ready to teach kids the basics of software development using Scratch programming.
 “Computer Scientists are everywhere solving problems in very diverse corners of society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refreshing Valley Youth Recognized For Their Entrepreneurship</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/post/refreshing-youth-recognized/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/post/refreshing-youth-recognized/</guid>
      <description>Wolfville, NS, (Nov. 29, 2018) — At a recognition event for outstanding community contributors to the Kings South riding, MLA Keith Irving presented a group of Refresh Annapolis Valley youth an award for their efforts and contributions. Recipients Emma He, Gerald Kaulback, Max Caplan, and Alexander Petkov were recognized for placing first place at Start It Up, a rigorous business ideation competition hosted by the Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre.
“Entrepreneurship is crucial to the future economic success of our province and with amazing young entrepreneurs like these in our communities, I think our future is bright,” said Keith Irving MLA in a statement read in the Nova Scotia House of Assembly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>