<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrew Button on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/people/andrew-button/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Andrew Button on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/people/andrew-button/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>CO3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CO3 is a fresh bew co-working space for freelancers, entrepreneurs and independents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CO3 Is a concept created by &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button&#34;&gt;​Andrew Button&lt;/a&gt;
, a social entrepreneur based in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The mission is to create a space that further cultivates rural Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s freelance economy.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the success of his own company Mashup Lab and other social ventures ​he&amp;rsquo;s discovered a lot of hidden talent in the Maritimes which he feels needs more room to grow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a member of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-south-shore&#34;&gt;
    
        The HUB South Shore
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 himself, he knows the value of working with entrepreneurial spirited individuals and the impact it makes on self-confidence, motivation and forward thinking.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Work: Coworking</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is lots of buzz around coworking spaces as a new way for independent and SME creative professionals to engage work. Coworking is about shared office space for professionals, but it is also about a style of work that suggests there are greater opportunities working in a diverse community setting. Coworking spaces themself are diverse in structure, ranging from the community powered, real-estate centric, to highbred business incubators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In rural Nova Scotia, numerous coworking spaces are springing up. The HUB South Shore in Mahone Bay, L-Ink&amp;rsquo;d in Annapolis Royal, CO3 in Bridgewater, The Hub Yarmouth, The Hub Annapolis Valley, the Rural Innovation Centre at Acadia University. Wow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us for a virtual tour of these coworking spaces. Learn about their unique take on coworking, and how they envision redefining how we do work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>