<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keegan Francis on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/people/keegan-francis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Keegan Francis on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 17:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/people/keegan-francis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency and Blockchain: The Crash Course</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/blockchain-the-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 17:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/blockchain-the-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>This 4 hour crash course will get attendees up-to-speed on the world of cryptocurrency and the technology that powers much of it: Blockchain.
This unique opportunity runs from 5PM to 9PM, and is limited to 20 attendees. Dinner and snacks provided.
Part 1: Intro to Blockchain Fintech The Bitcoin Blockchain just had its 10 year anniversary on January 3rd, 2019. With several monumental crashes and rushes in its market, no one could say with certainty whether or not the network would be a success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digitized Reality</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/digitized-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/digitized-reality/</guid>
      <description>Come slap on a headset and enter the world of virtual reality. In this workshop, we will explore virtual reality by both examining the capabilities of commercial headsets, as well as learn how to build our own VR environments. If you can, bring a smart phone to test your uniquely constructed VR world. We can only accommodate a limited number of people for this event, so get your free ticket fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Blockchain Company</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/atlantic-blockchain-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/atlantic-blockchain-company/</guid>
      <description>We are the Atlantic Blockchain Company Atlantic Blockchain Company Inc. is an education based company operating out of Halifax, Nova Scotia, in Atlantic Canada.
Who do we help? We consult with businesses of all sizes to determine the possible adoption of blockchain technology into their existing business infrastructure.
We deliver educational seminars to universities and private venues to give the common individual the tools and definitions they need to make sense of the “crypto phenomenon” that is sweeping the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>