<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Morton Horticultural Associates on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/morton-horticultural-associates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Morton Horticultural Associates on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/morton-horticultural-associates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ag &#43; Tech = Innovation</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ag-tech-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ag-tech-innovation/</guid>
      <description>Agriculture globally is a 12 trillion dollar annual industry ripe for technology startups looking to bring new hi-tech innovations to market. Where does digital technology and agriculture meet, and what are the opportunities?&#xA;Gary Morton (Morton Horticultural Associates, Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce Agriculture Committee) will discuss this exciting technology space, and the over $160,000 (cash and in-kind services) that the AVCC has awarded locally to spark agriculture innovation. Dr. Danny Silver (Acadia Institute for Data Analytics) will look at the opportunities around ag.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gary Morton</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/gary-morton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/gary-morton/</guid>
      <description>Gary is a business development consultant/coach that for over 30 years has worked with farms, business and organization clients to find and develop new value added ideas, profit and success from what they do. This includes product development, commercialization, business planning, market development (domestic and export), product launch, training programs and managing business growth around new products and services.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
