<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Education on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Education on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Where Did All The Women Go?  Retaining Women in Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/where-did-all-the-women-go-retaining-women-in-computer-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/where-did-all-the-women-go-retaining-women-in-computer-science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the last 30 years, the number of women entering Computer Science university programs has dropped from 50% to around 10%. Once in the program, women have a higher drop out rate than men.  And women graduating with Computer Science degrees often leave the field and pursue alternate careers. &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-randy-newman&#34;&gt;Dr Randy Newman&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel&#34;&gt;Cindy Trudel&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; have been actively researching this phenomenon over the last few years. In this Refresh Annapolis Valley talk, Randy and Cindy will discuss the problem, the programs that Acadia has in place, and the needs for the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of Computer Science Education</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-computer-science-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-computer-science-education/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With an estimated 218,000 new skilled ICT workers needed in Canada by 2020 to meet the short term demands of our digital economy, focus on our educational system to address this challenge is paramount. The profound lack of diversity within the digital tech economy further complicates the response required. With changes in our provincial educational pipeline well under way, we are still early on in deploying a comprehensive response.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Join our panel discussion focused on defining challenges and solutions for Computer Science education today.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cindy Trudel</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cindy Trudel is an Instructor in Acadia University&amp;rsquo;s Departments of Computer Science, Business and Mathematics. Her primary research interest is in developing retention programs for students who have self-selected Computer Science as an area of study.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genevieve Allen Hearn</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/genevieve-allen-hearn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/genevieve-allen-hearn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Genevieve is an arts administrator, specializing in organizing cultural events and festivals. Currently, Genevieve is working for the Atlantic Public Arts Funders, organizing an Indigenous Arts Symposium for Atlantic Canada. She is part-owner and Operations Manager of The Grapevine, the Annapolis Valley’s bi-weekly arts and culture publication. Her volunteer work includes serving on the board of Uncommon Common Art, the Kentville Art Gallery Society, and the Youth Engagement Working Group for the Municipality of the County of Kings. While completing her Masters in Art-Based Community Development, Genevieve was the project manager for the &lt;a href=&#34;http://kingsculturalmap.ca&#34;&gt;Kings County Cultural Map&lt;/a&gt;. She spends every free minute raising the coolest toddler in town.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Richards</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-richards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-richards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mark has been working in the field of education for over 20 years. For the past four years Mark has been the AVRSB Consultant of Technology integration and Student Data. Prior to that, Mark spent 10 years teaching high school science/technology, was a high school vice principal and was project manager for the provincial PowerSchool implementation. Mark wrote the original Computer Programming 12 curriculum document for the province of Nova Scotia in the early 2000’s.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Baskwill</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/nick-baskwill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/nick-baskwill/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nick is a grade 5 teacher at Kingston Elementary school in Kingston, NS.  He has been teaching for 10 years. Nick completed his B. Sc from Lyndon State College, his B. Ed from Acadia University, and his M. Ed from Mount Saint Vincent University.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Ryan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sarah-ryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/sarah-ryan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A graduate of Mount Saint Vincent University, Sarah has worked in the science enrichment and education fields for over nine years. For the past three years, Sarah has been Program Director at Brilliant Labs Nova Scotia, a not-for-profit organization that supports students and educators with innovative ways to make learning fun and relevant by using tools, materials and technologies to solve everyday challenges. In this role, she is responsible for delivering programming to enhance digital literacy skills and support project-based learning initiatives for teachers, students, and community groups across Nova Scotia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
