<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Women in Tech on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/women-in-tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Women in Tech on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 10:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/women-in-tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>National Ladies Learning Code Day: Intro to UX Design</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-user-experience-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-user-experience-design/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Join thousands of Canadians coast to coast to coast taking their first steps learning about application development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With great design comes great responsibility. User experience (UX) design isn’t just about creating pretty or functioning websites - it’s about creative solutioning and trying to make people&amp;rsquo;s lives and experiences better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As application designers, we need to remember that we aren&amp;rsquo;t designing products for ourselves, but for other people. Being a UX designer allows you to work with and problem solve for a variety of different people, and empathy plays a huge part in this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women in Technology: Uncensored</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/women-in-technology-uncensored/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/women-in-technology-uncensored/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Join &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/acadia-women-in-technology-society&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Acadia Women in Technology Society&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; and Refresh Annapolis Valley for an evening of networking, refreshments, and discussion.  Guest speakers &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/lori-shepherd&#34;&gt;Lori Shepherd&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;, Chief Creative Officer Cold Furnace Studios, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel&#34;&gt;Cindy Trudel&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;, Instructor in Acadia University’s Jodrey School of Computer Science, will lead a discussion about hacking the male dominated computer science academy and industry to work for women.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Learn to Code Day: Build a Browser Extension!</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-browser-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-browser-extensions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Join thousands of Canadians coast to coast to coast taking their first steps learning about Computer Science.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At this &amp;ldquo;Women Learning Code&amp;rdquo; event, we will learn how to build web browser extensions with JavaScript. Browser extensions extend your web browser with additional features, modify web pages, and integrate your browser with the other services you use.  Extensions can help customize our browsing experience or increase productivity by reducing repetitive tasks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Did All The Women Go?  Retaining Women in Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/where-did-all-the-women-go-retaining-women-in-computer-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/where-did-all-the-women-go-retaining-women-in-computer-science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the last 30 years, the number of women entering Computer Science university programs has dropped from 50% to around 10%. Once in the program, women have a higher drop out rate than men.  And women graduating with Computer Science degrees often leave the field and pursue alternate careers. &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-randy-newman&#34;&gt;Dr Randy Newman&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel&#34;&gt;Cindy Trudel&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; have been actively researching this phenomenon over the last few years. In this Refresh Annapolis Valley talk, Randy and Cindy will discuss the problem, the programs that Acadia has in place, and the needs for the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>f5://imagination</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/f5/imagination/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;f5://imagination is a pop up exhibit focused on digital creativity.  This one day temporary exhibit features work from digital artists, makers, scratchers, computer scientists, engineers and pretendgineer, hardware hackers, lego robotics warriors, indy game developers, new media innovators, VR and AR pioneers&amp;hellip;  digital builders of all shapes, sizes, and credentials.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Schedule&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;    &lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10 AM to 12:30 PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;    &lt;dl&gt;Screening &amp; discussion of &lt;em&gt;Hidden Figures&lt;/em&gt;:  The story of a team of female African-American mathematicians who served a vital role in NASA during the early years of the U.S. space program.  Hosted by Dr. Randy Newman (Professor of Psychology, Acadia University.  &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Women in Science and Engineering at Acadia University&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;).  An area of Dr. Newman&#39;s work is in understanding factors responsible for the gender gap that persists in some areas of science, notably computer science and engineering.  &lt;strong&gt;Limited Space: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.eventbrite.ca/e/f5imagination-hidden-figures-screening-discussion-tickets-40998671129&#34;&gt;get your free ticket to secure your spot&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&#xA;    &lt;dd&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1 PM to 4:00 PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;    &lt;dl&gt;f5://imagination reception. Artists will be in attendance, light refreshments served.&lt;/dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Submissions are being accepted until midnight December 13.  To submit, fill out the below form (bottom of the page).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Learn to Code Day: Intro to AI and Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-ai-and-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-ai-and-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Join hundreds of Canadians coast to coast to coast taking their first steps learning about Computer Science. National Learn to Code Day was launched by Ladies Learning Code 5 years ago!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At this &amp;ldquo;Women Learning Code&amp;rdquo; event, we will learn about Artificial intelligence and machine learning. From Siri on your iPhone to Google Map suggestions, to recommendations for purchases during your Amazon check-out, AI is all around us.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AI and machine learning at its core is about data - and ways to make meaning of data. In this hands on workshop, we’ll learn how to put data to use for us in our everyday lives.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CODE: Debugging the Gender Gap</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;float-right&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/images/event/code-debugging-the-gender-gap/poster.jpg&#34;&#xA;    alt=&#34;CODE: Debugging the Gender Gap&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CODE: Debugging The Gender Gap&lt;/em&gt; exposes the dearth of female and minority&#xA;software engineers and explores the reasons for this gender gap and digital divide.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tech jobs are growing three times faster than our colleges are producing computer science&#xA;graduates. By 2019 there will be 182,000 jobs in information and communications technology&#xA;that will go unfilled by homegrown Canadian talent because not enough people will have the right skills.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cindy Trudel</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cindy-trudel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cindy Trudel is an Instructor in Acadia University&amp;rsquo;s Departments of Computer Science, Business and Mathematics. Her primary research interest is in developing retention programs for students who have self-selected Computer Science as an area of study.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr Randy Newman</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-randy-newman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/dr-randy-newman/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Newman is a Cognitive Neuroscientist whose primary research interest is in understanding the brain mechanisms responsible for reading and speech processes using event-related potentials and eye tracking techniques. Current research is examining the impact of a word&amp;rsquo;s spelling on how quickly we recognize spoken words.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A secondary area of interest is in understanding factors responsible for the gender gap that persists in some areas of science, notably computer science and engineering. Current research is examining the impact of girls only science-based activities (e.g., camps) on girls&amp;rsquo; career aspirations in science, as well as on their self-efficacy and their sense of belonging in science-based disciplines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lori Shepherd</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/lori-shepherd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/lori-shepherd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lori builds games. Lori also builds teams from the ground up, ensuring the effectiveness of the team through collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lori creates military based games, combining her security training, and creativity into realistic and engrossing experiences. Encompassing criminal elements, espionage, law enforcement, cyberwarfare, intelligence, and tactics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lori’s audience, in the security forum, have included police agencies, government, military and defense, legal professionals, technology sectors, consultants, and private investigators.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;International law enforcement and security organizations have worked with her in understanding and preparing for virtual world culture and threats to games associated with crime in online gaming. Lori has contributed to the INTERPOL Working Party on Information Technology Crime, regarding Gaming and Virtual Worlds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women in Science and Engineering at Acadia</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WISE (Women in Science and Engineering) at Acadia is a group of female faculty members from the &lt;a href=&#34;http://science.acadiau.ca/&#34;&gt;Faculty of Pure and Applied Science&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://kinesiology.acadiau.ca/&#34;&gt;Kinesiology&lt;/a&gt; who gather together to address the unique issues that women in academia face. The group has supported learning opportunities and award applications for Acadia women faculty members. After a &lt;a href=&#34;http://bit.ly/WISEacadia&#34;&gt;gathering held in October 2014&lt;/a&gt; additional WISE priorities have been identified related to mentoring, science camps for young women, and a course offering for undergraduates in Women and Science.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women&#39;s and Gender Studies</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-and-gender-studies-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/women-and-gender-studies-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In 1973, Acadia University became one of the first universities in Canada to offer a course in Women&amp;rsquo;s Studies. The course, entitled Women in the Modern World, was the cornerstone of a program which in three decades has developed a multi-disciplinary approach to teaching and research in gender-related issues. Faculty members from the Arts, Pure and Applied Sciences, Education, Kinesiology, and Theatre contribute to the program on a rotational basis.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
