<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Marketing on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/digital-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Marketing on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/digital-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blogging to Be Found</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/blogging-to-be-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/blogging-to-be-found/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-use-a-business-blog-to-improve-search-engine-ranking&#34;&gt;How to use a business blog to improve search engine ranking&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Upon learning simple strategies for business blogging, &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anita-kirkbride&#34;&gt;Anita Kirkbride&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&amp;rsquo;s WordPress business blog (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twirp.ca/&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twirp.ca/&#34;&gt;https://twirp.ca/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) went from ZERO to HERO in a matter of weeks and she&amp;rsquo;s coming to share with you her best tips for using a business blog to be found. Anita will share her best strategies, and walk you through how to use WordPress to get your search engine placement scores up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winning at Search Engines</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/winning-at-search-engines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/winning-at-search-engines/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What’s the point of having a website if you’re not getting any traffic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With over half of the average website’s traffic coming from search engines, it’s important to rank in search results for keywords that are not only searched frequently but also have high intent.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You’ve taken the first step, you’ve built a website you’re happy with – now,  it’s time to take out the guesswork and help your target market find what they are looking for. Identify your keywords and develop a strategy that will bring customers to you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Ideas for Your Next Social Media Campaign</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/10-ideas-for-your-next-social-media-campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/10-ideas-for-your-next-social-media-campaign/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/wes-booth&#34;&gt;Wes Booth&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; will break down and share 10 tips he&amp;rsquo;s learned over his 10 year experience in the world of social media. Everything from emerging platforms and tools you can use to promote your business, to specific tips for boosting your marketing campaign success, and how to go above and beyond for your audience and customers. Wes won&amp;rsquo;t promise you life changing results because that&amp;rsquo;s not possible, but what he can do is prepare you to be in a position to have success and offer you practical things to take away and test out on your business. Come ready to like, share, comment and put into action everything you learn!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Meetups</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/meetups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/meetups/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our monthly Refresh meetup is where the Annapolis Valley community of designers, developers and innovators come hang out.  Those interested in the creative, technical, and professional culture of digital technology endeavours in the Annapolis Valley meet and talk about all things design, technology, and entrepreneurship.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Refresh meets the second Tuesday evening of each month in the Wolfville area. These are casual affairs with short, member-interest talks followed by an opportunity to mingle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Sanford</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/alex-sanford/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/alex-sanford/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Alex is a software developer, musician, coffee enthusiast, and space geek. He was born and raised here in the Valley, and has a long time passion for science, technology, and lifelong learning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently, Alex is a Code Wrangler for Automattic, the creators of WordPress.com. Automattic has close ties with the WordPress open source project, which powers 33% of the websites on the internet. Automattic’s mission is to make the web a better place by advocating openness, freedom, diversity, and inclusivity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anita Kirkbride</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anita-kirkbride/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/anita-kirkbride/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;She&amp;rsquo;s on a mission to help small businesses understand how to use social media to serve their clients and grow sales.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Trying to keep up with ever-changing social media trends is exhausting, even for the most caffeinated among us. But Twirp Communications founder Anita Kirkbride is here to help you save all that coffee money.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anita’s social media experience extends all the way back to the 90s, when she joined the first generation of bloggers, launching a crafting blog in a flurry of cardstock, buttons, and fabric swatches. She promoted it using new-at-the-time marketing tactics like blog circles, link parties, and roundups.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Macmillan</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-macmillan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/michael-macmillan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Michael is an SEO and marketing specialist, focusing on consultancy for software &amp;amp; service companies and specializing in troubleshooting. He built his first website in 1996 and was a working professional in the digital world by 1999. Having held various roles in the digital world, he transitioned to an SEO role in 2009. Since then he has held SEO roles in-house, as leadership for an agencies SEO team, and as an independent consultant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shift! Mobile Interactive</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/shift-mobile-interactive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/shift-mobile-interactive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Digital media technology changes weekly. We help you understand digital marketing and how to use it to grow your business.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Organizations typically approach us because they are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Feeling overwhelmed by all the digital marketing options&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sick of getting “marketing tactics,” without effective and efficient methods to implement them&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On the “marketing hamster wheel” spending too much time and or ad money on digital media channels and they want better results&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Looking to rebrand or launch a brand&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Looking to launch a website&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Getting people to their website, but people aren’t converting or purchasing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Needing a marketing planning template plan, implement, measure, and adjust as things change&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Any of these sound familiar? Drop us a line!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wes Booth</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/wes-booth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/wes-booth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wes Booth literally grew up during the birth of social media. In 2006, he signed on Facebook for the first time and in 2013 he sent his first Snap. Wes started his first business when he was 14 and is now working on a project to better connect and support brands and creative talent in Nova Scotia through his social media community called We Are NS. Wes believes in Atlantic Canada 100% and is determined social media is a good place to start telling our stories. He thinks the fresh perspective and confidence that youth bring to the table could be our answer!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
