<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gary Morton on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/people/gary-morton/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gary Morton on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/people/gary-morton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ag &#43; Tech = Innovation</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ag-tech-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/ag-tech-innovation/</guid>
      <description>Agriculture globally is a 12 trillion dollar annual industry ripe for technology startups looking to bring new hi-tech innovations to market. Where does digital technology and agriculture meet, and what are the opportunities?
Gary Morton (Morton Horticultural Associates, Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce Agriculture Committee) will discuss this exciting technology space, and the over $160,000 (cash and in-kind services) that the AVCC has awarded locally to spark agriculture innovation. Dr. Danny Silver (Acadia Institute for Data Analytics) will look at the opportunities around ag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morton Horticultural Associates</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/morton-horticultural-associates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/morton-horticultural-associates/</guid>
      <description>Morton Horticultural Associates was established in 1982 to provide specialized consulting, advisory and coaching services to clients in the horticulture, agriculture and the agri-food industry. The company focus is on helping agriculture businesses and organizations chart a clear path to the future and to develop the business management skills that will get them there. The areas of expertise include industry analysis, new value-added product development and commercialization, direct marketing, agritourism, business development, strategic and business planning and market innovation strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F5://Food</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/f5-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/project/f5-food/</guid>
      <description>Measure and mix together:
1 cup of farmers
½ pound regional food distributors
2 tbsp chefs
1 cup food policy experts
1 dash of deep concern about making our regional bounty more accessible
Stir in:
2 tbsp software developers
½ cup interactive designers
4 tbsp marketers
1 pound new media entrepreneurs
Stir new media ingredients into agricultural mixture. Mix thoroughly with a group of mentors. Broil for 48 hours. Serve hot to a group of judges.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>