<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CO3 on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/co3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CO3 on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/co3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Button</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a 15 year career with various businesses and economic development organizations, Andrew felt it was about time to move from being a ‘cheerleader’ and ‘curator’ of entrepreneurship to doing something that actually produced more entrepreneurs in rural communities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;​In 2014 he founded &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mashuplab.ca/&#34;&gt;Mashup Lab&lt;/a&gt;; a for-more-than-profit company that activates rural ideas.  That same year he launched a chapter of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.awesomesouthshore.ca/&#34;&gt;Awesome Foundation&lt;/a&gt; in his community. Andrew has since gone on to launch another social enterprise - &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        CO3&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;, a fresh new coworking space for Freelancers, Entrepreneurs, and Independents located in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Work: Coworking</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is lots of buzz around coworking spaces as a new way for independent and SME creative professionals to engage work. Coworking is about shared office space for professionals, but it is also about a style of work that suggests there are greater opportunities working in a diverse community setting. Coworking spaces themself are diverse in structure, ranging from the community powered, real-estate centric, to highbred business incubators.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In rural Nova Scotia, numerous coworking spaces are springing up. The HUB South Shore in Mahone Bay, L-Ink&amp;rsquo;d in Annapolis Royal, CO3 in Bridgewater, The Hub Yarmouth, The Hub Annapolis Valley, the Rural Innovation Centre at Acadia University. Wow!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
