<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Management on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/project-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project Management on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/project-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Sucks</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/project-management-sucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/project-management-sucks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Project management seems to be one of those areas of necessary evil. Disconnected project managers who don&amp;rsquo;t really understand your work coupled with never ending meetings, charts, spreadsheets, forms, paperwork, complicated management software&amp;hellip;  Project management can feel like it is more of a barrier than a help to team productivity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/images/event/project-management-sucks/dilbert.gif&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this talk, Mike Caplan, a reluctant Software Development Manager, will explore a lightweight tool for overseeing the project processes.  Based on a simple board, this technique helps visualize workflow, expose operational problems, and reduce wasted time from excessive multitasking.  Best of all, it is a team tool that helps decentralize project management to the group.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geoff Crouse</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/geoff-crouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Geoff has more than 17 years of combined Software Engineering and Information Technology Consulting experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Technical Sales Engineer, specializing in medium to large scale Drupal CMS projects including new development, site audits and analysis, and expert support services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Account Management, coordinating customer projects with engineering and support teams from initial conception to final delivery, and continued support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Geoff&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove.  Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove pic care of Wikipedia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
