<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Side Door on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/side-door/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Side Door on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 18:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/side-door/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Enter the Side Door</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-enter-the-side-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-enter-the-side-door/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Side Door is a digital platform that matches performing artists with venues to create shows anytime, anywhere, on their own terms.  Come meet CEO &amp;amp; Co-Founder &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson&#34;&gt;Laura Simpson&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; for a fireside chat and live performance with &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/cassie-josephine&#34;&gt;Cassie Josephine&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; (Indie Folk Country princess).  Laura and Cassie will talk about the challenges artists in the music business face and how &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/side-door&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;        Side Door&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&amp;rsquo;s unique digital platform is defining a new business model capitalizing on the power of a networked community.  Learn how Side Door is poised to hit $1 million in annual ticket sales by the end of 2020.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laura Simpson</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/laura-simpson/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lover of music and truth. Listen to the poets. Founder of The Syrup Factory, Make.Do.Camp. and Side Door.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Laura Simpson is a music industry professional, living with her family in Halifax, Nova Scotia. She founded The Syrup Factory, which began hosting house concerts 2011 and offering strategy and services to artists in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She has been an organizer in the arts scene since she was 14, going to all-ages shows and then eventually taking live music photography and freelance writing about shows and artists. That led her to be a journalist for seven years, working for CBC and Rogers Radio.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
