<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Annapolis Valley Regional School Board on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/annapolis-valley-regional-school-board/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Annapolis Valley Regional School Board on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/annapolis-valley-regional-school-board/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>State of Computer Science Education</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-computer-science-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/state-of-computer-science-education/</guid>
      <description>With an estimated 218,000 new skilled ICT workers needed in Canada by 2020 to meet the short term demands of our digital economy, focus on our educational system to address this challenge is paramount. The profound lack of diversity within the digital tech economy further complicates the response required. With changes in our provincial educational pipeline well under way, we are still early on in deploying a comprehensive response.
Join our panel discussion focused on defining challenges and solutions for Computer Science education today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seed: Hacking Entrepreneurship in the Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/seed-hacking-entrepreneurship-in-the-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 18:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/seed-hacking-entrepreneurship-in-the-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>Seed is a documentary that follows an international group of programmer entrepreneurs at AngelHack: one of the most competitive global hackathons and digital business ideation competitions. Three minutes to pitch. One shot to fund their proposals.
Seed is also a gathering of our Annapolis Valley startup community. The event will feature the diversity of associations, businesses, and individuals who comprise our digital tech startup community. An assembly of our entrepreneurial family.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>