<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coworking on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/coworking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coworking on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/coworking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Button</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</guid>
      <description>After a 15 year career with various businesses and economic development organizations, Andrew felt it was about time to move from being a ‘cheerleader’ and ‘curator’ of entrepreneurship to doing something that actually produced more entrepreneurs in rural communities.&#xA;​In 2014 he founded Mashup Lab; a for-more-than-profit company that activates rural ideas. That same year he launched a chapter of the Awesome Foundation in his community. Andrew has since gone on to launch another social enterprise - CO3 , a fresh new coworking space for Freelancers, Entrepreneurs, and Independents located in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CO3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3/</guid>
      <description>CO3 is a fresh bew co-working space for freelancers, entrepreneurs and independents.&#xA;CO3 Is a concept created by ​Andrew Button , a social entrepreneur based in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;The mission is to create a space that further cultivates rural Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s freelance economy.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Through the success of his own company Mashup Lab and other social ventures ​he&amp;rsquo;s discovered a lot of hidden talent in the Maritimes which he feels needs more room to grow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUB Kentville</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville/</guid>
      <description>Get Inspired, Get Connected, Get involved. HUB spaces provide an inspirational home to members and are a focal point for change within the local communities.&#xA;What is the Hub? The HUB is about the power of innovation through collaboration.&#xA;We believe there is no shortage of good ideas to solve the issues of our time. But there is an acute lack of collaboration and support structures to help make them happen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Davis</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-davis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/mark-davis/</guid>
      <description>Founder / CEO at colovo and co-founder of The HUB Yarmouth .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Hall</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matt-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matt-hall/</guid>
      <description>I make stuff happen at Agile*, an independent geoscience idea factory in Canada.&#xA;We build awesome knowledge engines for organizations (mostly wikis), and we hone our skills in subsurface science&amp;hellip; We have most recently been working on geothermal reservoir description. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked the Montney tight gas of Alberta and BC, frontier exploration in the Canadian Beaufort Sea, the Athabasca oil sands, the Norwegian North Sea. I also worked in software for several years, as an advocate of integrated volume visualization and interpretation and viz room pilot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Doucette</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matthew-doucette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matthew-doucette/</guid>
      <description>I am a video game developer (Xbox 360 &amp;amp; PC). Check out my video game company, Xona Games, and my first professional video game, Duality ZF, for more information. My only parter is my twin brother, Jason Doucette.&#xA;Here is the Duality ZF April 2009 trailer:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The HUB South Shore</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-south-shore/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-south-shore/</guid>
      <description>The HUB South Shore is a coworking space that connects progressive businesses and people together so innovation and enterprise can thrive. We enjoy the freedom to run our own lives and depend on the motivation, productivity, and creativity that comes from working with others.&#xA;Our vision is for a self-reliant rural economy rooted in the collaboration of local entrepreneurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The HUB Yarmouth</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-yarmouth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-yarmouth/</guid>
      <description>Creative shared space The Hub is a co-working space for creative and social entrepreneurs in Yarmouth, Nova Scotia, Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Work: Coworking</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</guid>
      <description>There is lots of buzz around coworking spaces as a new way for independent and SME creative professionals to engage work. Coworking is about shared office space for professionals, but it is also about a style of work that suggests there are greater opportunities working in a diverse community setting. Coworking spaces themself are diverse in structure, ranging from the community powered, real-estate centric, to highbred business incubators.&#xA;In rural Nova Scotia, numerous coworking spaces are springing up.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
