<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coworking on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/coworking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coworking on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/coworking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Button</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a 15 year career with various businesses and economic development organizations, Andrew felt it was about time to move from being a ‘cheerleader’ and ‘curator’ of entrepreneurship to doing something that actually produced more entrepreneurs in rural communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​In 2014 he founded &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mashuplab.ca/&#34;&gt;Mashup Lab&lt;/a&gt;; a for-more-than-profit company that activates rural ideas.  That same year he launched a chapter of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.awesomesouthshore.ca/&#34;&gt;Awesome Foundation&lt;/a&gt; in his community. Andrew has since gone on to launch another social enterprise - &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3&#34;&gt;
    
        CO3
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, a fresh new coworking space for Freelancers, Entrepreneurs, and Independents located in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andrew&amp;rsquo;s work with over 1,000 Entrepreneurs located in rural has convinced him that great ideas can come from anywhere. His passion and energy is focused on one thing: unleashing entrepreneurial potential in rural communities that has yet to be inspired into action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Andrew&amp;rsquo;s banner image is a Captain Canuck inspired rendition of artwork blatantly ripped off the Mashup Lab website.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CO3</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/co3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CO3 is a fresh bew co-working space for freelancers, entrepreneurs and independents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CO3 Is a concept created by &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/andrew-button&#34;&gt;​Andrew Button&lt;/a&gt;
, a social entrepreneur based in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The mission is to create a space that further cultivates rural Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s freelance economy.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the success of his own company Mashup Lab and other social ventures ​he&amp;rsquo;s discovered a lot of hidden talent in the Maritimes which he feels needs more room to grow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a member of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-south-shore&#34;&gt;
    
        The HUB South Shore
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 himself, he knows the value of working with entrepreneurial spirited individuals and the impact it makes on self-confidence, motivation and forward thinking.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HUB Kentville</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/hub-kentville/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Get Inspired, Get Connected, Get involved. HUB spaces provide an inspirational home to members and are a focal point for change within the local communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-the-hub&#34;&gt;What is the Hub?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HUB is about the power of innovation through collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe there is no shortage of good ideas to solve the issues of our time. But there is an acute lack of collaboration and support structures to help make them happen. The HUB was founded to address this need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We set out to create spaces that combine the best of a trusted community, innovation lab, business incubator and the comforts of home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spaces with all the tools and trimmings needed to grow and develop innovative ventures for the world. But above all, spaces for meaningful encounters, exchange and inspiration, full of diverse people doing amazing things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea has been spreading like wildfire and resulted in the emergence of a global movement. To date, there are 25+ open HUBs and many more in the making, from London to San Francisco, Johannesburg, Melbourne and Sao Paulo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;mission&#34;&gt;Mission&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To become a global network of connected communities that enable collaborative ventures for a better world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the HUB, people from every profession, background and culture are being united by one thing: the imagination and drive to pursue enterprising ideas for the world. These are the people who see and do things differently and have entrepreneurial passion to create sustainable impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HUB is becoming the place they call home.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Hall</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matt-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matt-hall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I make stuff happen at Agile*, an independent geoscience idea factory in Canada.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We build awesome knowledge engines for organizations (mostly wikis), and we hone our skills in subsurface science&amp;hellip; We have most recently been working on geothermal reservoir description. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked the Montney tight gas of Alberta and BC, frontier exploration in the Canadian Beaufort Sea, the Athabasca oil sands, the Norwegian North Sea. I also worked in software for several years, as an advocate of integrated volume visualization and interpretation and viz room pilot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since 2001 I&amp;rsquo;ve been a registered professional Geologist and professional Geophysicist in Alberta. I review technical papers for SEG&amp;rsquo;s journal Geophysics. I sometimes teach university courses. With my Agile colleague, I write a blog at agilegeoscience.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specialties: Seismic interpretation and analysis, sedimentology, sequence stratigraphy, geoscience software, integrated reservoir description, knowledge sharing, writing&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The HUB South Shore</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-south-shore/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organization/the-hub-south-shore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The HUB South Shore is a coworking space that connects progressive businesses and people together so innovation and enterprise can thrive. We enjoy the freedom to run our own lives and depend on the motivation, productivity, and creativity that comes from working with others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our vision is for a self-reliant rural economy rooted in the collaboration of local entrepreneurs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Work: Coworking</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is lots of buzz around coworking spaces as a new way for independent and SME creative professionals to engage work. Coworking is about shared office space for professionals, but it is also about a style of work that suggests there are greater opportunities working in a diverse community setting. Coworking spaces themself are diverse in structure, ranging from the community powered, real-estate centric, to highbred business incubators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In rural Nova Scotia, numerous coworking spaces are springing up. The HUB South Shore in Mahone Bay, L-Ink&amp;rsquo;d in Annapolis Royal, CO3 in Bridgewater, The Hub Yarmouth, The Hub Annapolis Valley, the Rural Innovation Centre at Acadia University. Wow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us for a virtual tour of these coworking spaces. Learn about their unique take on coworking, and how they envision redefining how we do work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>