<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>We Are NS on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/we-are-ns/</link>
    <description>Recent content in We Are NS on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/we-are-ns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Ideas for Your Next Social Media Campaign</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/10-ideas-for-your-next-social-media-campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/10-ideas-for-your-next-social-media-campaign/</guid>
      <description>Wes Booth will break down and share 10 tips he&amp;rsquo;s learned over his 10 year experience in the world of social media. Everything from emerging platforms and tools you can use to promote your business, to specific tips for boosting your marketing campaign success, and how to go above and beyond for your audience and customers. Wes won&amp;rsquo;t promise you life changing results because that&amp;rsquo;s not possible, but what he can do is prepare you to be in a position to have success and offer you practical things to take away and test out on your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wes Booth</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/wes-booth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/wes-booth/</guid>
      <description>Wes Booth literally grew up during the birth of social media. In 2006, he signed on Facebook for the first time and in 2013 he sent his first Snap. Wes started his first business when he was 14 and is now working on a project to better connect and support brands and creative talent in Nova Scotia through his social media community called We Are NS. Wes believes in Atlantic Canada 100% and is determined social media is a good place to start telling our stories.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>