<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/artificial-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artificial Intelligence on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 19:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/topics/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Life: Meet R2-Weed2</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-r2-weed2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/the-startup-life-r2-weed2/</guid>
      <description>Technology-driven agricultural experimentation. Iterative product testing. Validated machine learning. Pivot. Pivot. Pivot. Welcome to the ag-tech startup world of Teric Greenan and Nexus Robotics .&#xA;With Nexus Robotics , Teric is applying Artificial Intelligence to building a reliable and cost-effective way to produce crops. Their autonomous robot R2-Weed2 is capable of cutting and spraying weeds, fertilizing crops, and collect data about growing conditions. Teric will talk about his team&amp;rsquo;s start up journey, and the amazing technological innovations they are applying to revolutionize agriculture as we know it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Learn to Code Day: Intro to AI and Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-ai-and-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 12:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/national-learn-to-code-day-intro-to-ai-and-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Join hundreds of Canadians coast to coast to coast taking their first steps learning about Computer Science. National Learn to Code Day was launched by Ladies Learning Code 5 years ago!&#xA;At this &amp;ldquo;Women Learning Code&amp;rdquo; event, we will learn about Artificial intelligence and machine learning. From Siri on your iPhone to Google Map suggestions, to recommendations for purchases during your Amazon check-out, AI is all around us.&#xA;AI and machine learning at its core is about data - and ways to make meaning of data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Doucette</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matthew-doucette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matthew-doucette/</guid>
      <description>I am a video game developer (Xbox 360 &amp;amp; PC). Check out my video game company, Xona Games, and my first professional video game, Duality ZF, for more information. My only parter is my twin brother, Jason Doucette.&#xA;Here is the Duality ZF April 2009 trailer:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
