<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshav.github.io/topics/software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshav.github.io/topics/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Greene</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/person/charlie-greene/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/person/charlie-greene/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Charlie is a software developer and system administrator at The REDspace. He is alumni from &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/colibri-software&#34;&gt;
    
        Colibri Software
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 where he worked for two years, ever since graduating from Acadia University with a Honors degree in Computer Science with Co-Op option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlie&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by the work of Ruby the painting elephant.  True story.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Jordan</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/person/chris-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/person/chris-jordan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chris is a software developer with 16+ years experience with Henry Schein.  Not to be pigeonholed, he&amp;rsquo;s got his hand in all sorts of things: Top tier support for an installation base spanning 2000+ customers, Brand development, Application planning and development, Database design, Documentation, Testing, Training, Training material development: web, print and video, Customer support, Installer creation, Phone system programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chris&amp;rsquo; profile pic is a mashup of a picture of his swiped from Facebook and R2D2.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HarvestHand</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/harvesthand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/harvesthand/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HarvestHand is a community platform dedicated to strengthening regional food systems. We&amp;rsquo;re passionate about supporting farms with CSA&amp;rsquo;s to become more profitable using HarvestHand CSA Software, helping communities eat better through the HarvestHand Community, creating good jobs in rural communities, and building new media solutions that make sharing the harvest easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our vision is to create new media solutions that strengthen regional food systems&amp;rsquo; ability to succeed in value oriented approaches to production, distribution, consumption and community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Mandate is to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the profitability of Community Shared Agriculture (CSA) farms through the ease and functionality of HarvestHand CSA Software Platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create localized and fairly paid employment opportunities in rural communities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make it easy for citizens to locate, join and remain a member of a CSA farm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a space for exploration of ideas, identification of problems and creation of solutions related to local food systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build out best of regional food tooling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;flex-video&#34;&gt;
    &lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/qNxWThFGa5M&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justin Bezanson</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/person/justin-bezanson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/person/justin-bezanson/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since 2000 I have continued to expand my knowledge and skills and worked hard to be the best developer I can be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I enjoy meeting challenges and working hard to find creative and user friendly solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My goal is to continually improve my development process, delivering higher quality and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specialties: PHP, ASP.NET MVC, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, CodeIgniter, Zend Framework, AJAX, Windows, Linux, MySQL, SQL Server, WordPress, ASP.NET&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Justin, pictured here, &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; The Thing from the Fantastic Four.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keith Diehl</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/person/keith-diehl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/person/keith-diehl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Keith is a webmaster for CED Solutions.  An expert in all things Coldfusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keith&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by Vincent van Gogh&amp;rsquo;s Portrait of Camille Roulin.  Header image swiped from &lt;em&gt;The Walt Disney Story of Our Friend the Atom&lt;/em&gt; (1956) by Heinz Haber.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Labnet Dental Lab Systems</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Labnet Dental Lab Systems offers the Dental Lab industry&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive and powerful management systems with solutions suited for labs of all sizes and budgets. Whether your lab is a thriving multi-site corporation or a one-technician miracle lab, we have a perfect fit for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Henry Schein company, you can depend on Labnet Dental Lab Systems for stability and providing your dentists with the latest technological advancements. When you are operating within tight deadlines, the last thing you should worry about is your software. Stability in your software means consistency and piece of mind in your lab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Henry Schein’s commitment to software in dentistry is unparalleled. No other company is in the unique position of developing software for both dentists and laboratories. The internet link between the labs and dentists shows the foresight one expects from industry leaders Labnet Dental Lab Systems and Dentrix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://labnet.net/products/labnet/index.html&#34;&gt;Labnet&lt;/a&gt;: The most powerful lab management software ever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://labnet.net/products/supplynet/index.html&#34;&gt;Supplynet&lt;/a&gt;: The leading inventory management application in our industry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.labnext.net/&#34;&gt;Labnext&lt;/a&gt;: Web based lab management software designed specifically for digital dentistry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ddxdental.com/&#34;&gt;DDX&lt;/a&gt;: Share pertinent information with your accounts at your convenience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Caplan</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/person/michael-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/person/michael-caplan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mike has been active as a web application developer and web designer for 16 years, working in the non-profit, university, retail, agricultural, and dental industries. He is a founding partner of &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/harvesthand&#34;&gt;
    
        HarvestHand
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, a platform that services Community Shared Agriculture farms. More recently, Mike founded &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley&#34;&gt;
    
        Refresh Annapolis Valley
    
&lt;/a&gt;
, a new media professional association to help grow the Valley&amp;rsquo;s technology industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike is the Software Development Manager for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://refreshav.github.io/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems&#34;&gt;
    
        Labnet Dental Lab Systems
    
&lt;/a&gt;
 division of Henry Schein - a Fortune 300 company with a small footprint here in Wolfville.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pierre Clouthier</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/person/pierre-clouthier/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/person/pierre-clouthier/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Co-founder, President, Progeny Genealogy Inc., specialising in computer graphics software for genealogy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progeny Genealogy</title>
      <link>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/progeny-genealogy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://refreshav.github.io/organization/progeny-genealogy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Progeny Genealogy is the leading developer of family tree software and other useful, easy-to-use genealogy research resources, including &lt;a href=&#34;http://progenygenealogy.com/Products/FamilyTreeCharts.aspx&#34;&gt;Charting Companion&lt;/a&gt;™, &lt;a href=&#34;http://progenygenealogy.com/Products/TimelineCharts.aspx&#34;&gt;Genelines&lt;/a&gt;™ and &lt;a href=&#34;http://progenygenealogy.com/Products/FamilyMaps.aspx&#34;&gt;Map My Family Tree&lt;/a&gt;™. More than pretty charts, our genealogy software programs are also powerful research tools.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>