<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The HUB South Shore on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/the-hub-south-shore/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The HUB South Shore on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/organizations/the-hub-south-shore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Matt Hall</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matt-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/person/matt-hall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I make stuff happen at Agile*, an independent geoscience idea factory in Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We build awesome knowledge engines for organizations (mostly wikis), and we hone our skills in subsurface science&amp;hellip; We have most recently been working on geothermal reservoir description. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked the Montney tight gas of Alberta and BC, frontier exploration in the Canadian Beaufort Sea, the Athabasca oil sands, the Norwegian North Sea. I also worked in software for several years, as an advocate of integrated volume visualization and interpretation and viz room pilot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Work: Coworking</title>
      <link>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 19:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://refreshannapolisvalley.org/event/redefining-work-coworking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is lots of buzz around coworking spaces as a new way for independent and SME creative professionals to engage work. Coworking is about shared office space for professionals, but it is also about a style of work that suggests there are greater opportunities working in a diverse community setting. Coworking spaces themself are diverse in structure, ranging from the community powered, real-estate centric, to highbred business incubators.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In rural Nova Scotia, numerous coworking spaces are springing up. The HUB South Shore in Mahone Bay, L-Ink&amp;rsquo;d in Annapolis Royal, CO3 in Bridgewater, The Hub Yarmouth, The Hub Annapolis Valley, the Rural Innovation Centre at Acadia University. Wow!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
